Subtitles: Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu
The Russian people join you
in mourning President Hassan.
We both know the opposition
that undid him had outside help.
I just got off the phone
with the Russian foreign minister.
He said that he would be coming
to the United Nations in five hours
with the Russian premier
to sign the treaty as scheduled.
The credit for that is all yours.
It's good to be back in the game.
Elements
inside the Russian government
were behind both the assassination
of President Hassan
and the supply
of nuclear material to his enemies.
The Russian government?
The Russians inserted
Dana Walsh at CTU months ago.
She was their agent.
If Bauer gets to her,
this will all be finished.
I want to know
who killed Renee Walker.
Renee's dead? I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
- I can give you the hitter.
- I want more than names, I want proof!
I have proof.
An audio file.
Film.
- Where?
- First I want my immunity deal back.
I'm sorry.
I won't give her immunity.
I believe she knows
the names of the people who facilitated
the assassination
of President Hassan,
people working
within the Russian government.
I won't allow it.
You don't want to know the truth.
What I want is to keep
the Russians at the table.
Allegations of this sort
will drive them away.
I've arranged a helicopter to fly you
from CTU to McGuire Air Force Base.
You're locking me down.
I'm taking this helicopter.
Tell your men to drop their weapons
or you're gonna die.
Out of the copter now!
All security to the helipad.
Security to the helipad now.
Call the FAA, Air Force,
say that we have a stolen helicopter
that needs to be forced down.
Jack, it's Chloe.
What are you doing?
Talk to me.
- Can you hear me?
- He can hear you.
Comm's on, he's just not answering.
Damn it.
Air Force choppers
are closing in on his position.
Mr. Bauer, you are ordered
to turn the aircraft around
and return to CTU.
I repeat,
turn the aircraft around now.
Jack's descending.
Air Force choppers are in pursuit.
This is crazy.
Come back to CTU.
NYPD, this is Ranger One.
Suspect just landed
on the Cooper Building.
We're gonna circle
and maintain visual contact.
We have a visual on NYPD.
Two units approaching the building.
They're one block out.
Suspect's on the fire escape.
He's descending to ground level.
We've lost him.
Attempting to reacquire.
Dispatch, this is unit 27.
We're at the building,
but we've lost the suspect.
Copy. We'll widen the perimeter.
What is Jack doing?
He's not letting this go.
Dana has proof about the Russians.
He'll probably come after her.
That's crazy. She's locked down.
Jack knows he can't get to her.
He'll either figure it out
or he'll die trying.
Go on the field.
Meet with NYPD
and coordinate an interagency search.
Bring in whoever you need.
Use satellite and traffic cam.
Maybe we can track him from here.
On it.
Keep me looped in
on the search status.
No, I don't want to be
updated in ten minutes.
I want a real-time uplink.
They still haven't been able
to lock Jack down.
They lost him. He landed the chopper
and escaped on foot.
NYPD is securing a perimeter.
CTU is coordinating
an interagency search.
If Jack gets this evidence
and exposes the Russians,
the agreement is over.
The peace agreement
may not be the only casualty.
You covered up
the Russians' involvement.
That's grounds for impeachment.
Possibly a criminal indictment.
You crossed a line.
But it may not be too late
to step back and limit the damage.
- How?
- Expose the Russians.
Grant Dana Walsh immunity
in exchange for evidence.
We'll launch an investigation through
transparent international channels.
Which will effectively end
- the peace deal.
- But it will save your administration.
There is still a chance
CTU will find Jack.
Even if they do,
the evidence is still out there.
Eventually, it will surface.
I know better than anyone
how much this means to you.
How much you've sacrificed
personally
to make it happen.
We are so close.
And we will be again.
If not during your administration,
then during the next one.
I wish I could believe that.
Ethan, I want you to prepare...
a statement
announcing our withdrawal
from this accord.
We have a...
a press conference in 40 minutes.
I'll make the announcement then.
As hard as this is,
you're doing the right thing.
It's over.
I won't go through
with the peace deal.
Because of Bauer.
Because the evidence
implicating the Russians,
that I helped cover up.
It is potentially too lethal.
I agree.
Doesn't sound
like you have much of a choice.
I'm surprised.
I expected more of a fight from you.
I'm nothing if not pragmatic.
Although I am disappointed.
I'm afraid you have to find
some other way to repair your legacy.
My own personal
disappointment aside,
it's a loss for the world.
Yes, it is.
Ethan's drafting my statement.
I need to call Mrs. Hassan.
Hope she'll forgive me,
for keeping the truth from her.
Before, there is one thing
you might consider.
A way to preserve the peace deal.
The peace deal is over.
You said so.
I said it was over,
if the evidence comes out.
Obviously,
you can't grant Walsh immunity.
The evidence
would become public record.
You need to control the evidence
by keeping Walsh off the grid.
Off the grid?
Classify her as an enemy combatant,
and incarcerate her.
There is a private firm
I can recommend.
They're effective
and discreet.
I have them standing by.
Sounds like you've been giving this
a lot of thought.
This evidence
is hanging over your head.
You need to deal with it.
We can't keep Walsh
locked up indefinitely.
You wouldn't have to.
Ms. Walsh may not give up
the information willingly,
but she will give it up.
And once we have it,
it won't matter what she claims.
You're talking
about using physical coercion.
I know how deeply this offends,
your public and private sensibilities.
It is repugnant,
even immoral.
But isn't morality relative,
considering what's at stake here?
You are still talking about torture.
I'm talking
about preserving a peace accord
that is crucial
to the security of this nation.
And that can only happen,
if you acquire
and control the evidence.
Believe me,
I don't make these suggestions lightly.
I appreciate the implications.
I've tried to be as open
and candid with you,
as I've been with anyone.
And the truth is, I regret
many of my own actions
when I was president.
But I've also had the time
and the distance
to see past them to a place of clear
and deep understanding.
What do you understand?
Wielding the kind of power
that I once had and you have now,
can change the world.
But that often requires making
impossible choices
that challenge
our most sacred ideals.
If you're not willing to do that,
you should take Ethan's advice,
and pull out now.
This was taken eight minutes ago
on the corner of 25th and Cleveland.
Give Cole this information,
have him redirect his search.
The President's calling for you.
Put her through.
Have you made any progress
in finding Jack Bauer?
Not yet. We're still searching.
I think it's safe to assume
he's on his way to CTU
and that Dana Walsh is his target.
That's why I'm calling.
I want Walsh transferred
to a safe house off-site.
I've doubled the security
around Dana Walsh.
This is the safest place
for her to be.
Your opinion notwithstanding,
I'd feel more comfortable,
with her in a place
where she can't be tracked.
Agents from a private security firm,
are coming to pick her up.
A private security firm?
You know as well as I do
that Jack has contacts,
throughout the government,
some of whom might be sympathetic
to his situation.
I'm not suggesting
that you're one of those people.
I just want to take
every precaution.
I'm sending over
the transfer order now.
The agent in charge
of the escort team
is named Mark Bledsoe.
Should be arriving in a few minutes.
Understood.
Thank you.
I know this was difficult,
but you did well.
These men of yours,
I want them to use
every method of non-coercive
interrogation available to them.
I've already given
that standing order.
No one wants this to get ugly.
It's already ugly.
Thanks.
I don't need the chargers.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Please, come back now.
This has got to stop.
I need you to get me access
to Dana Walsh.
The President said she's lying.
It's the President who's lying,
to protect the peace agreement.
Even if she is,
she must have good reason.
Besides, it's not your call,
it's the President's.
She's covering up the terrorist attack.
She no longer has the call.
You don't want to go against me.
Are you threatening me?
I'm trying to ask you for help.
Put me in a room with Dana Walsh.
You're being hunted
by every law enforcement agency.
You're not thinking clearly.
I'm the only one who is.
You can't just go against everyone.
Please, just come in here,
and we'll figure this out
before you get yourself killed.
Forget it.
I'll figure out another way.
Wait.
What?
If you do get the evidence from Dana,
what are you gonna do?
I want the people who are responsible,
to be held accountable.
All I need to do is expose them.
The President's having her
transferred out of CTU.
Why?
I'm not sure.
She hired a private security firm.
- Where are they taking her?
- I don't know.
Find out.
I'll call you back.
Okay. I will.
Thanks.
Yes?
Jim, it's Jack Bauer.
Heard you got
the whole damn city after you.
I need your help.
I'm running out of places to go.
Running out?
I'd say gone.
- What'd you do this time?
- The less you know, the better.
- For who?
- For both of us.
I'm gonna need weapons and equipment.
Can you make that happen?
I can make just about anything happen.
You already know that.
The problem is
that you're a walking bull's-eye.
Last thing in the world I need
is you on my doorstep.
You wouldn't have one
if it wasn't for me.
I'm calling in a favor.
I'll tell you what I want, and I want
it ready when I get there. Okay?
Well, I see you haven't lost
your personal touch.
I'm gonna need a comm unit, two MP5s,
an assortment of assault rifles
and body armor.
Hold on a second.
I also need
a full surveillance package.
It's me. We're at CTU.
- You have Walsh?
- Not yet.
I wanted
to talk about something before.
- Is there a problem?
- We quickly put this team together,
and we didn't discuss what to do
once we've extracted the information.
Hand her back to CTU.
Without the evidence,
she's harmless.
Even without it, she can make
accusations that might stick.
- You can't afford that.
- What are you suggesting?
We can make it look like she was killed
while she was trying to escape.
Wouldn't be difficult.
We're not willing
to go down that path.
You hired me to clean up this situation.
That's what needs to happen.
Talk it over with the client,
but I need to know soon.
Sir?
Yes, okay, I'll let you know.
Mr. Bledsoe?
Chloe O'Brian, acting director of CTU.
- Heard you've had a rough day.
- Yeah, you could say that.
- I'll take you to Dana Walsh.
- Thank you.
- Where are you taking her?
- I can't disclose that information.
The whole point of this exercise
is to keep Walsh off the grid.
Yes, but I'm responsible
for this prisoner.
You were given a presidential order
to turn over the prisoner.
I'm gonna need to see that order.
You should've received it already.
We didn't. Like you said, we've had
a rough day. We were hit by an EMP
and our systems are still down.
We don't have a lot of time.
Look, I can't let you take her
unless I see the order.
So, you can wait.
Might take an hour or more.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to be so by-the-book.
I was just promoted,
and I just want to make sure
that I dot all my I's and cross the T's.
- Satisfied?
- Yeah, great.
Good morning, Ms. Walsh.
My name is Mark Bledsoe.
The president's ordered your transfer
to an off-site facility.
You've been designated an enemy
combatant by special executive order.
What do you mean off-site facility?
It's a secure location.
Chloe, what the hell is going on?
Where's Bauer?
Where's my deal?
Just do what he says.
We can do it the hard way
or the easy way.
- But you're leaving here with us.
- Don't let them do this. Please.
They'll kill me.
Chloe, please.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Let's get units
on these two intersections.
Check anyone passing through.
I'll ask Transit Police
to lock down these subways.
Chloe, we're still searching.
No sign of Jack.
He just called me.
- What?
- He wants me to help him get to Dana.
- What did you tell him?
- That she's being transferred
and I would give him the address.
And I almost did.
But I can't.
I'm under presidential orders.
Besides, I don't think he's right.
He's not thinking clearly.
We have to find him
before he gets himself killed.
What if Jack is thinking clearly?
If he's right, if the president's lying,
and this conspiracy is real,
we might be
on the wrong side of this.
Bottom line is, we were given orders
to bring him in.
- That's what we're gonna do.
- All right.
I need everyone's attention, please.
We're mobilizing a sting operation
in the field to be led by Agent Ortiz.
The target is Jack Bauer.
Let's get to work.
Did you get what I need?
Nice to see you again, too, Jack.
- Did you get it or not?
- Yeah, it's right over there.
Everything you asked for...
right there.
I've been checking the scanners.
All the agencies
are looking for you.
But nobody will say what you did.
It's not about what I did.
They're afraid of what I'm gonna do.
I don't know what they did to you,
but it must have be pretty bad.
I got to make a phone call.
It's me. You find out
where they're taking Dana?
Think about what you're doing.
Just give me the address.
- It's not too late to turn yourself in.
- Will you give me the address or not?
Dana is being taken to a safe house
in the Middle Village.
It's an industrial laundry
at 141 Juniper Valley Road.
That's about ten minutes from here.
I'll leave now.
Call me when you arrive. I'm working
on pulling up the interior specs.
I'll be able to guide you in.
Chloe, thanks.
I know I've put you in a spot.
I'll get back to you.
I might need you later.
You can't come back here again.
- Besides that, we're even now.
- I'll let you know when we're even.
Jim, please.
I need your help, okay?
O'Brian briefed you?
We're drawing Bauer to this location
where he thinks Dana is being held.
It's an industrial laundry
the DEA seized a year ago.
CTU's been using it as a safe house,
but Jack can't know this.
Bauer's a highly skilled operative.
Make everything
as credible as possible.
He'll be expecting sentries,
so Beck,
you're out front.
Greer, you take the back.
You two will be stationed inside.
Everyone stays out of sight
until Jack's between our choke points.
We do the takedown when,
and only when I give the order.
We get this right,
we take Jack by surprise
before he has a chance to fight back.
Gear up.
Jack's ten minutes out.
- What's your status?
- We're getting ready on site.
Remember, non-lethal force.
I don't want to hurt him either,
but I can't tell my men not to defend
themselves if they are in danger.
You know that.
He's calling me when he arrives.
I'll let you know when that happens.
All right.
Let's go, guys, let's go.
I have a final draft
of your statement.
I think it best for now to...
cite President Hassan's death,
as the reason for your withdrawing.
Then after the dust has settled,
we can start prosecuting the Russians
through back channels.
I've chosen not to withdraw.
And I'm keeping
the press conference as scheduled.
I don't understand.
Dana Walsh is being moved from CTU
to a private detention facility.
She'll be off the grid,
out of Jack Bauer's reach.
I've authorized
a private interrogation team
to acquire the evidence.
Acquire the evidence?
Once we have it, she'll be irlevant.
Keeping the truth from Bauer
is one thing...
but authorizing the illegal detention
and torture of a prisoner?
How far are you willing to go
to protect this lie?
As far as necessary
to preserve this treaty.
It's vital to the security
of this nation.
And what I am doing
is for the greater good.
This was Logan's idea.
The decision was mine.
And I stand behind it.
Please listen to what I'm saying.
I think this is about
more than the greater good.
I think your presidency
has cost you your marriage
and your children.
And you think that this treaty
- will somehow redeem that loss...
- Ethan, that's enough.
You've made this personal,
and you've lost your way.
I've known you long enough
to see that.
I implore you...
take a step back,
look at this clearly.
That's enough.
I've explained my reasons.
I appreciate your objections,
but the debate is over.
So, let's move on.
Unless you stop
what's being done in your name,
I can't be a part
of this any longer.
Don't worry, I'll keep it to myself.
I'll cite my health
as the reason for my resignation.
After all, I'm... here
against doctor's orders.
Please.
We are almost there!
You can't just abandon me like this.
I'm not abandoning you.
I'm listening to my conscience.
Anyway,
you've got Charles Logan now.
Only room for one of us.
Madam President.
Look at me.
My hand is shaking.
I would be concerned if it weren't.
What you've agreed to take on is not
something that could be treated lightly.
I keep thinking that people
will accuse me of grabbing for power.
Exploiting my husband's death.
Which couldn't be
further from the truth.
Still, some people
may perceive it that way.
Remember what father said?
He said the best way
to dispel public misperception
is to address it directly.
Good.
I will take his advice.
Jamot, will you excuse us?
Of course.
I just need to remind you
that the other delegates
are expecting you in 20 minutes.
I'll be ready.
Mother, I'm sorry
for being so selfish earlier.
You were afraid.
You lost your father today.
And you were afraid
of losing me as well.
I still am.
This peace agreement,
Father died for...
How can so many people be
so violently against it?
Some people are so invested
in their fear and hatred that...
peace is the most threatening thing
they can imagine.
- Chloe, you still there?
- Yes.
I'm at the site.
- I only see one man out front.
- I found a schematic of the building.
There's a side entrance
to the north of the loading dock.
I got it.
It looks like
it's out of the sentry's line of sight.
According to the schematic, there's
an enclosed room at the SW corner.
- That's where they must keeping her.
- Copy that. I got go. I'm moving in.
He's going into the dock entrance
heading towards the takedown point.
I see him.
He's moving into the building
and headed towards you.
- Stay sharp.
- Copy that. We're ready.
I got a visual on the room.
No hostiles in sight.
- I'm going to try and grab her.
- Be careful, Jack.
Okay, copy that.
He's almost at the takedown point.
Copy that.
On my way.
Hopkins, we're moving in.
Son of a bitch.
Put your weapons down!
Put your weapons down now!
I can't do that!
If you don't, I'll kill him!
Put that gun down now!
Put your weapons down now!
Now!
Put 'em down!
Tell them to get down.
- Do it.
- Get on the ground.
Now!
Cole, slowly advance towards me.
Kick the guns over in my direction.
Get out of my line of sight.
How did you know?
I know Chloe.
You're gonna call CTU.
You're gonna tell her you've got me
locked down and ready for transport.
Put it on speaker.
It's Cole.
Go ahead.
What's happening?
We've got Jack. He's locked down.
- Is he okay?
- He's fine.
- What about your men?
- They're all right.
I know I should feel relieved,
but I just feel worse.
Like you said, Chloe,
it's for his own good.
I'll talk to him when he gets here.
- Lock your men down.
- What are your plans?
Lock 'em down!
All right,
- what now?
- Follow me.
Take a seat.
You're why I'm here.
I knew Chloe would send you.
- You're the only reason I risked it.
- What do you want with me?
Help me gain access to Dana Walsh.
I know that you don't want to be a part
of this cover-up.
President Taylor
wants the peace agreement so badly,
she's willing to lie about the Russian's
involvement in the attack,
and I can't let that happen.
How can you be sure?
Because she told me to my face!
She said it was more important
than anything the Russians have done.
Why the hell do you think
she came down to CTU to talk to me?
She didn't want me
to give the evidence.
She wanted to shut me up
and lock me down.
Damn it,
your hands aren't clean in this.
You protected Dana while
she was operating for the Russians.
You lied for her,
which enabled the Russians
to provide nuclear materials
to Hassan's opposition.
They facilitated his assassination
and what,
you lost four men?
I am giving you an opportunity
to fix it,
to make the people that are responsible
for today's events accountable.
You got a decision to make.
- Now, what if you're wrong?
- I'm not.
I can't do this on my own.
Your call.
Chloe says she's in a safe house
a few miles from here.
We'll notify CTU about your men
within the next two hours.
Right now it's imperative
that they think I took you hostage.
Get up!
We've been hearing speculation
that Dalia Hassan will be making
her first official statement
as the provisional head of state
of the Islamic Republic
of Kamistan.
Earlier, we spoke to a UN official
who confirmed
that under the IRK's constitution,
Mrs. Hassan would have the authority
to sign this treaty.
I heard about your resignation.
I'm glad to see
you're putting your health first.
We all just want you to get well.
I'm leaving because of you.
Because of what you've started here.
You've deliberately played this out
to maneuver the President
into a corner.
I brought the Russians
back to the table.
But you didn't tell her
how you were doing it.
She didn't ask.
Because she knew it was best for her
to preserve her own deniability.
The President knows
exactly what she's doing.
She's smart.
She's smarter than either of us
ever gave her credit for.
I see.
- You just provided counsel.
- That's right.
Well, let me counsel you.
Stop this cover-up
before it's too late.
This peace is no good.
There's too much blood on this treaty
for it ever to hold.
We've both been in this game
a long time,
and we both know damn well
that every treaty ever written
had blood on it!
Not like this.
You got Allison
so far into the woods,
she'll never be able
to find her way out.
She wasn't like you.
Wasn't like any politician
I've ever known.
That's right.
She's finally got some teeth.
You listen to me.
If she suffers for this,
I will come after you
with everything I have.
- You're threatening me.
- I'm warning you, Charles.
Do you need to sit down?
I'm fine.
If you don't mind, Allison will be
taking the podium any second now.
Get some rest, Ethan.
You need it.
You told Bauer you have evidence.
I need to know where it is.
Come on.
You know the deal. The sooner
you tell me, the easier it'll go.
Please,
I have got nothing to tell you.
There is no evidence.
If that's the way
you want to play it, fine.
Ladies and gentlemen,
no questions will be taken
until after this morning's address.
I want to thank you
for your thoughts on my speech.
They were very helpful.
I'm glad.
My husband would have been grateful
for the support
that you have given me.
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the President of the United States.
My fellow Americans
and friends in foreign lands,
I speak to you this morning
with a heavy heart.
The brutal and cowardly murder
of President Omar Hassan
was a blow to every civilized person
in the world
and a stark reminder
that the pursuit of peace
sometimes comes with a steep price.
President Hassan understood that,
yet still had the fortitude
to pursue a better tomorrow
against so many odds.
I join with the American people
in mourning him
and every other innocent life
that was lost during this crisis.
But let it be known here and now
their sacrifice
will not have been in vain.
Peace must and will prevail
no matter the cost.
No matter the cost,
no matter the compromises.
We have waited too long
and worked too hard,
to allow this opportunity
to pass us by.
And that is why
in Omar Hassan's name,
I am choosing to move forward
with this historic summit.
One that was made possible
by the shared hopes and ideals
of the IRK leadership,
and will continue
under its new leader...
a woman of unparalleled courage
and grace,
who has been chosen by her people
to carry on the mantle
of her late husband...