Have you made the preparations?
Are you sure you want
to leave now, Colonel?
Can't imagine General
Juma will be pleased
to learn that you're
abandoning your mission.
The mission is over.
You think I'm a fool,
Mr. Burnett?
If anything should happen to me
on my way out of the country,
the data file with all the
names and bank transactions
of all those involved will be
sent to the Justice Department.
When the car arrives,
we would like you to go with the driver
so that we could follow
you back to Dubaku.
You want her to go
to him and face him?
It's the only chance we
have of finding him before
he disappears forever.
I'll do it.
You keep her safe, you hear me?
We will.
Colonel!
FBI.
Go! Go!
I want the names of everyone in
the United States government
that you've been working with.
I have a list.
I found some kind of digital storage
device implanted under Dubaku's skin.
Can you upload
the files to FBI?
Marika didn't make it.
You killed my sister.
I'm so sorry.
What do you want from me?! I just
want to know that you feel something.
I want to know that you feel
the same kind of pain that I do!
Do you feel that?!
I'm working with FBI to
coordinate an interagency sweep.
We should start making
arrests within the hour.
What you have done here today
puts all of us in your debt.
There are a lot of people to thank,
including Jack Bauer.
What are you asking
me to do, Bill?
I'm asking you to speak
to Senator Mayer.
Jack Bauer helped
save this country.
He doesn't deserve to spend
the rest of his life in prison.
I'm going to the
White House. Sir?
President Taylor wants to speak
to me regarding Jack Bauer.
Grab your laptop, Ryan.
I want you there with me.
There's gonna be
another attack.
Here in D.C.
My source tells me that the
window opens at 1900 hours.
What's the target?
He doesn't know
the exact target,
but it's definitely going to be
of high value and high impact.
He gave me the name of somebody who's
been involved in the planning. Who?
Ryan Burnett.
Senator Mayer's chief of staff.
That's right.
Hold on a second.
Go ahead.
Dr. Schonfeld, 305.
ICU.
One moment, please.
Corinna, you got
a call on three.
Who is it?
Dr. May. He's got a question.
Doctors are so helpless.
Dr. May?
Hello?
There was no one there.
If he calls back,
tell him I'll call him back in a minute.
Code Blue.
Code Blue!
We have a Code Blue in the ICU!
Get Agent Walker
down to ICU now!
Swift and decisive is how
the Pentagon describes
the U.S.
invasion now underway in Sangala.
"Sporadic resistance,
minimal casualties."
This in direct contrast
to assertions made
by Sangalese leader
Benjamin Juma
on state-supported
television.
Our brave soldiers are beating back
the enemy all across Sangala City.
History is on our side,
my friends.
We survived their slave ships,
and we will survive their warships, too.
Declaring victory while his own
troops are fleeing the capital,
and his palace lies in ruins.
When do we think this was made?
My guess is these recordings were made
some time before the invasion, ma'am.
Which begs the question, John.
Where is he,
and why haven't we found him yet?
Special Forces teams all over
Sangala City are searching for him.
There is some intelligence to
suggest he may have fled the country.
Admiral Smith, you and I both
know that Juma must be captured.
He must be tried and convicted
of his crimes against humanity.
Otherwise, we've
as good as failed.
He can't go far, ma'am.
No country on earth
will grant him asylum.
Then find him, Admiral Smith.
Wherever he is.
General Juma?
Beautiful, isn't it?
Sir?
It's not a trick
question, Laurent.
It is beautiful.
Why not?
It is almost time.
The men-- are they ready?
Yes, sir.
Are they afraid?
I don't know, sir,
but some of them are praying.
It's good if they are afraid.
It means they will
fight bravely.
Have you heard from
my father yet, sir?
I thought he was supposed
to be meeting us here.
Don't worry, Laurent.
He will be here.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
Colonel Dubaku is dead.
Are you certain?
The dose I administered
was catastrophic.
His son just asked
me about him.
He must never know about this,
or about his father's cowardice.
He won't.
Then nothing will stand in our way, Udo.
But hurry.
The attack window is narrowing.
The timing must be precise.
Clear! Yes, sir.
Clear.
One more time at 360.
Nothing.
Going again, Doctor?
No.
That's it, everybody.
I'm calling it.
Time of death: 6:06 p.m.
Dr. Stahl, what's going on?
A massive heart attack.
You said that he was stable,
that he was going to be okay.
So, what happened?
I'm not sure.
Maybe a preexisting condition.
The autopsy will tell us.
Excuse me.
The wide extent of the corruption
requires a coordinated approach.
We know the government's
been compromised.
We just don't know
at what level.
Presently, Chloe O'Brian is vetting
the names department by department.
I'm prioritizing
Secret Service,
so the president is secured
as soon as possible.
Team leaders will then receive their
assignments-- Defense, Treasury, State,
et cetera-- and make their arrests
contemporaneously across the District.
O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Have the names from Dubaku's database
been handed over to the arrest
teams yet?
Not yet. Okay, listen to me.
I've just learned that Juma's
operatives are planning another attack.
Jack, they're telling
us here it's over.
That's wrong.
Tony's my source on the intel.
Do you know what the target is?
Only that it's high value,
high casualty, and that
it's happening now,
which is why I need your help.
There's a man on the list,
a Ryan Burnett.
He's Senator Mayer's
chief of staff.
Mayer? Isn't he the guy who
grilled you this morning
at the Senate
Subcommittee hearing?
Yeah, but the senator's not
implicated in the conspiracy.
But Burnett has been providing
support for Juma and Dubaku all along.
Chloe, I need you to delete
his name from the list.
What? Why?
If the FBI start to move in on him,
he'll lawyer up,
and no one will get the
information on time.
Where is he now?
He's at the White
House with the senator.
They've got a meeting
with the president.
I'm on my way there now
to be debriefed by Bill.
I'll take care of him then.
Jack, you don't expect to interrogate
a suspect in the White House?
Let me handle that.
Chloe, just get his name
deleted from the list.
I'll get back to you.
She's in.
Hi.
How close are we? Close.
Is there anything
I can do to help?
I'm just cycling through
the last layer of data now.
You know, it might be quicker if you
send the subsets to my station one
by one.
Good idea.
And then that way I can get
to work on distributing them.
Okay, then.
Thank you.
Listen, Jack,
maybe you should reconsider.
Reconsider what?
Taking Bill into
your confidence.
Look, I mean, he's been a part of
this operation since the get-go.
I don't know what it's going to
take to get Burnett to talk.
If I have to use
extreme measures...
I don't get it.
What, you don't think he'll go there?
I'm driving off a
cliff here, Tony.
I don't need to put Bill
in the passenger seat.
All right, then, fine.
I'll go with you.
You're a wanted felon.
You wouldn't get past
the first checkpoint.
Besides, with all of
the government agencies
still compromised, it might be
up to you to stop the attack.
See you on the other side.
Yes?
Can you extend
the attack window?
Not without risking
the entire operation.
Why?
There's been a complication.
I may be stuck here longer
than I anticipated.
I'll call you back.
Mr. Kanin.
Ryan Burnett,
Senator Mayer's chief of staff.
We've spoken on the phone.
Many times.
It's good to finally meet you.
Likewise. The senator's inside.
Right this way.
Senator?
Well, Senator,
I see you've found the bar.
Mind if I join you?
Something I never knew.
If it ain't from Kentucky,
you can't call it bourbon.
Spare me the Southern
gentleman routine, Ethan.
The president didn't
call me up here
at the ass-end of the day to drink her
booze and flip through a briefing book.
I thought it might be helpful, before
your meeting, to bring you up to speed
on the events of
the last ten hours.
Okay.
I'm up to speed.
Senator, surely you have some
reaction to what you just read.
Damn right I have a reaction.
I want to know what all this
has to do with Jack Bauer.
I mean,
that's the reason I'm here, right?
Without Mr.
Bauer, we would never have uncovered
the conspiracy in the first
place nor the people behind it.
His efforts, in conjunction with those
of the FBI, are largely responsible
for the arrests being made
right now across the District.
You're not saying that he's
acting in an official capacity?
I don't have to tell you
how this looks, Ethan.
Colluding with a rogue operative
from a disbanded agency.
I'm sorry you see it that way.
How else am I
supposed to see it?
The way the president does--
that Jack Bauer saved lives today, plain
and simple, including her husband's.
Look, Senator,
I know this isn't easy for you.
The public battle you've waged
against detainee abuse and
human rights violations...
Are you seriously asking me to
look the other way on this?
I have been after this
son of a bitch for years.
He's a thug, Ethan.
He's exhibit "A."
The president is prepared
to reverse policy
and support your amendment
to the War Crimes Act.
In exchange for what exactly?
The hearings.
Declare a recess till
after the holidays
and then quietly let Mr.
Bauer's subpoena expire.
And if I refuse to go along?
The president is prepared to invoke
executive privilege.
Executive privilege--
meaning what exactly?
Well, that's for the
president to decide.
Are you talking about a pardon?
I wouldn't rule it out.
Well, if that's how the
president wants to play it,
you can tell her she just
walked into a street fight.
You can tell her yourself.
Jack.
Hi, Bill.
You got here sooner than I expected.
Jack. Put down your weapon now!
Step away from the desk!
Take a seat.
Sit down, Bill!
Okay, okay, I'm sitting.
Now, what's this all about?
Where is Ryan Burnett? What?
Senator Mayer's chief of staff--
where is he?
I'm not saying anything until you
tell me what the hell's going on.
Tony doubled back to
one of his contacts,
who gave him information
of a second attack.
It's going to take place here
in Washington within the hour.
Juma's operatives
are carrying it out.
Burnett's been supporting
them all along.
He knows where the attack's
going to take place, so you can
either tell me where he is
or I will find him myself.
Jack, I can't.
Fine, put your hands
behind your back now.
How good is the intel?
Good enough for me to
need to talk to him.
Don't you move.
Jack, let me have him arrested.
There are other ways
to deal with this.
The attack window's open.
We're out of time.
Jack, listen to me.
I spoke to the president
on your behalf.
She's going to intervene with
Senator Mayer, stop the hearings.
You can get your life back.
You do this,
you're throwing it all away.
I wish I thought there
was another option.
Let me help you at least, Jack.
Y-You don't have
to do this alone.
Yes, I do.
It's the only way I can make
sure to keep you out of this.
Jack. Bill, I'm sorry.
Jack, w-w-wait!
Jack!
It's all right.
Don't fight it.
This is Moss.
Larry, it's me.
Dubaku's dead.
I thought the doctors
said he was stabilized.
What happened?
Officially, they're characterizing
that it was a coronary
brought on by systemic shock.
Sounds like you
don't believe it.
I did a follow-up with
the hospital admin.
She confirmed that there was an
eight-member team on duty when
Dubaku flatlined.
Yeah?
There was a ninth man in the ICU just
before the code was called-- an orderly.
I ran back the tapes on the ward
and that's when I spotted him.
The thing is: I've asked around
and nobody seems to know who he is.
Renee, wait, a-are you saying
you think Dubaku was murdered?
I'm saying that there was an
unidentified man in with Dubaku
just before he went
into cardiac arrest.
What does the admin say?
She says that they often use floaters--
personnel from other area hospitals
filling in from time to time.
Said it's not uncommon for the regular
staff not to know who they are.
She's double-checking
with payroll now.
Right, so there's your answer.
Still it seems odd.
I mean, what if Dubaku knew something
and they needed to shut him up?
Is this Bauer's theory, too?
Jack's not even here and, you know,
I resent that implication, Larry.
That I'm not the one calling the shots.
What implication is that?
This has been my investigation from
the beginning, not Jack Bauer's.
I was just asking a question.
I wasn't implying anything.
You there? I'm sorry.
I guess I'm a little
sensitive on the subject.
Look, everything we needed from Dubaku,
we got.
Names and bank accounts of every
corrupt official on his payroll.
Teams are in the
field as we speak.
So you're saying you
want me to come in.
We need you back in the
office sooner than later
to help process
all these arrests.
Larry, look, I've got security searching
the hospital and reviewing more video.
So, what,
you want to follow that up first?
Fine, call me when
you clear it. Yeah.
I will.
Thanks, Larry.
Excuse me, Agent Walker?
That orderly you were looking for--
one of our parking lot cameras
picked him up getting
into his car. When?
Uh, about 15 minutes ago. I've got
a screen grab of his license plate.
Thank you.
This is Agent Walker.
Put me through to
our DMV contact.
Are you busy?
I'm just reformatting the server,
so, yeah, I guess I am busy. Why?
Well, I was cross-referencing
Dubaku's offshore accounts
and I came across an
orphaned header fragment.
What are you talking about?
Take a look.
Okay, see, there,
right there, right there.
It's a remnant file header.
It's probably just a
phantom data string.
No, it isn't.
I ran a systems analysis.
The coding is not random.
It can be traced back
to one of the accounts.
Also, it looks like a name
was deleted from the list.
Why don't I run a
recovery program?
Well, you're very busy with
the reformatting and all,
so why don't I just upload it to my
station and take care of it there?
Well, that's okay,
I can do it faster.
No offense.
I'll let you know if
I retrieve anything.
Sure.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Have you gotten to Burnett yet?
Working on it.
Making my way over
to the West Wing.
Someone here has figured out that a name
has been deleted from the database.
I don't know how much
longer I can hold her off.
Do they know it was Burnett?
No, but it's just
a matter of time.
Okay, I'll get back to you.
Great.
Senator, I'll head back to
the Hill and get with Sandy.
We should have a press release drafted
by the time you finish your meeting.
I'm also going to need a sit-down
with your friend Hauser at the Post.
Off the record, I assume.
We've got to make pardoning
Jack Bauer as politically toxic
for the president as possible.
She's a woman in a
highly emotional state.
Her husband's been shot.
You suggesting her
judgment's impaired?
I'm suggesting that
a case could be made.
Excuse me, Senator.
President Taylor is
ready to see you now.
Go ahead, Senator.
I'll get this to the AG,
tell him you want the option to go ahead
with the hearings
tomorrow as scheduled.
Thanks, Ryan.
Yes?
It's Burnett.
You took care of the problem?
I'm leaving now.
Good, then we rendezvous at 2130 hours,
as planned.
I'll be there.
Excuse me,
I'll be out of here in just one second.
You and I...
...we're going to have a talk.
We've got a command
post set up at EEOB,
and we'll brief CIA and
Diplomatic Security,
but not until after the
first sweep of arrests.
Look, nobody is
going anywhere, Phil.
We've dropped a
net on the city.
And I'll let you know as
soon as that happens.
All right.
Yeah. I'm sorry to interrupt,
but I need you to listen to something.
May I? Yeah, that's fine.
She's supposed to be this
whiz-bang systems analyst,
which is actually what tipped
me off in the first place.
Her demeanor is so bizarre...
W-W-Whoa, Janis, Janis, slow down.
Who are you talking about?
Chloe O'Brian.
I ran a systems check on her work,
and it turns out
there's evidence
of file tampering.
Plus she's been scrambling all
her out-of-office phone calls,
so I had Operations archive
her cellular traffic.
I did a work-around.
Listen.
Yeah.
Have you gotten to Burnett yet?
Working on it.
Making my way over
to the West Wing.
Someone here has figured out that a name
has been deleted from the database.
I don't know how much
longer I can hold her off.
Do they know it was Burnett?
No, but it's just
a matter of time.
Okay, I'll get back to you.
Becker.
In the conference room.
I want Chloe O'Brian detained.
And get her off that server.
Get me the White House.
Let me just remind you, Madam President,
you supported the effort
to ban abuse and torture.
You campaigned to reform
the intelligence agencies.
These past ten hours, Senator,
things haven't appeared as black
and white as they once did.
Well, there's nothing
gray about Jack Bauer.
The man has
committed atrocities.
Prisoners have died
in his custody.
Mr. Bauer has served under the aegis
of three presidents, not just me.
Is it any more lawful
or any less repugnant
if it's authorized at
the highest level?
A state of war is not a blank check
for the president or for anyone.
Oh, don't lecture me, Senator.
I am well aware of the
limits of my power.
Due respect, Madam President...
your power is great.
Just be careful that you use
it to send the right message.
All I'm asking you to do is excuse Mr.
Bauer as a witness.
It's not a message.
It is an expression of gratitude
for what he's done today.
You're asking me to excuse him as
a target of the investigation.
And the message is clear.
Under certain circumstances,
you believe his methods are acceptable.
Some would argue that they are.
And they would be wrong.
Under any military
or moral standard.
America has been down this road before,
Madam President.
You yourself called it
a national tragedy.
It was a tragedy.
I still believe that.
Pardon Jack Bauer, and you're telling
every interrogator in the field
that it's open season again.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
Madam President.
There's an urgent call
from Larry Moss at FBI.
Put him through.
Agent Moss is on the line.
Agent Moss,
this is Ethan Kanin.
You're on speaker
with the president.
Madam President, forgive me for
coming directly to the point.
You have a meeting this evening
with Senator Mayer? In fact, I do.
I'm with him right now.
Did the senator's chief of staff,
Ryan Burnett, accompany
the senator to the White House?
Yes, he did, Agent Moss-- why?
I have reason to
believe that Jack Bauer
is carrying out an off-book
interrogation of Mr. Burnett as
we speak.
I can pull the trigger 128 more
times before this battery dies.
I'm telling you,
I don't know anything about an attack.
Stop lying to me.
I'm not lying.
What's the target?
I can't tell you what I don't know.
Mr. Burnett,
you are a traitor
and a terrorist.
I'm not.
I love my country.
That was 1,200
volts of current.
Now, when I eject this cartridge,
I access the drive stun mode,
upping the voltage 40 times
when directly administered.
All you need to
do is talk to me.
Mr. Burnett,
it's really simple.
Just tell me what the target is,
and this will be all over. I promise.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
This is your last chance.
If I knew, I would tell you, I swear it.
What do you want me to say?
Just... Just tell me what to say,
and I'll say it.
Don't you even try and
play that game with me.
Mr. Burnett, I've been doing this a long
time, and I can tell the difference,
especially when a man is under duress,
if he's got information that I need
or if I'm just wasting my time.
And I promise you,
I am not wasting my time.
The next jolt is gonna
be in your throat.
Anything above your neck runs the risk
of a complete neuromuscular shutdown.
That means you run the risk
of becoming paralyzed.
No, please.
Mr. Burnett, you built the
entire federal case against me.
You of all people should know
how far I am willing to go
to stop this attack
from happening.
So, I'm gonna ask
you one last time.
Where is the target?!
I...
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm listening.
Soldiers.
How many?
A unit.
Juma's presidential guard.
When?
It already started.
Where?
Where?!
Mr. Bauer,
this is President Taylor.
Where is the target?
Mr. Bauer... Where?!
Mr. Bauer,
I am ordering you to answer this page.
Mr. Bauer, do you hear me?
Damn it!
Madam President,
this is Jack Bauer.
I don't know what you've heard so far,
but this thing is not over.
There is another terrorist attack
going to take place within minutes.
There will be no discussion
until you unlock this door.
Madam President,
the attack window is open.
Juma's men are moving.
What you're doing is against the law,
Mr. Bauer.
I am your commander in chief,
and I am ordering you to stand down.
How much longer, Sergeant?
Good to go, ma'am. Do it.
Where's the target?
Where is the target?!
Where is...?!
I had him!
Man down.
EMTs to the visiting
dignitary suite.
You're done, Bauer.
You're finished.
He was talking.
Whatever's going to happen is happening
now, and it's on your conscience.
My conscience has a lot less
to answer for than yours.
Mr. Bauer,
you say an attack is imminent.
My source intel is good.
Who is your source?
I'd rather not say.
The name, Mr. Bauer.
Tony Almeida.
Tony Almeida--
the man's a fugitive.
Without Tony Almeida, we would
never have recovered the CIP device.
Madam President,
I don't care if his source
is the blessed Virgin Mary.
Nothing justifies what
went on in this room.
Even if he's right, Blaine?
Even if it means we
could save lives?
Look at that,
and tell me it's not barbarism.
Is that something
you can live with?
Earlier today, Madam President,
two airplanes were brought down.
Is that something
you can live with?
You're reprehensible, Bauer.
And you, sir, are weak!
Unwilling and unable to look evil
in the eye and deal with it.
Ethan, step out for a second.
Suddenly, it's not so hypothetical,
is it?
In your opinion,
is Bauer's intelligence actionable?
If Bauer says there's
going to be an attack,
my belief is,
there's going to be an attack.
Torture was originally intended
to force false confessions.
Now we use it to try
and find the truth.
These people murdered your son,
Madam President.
They attempted to
murder your husband.
They will stop at nothing.
Sergeant, take Mr. Bauer away.
He's under arrest.
You should have come to me.
You should have
presented your case.
We didn't have time.
And would it really have
made a difference, ma'am?
Madam President...
you're doing the right thing.
271 dead already.
I wish to God it felt more
like the right thing.
Ethan, raise the threat levels.
Tell Homeland they have until 7:00
to come up with a response scenario.
And get Tim down here.
Also, I want to talk to Mr.
Burnett myself.
Let me do that.
I know the man.
Apparently, you don't.
Got it.
Tim, I understand the threat
level has been raised, but only
for first responders
and federal agents.
There's a concern that mass evacuation
by the public could hamper efforts
to thwart an attack
when it comes.
What about the airspace
over Washington?
Restricted.
Military flyovers
are commencing.
DOD has recommended that we deploy
mobile teams to sweep the area
for radioactive and
biological signatures.
I'll call Phillip at the
Pentagon and push it through.
What about NSA?
There's elevated
anti-American chatter
coming from the usual Web
sites and telephone traffic,
but nothing specific
to the attack.
Thank you, Tim.
I'll see you upstairs in 15 minutes.
Yes, ma'am.
Which means our best source of
intelligence is still right here under
our noses.
You realize we're gonna have to
offer this bastard a free pass.
With coercive measures off the table,
it's our only option.
Bauer's going to prison,
and a traitor walks.
What's wrong with this picture?
I need a minute
with the prisoner.
Mr. Burnett, you will be charged
with treason under Title 18,
Section 2381,
of the United States Code.
Giving aid and
comfort to the enemy
and directly causing the
death of American citizens.
Do you understand?
Surely, you have something
to say for yourself.
I demand my right to counsel.
You'll have your counsel,
Mr. Burnett,
but first, you're going to
tell me everything you know.
Not in this lifetime.
What did you say?
I said, not in this lifetime.
Don't be so quick to make up your mind,
Mr. Burnett.
In exchange for information which stops
or significantly mitigates this attack,
the president is prepared to grant
you full immunity from prosecution.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
If you and your family are
being threatened in any way...
Do you realize what the
president is offering you?
Treason is a capital offense,
Mr. Burnett.
If you don't cooperate with us right
now, I will make it my personal mission
to see that you pay the
ultimate price for your crimes.
I won't condone torture,
but in your case,
I would have no problem
with the death penalty.
Where's my lawyer?
??
Walker. MOSS: It's me.
That situation at the
hospital you told me about?
Yeah, I'm on it, Larry.
I traced a license plate
to an import/export firm.
Tell me.
The orderly I mentioned-- he just
joined up with about a dozen soldiers.
Africans. Heavily armed.
Where are you?
44543 Lambourne Marina,
near Johnson Park.
I'm in the warehouse basement.
Renee, we have intel on another
attack by Juma's people.
It's happening in D.C.,
sometime after 1900 hours.
This is it, Larry. No question.
All right, listen, sit tight.
I'm on my way with back.
Make it quick.
Janis, scramble a chopper.
On the roof in two minutes.
Okay. But also...
Janis, just do it.
This is Larry Moss.
Put me through to Metro Police.
Charters, Turner-- with me.
General, there is no
sign of my father.
I just spoke with him.
Unfortunately he won't
be able to join us.
Why not?
Because he got delayed in his
attempt to secure safe passage for us
from the country.
Then, sir, let me take his
place on the assault team.
Spoken like a true
Dubaku, Laurent.
But you are also my only reconnaissance
officer. But, General...
No, I need you on the perimeter
to provide intelligence
and also to disrupt whatever
rescue operations there may be.
Understood?
Understood, sir.
Make your final preparations.
It is time for us to go.
Yes, sir.
Yeah?
Larry, hurry,
they're moving out.
We're ten minutes away.
Is it possible that Juma
himself is leading this attack?
Juma? Why do you say that?
I know it sounds crazy,
but I swear that I just saw him.
What?! Here?!
Are you sure?
Unless he has an identical twin.
All right, I'll alert Homeland.
Good work.
Any idea what the
next target is?
Negative.
See if you get a fix on that.
But, listen, don't take any chances.
All right?
I won't.
Sir.
You should have an EMT take
a look at you. I'm fine.
Is Bauer in custody? Yes, sir.
He's in holding.
That'll be all.
Tony, it's Bill.
Bill. Jack's under arrest.
They've got him locked down
in a holding cell here.
Listen to me, Bill...
No, you listen.
We still don't know where
this attack's taking place.
Burnett didn't break?
No. They stopped Jack before
he could get the information.
And Burnett didn't go for the
president's immunity deal.
You were the one who brought
Jack the intel, right?
That's right.
How real is it?
Very.
Who was your contact?
It was a guy in Emerson's crew
with a direct line to Juma.
Any chance we get another
crack at this guy?
That's highly unlikely,
to say the least.
What are you telling me,
he's dead?
That's right?
I wish to God you'd
brought me in on this.
Jack didn't want to put
you in that position.
For what it's worth,
he was trying to protect you, Bill.
Did you have a fallback plan,
at least?
Immunity for Burnett
was the fallback.
That's it? Nothing else?
No.
Nothing.
I keep trying Renee,
and I keep getting her voice mail.
What the hell's going on?
There's something
wrong with her phone.
What do you mean,
something's wrong?
I just spoke to her
five minutes ago.
Can you triangulate
her position?
I can't. Why not?
There's no signal.
Either the battery's dead,
or her cell got damaged somehow.
All right, keep trying.
Get back to me when you
know something. Okay.
From our location it is approximately
100 meters to the entrance.
From this point forward,
we maintain radio silence
until the target is secure.
Understood?
Yes, sir. Understood.
You all have your assignments.
May God be with us.
Laurent, take your position.
Yes, sir.