Subtitles:
Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu (V 1.00)
Our security police have completed
their initial sweep of the capital city.
65 known members of the opposition
have been arrested and are interrogated.
Have you learned anything?
Were anyone working with my brother?
It's too early.
Your father is a great man,
but Farhad's betrayal
has changed him.
What can we do?
The president says
you may be involved.
He's ordered me to detain you.
I'll talk to him.
President Hassan's crackdown
isn't just a response
to the attempt on his life.
There are
unsecured nuclear materials in play.
CTU is running an undercover operation
to retrieve them as we speak.
I've got something.
It's an NYPD evidence lockup.
A local vice group
just impounded $120,000.
I help you do this
and you never call me again.
That's beautiful, man.
Absolutely beautiful.
It's a cop.
You're going
to have to slip past him.
- I'm at the warehouse...
- Nick!
Stop him!
I hear there are materials for sale.
Talk straight. What materials?
Nuclear rods.
Nobody deals in nuclear rods,
nobody.
We've a problem.
Vladimir Laitanan knows about
the fuel rods.
Come on, Vladimir, push them harder.
Somebody knows something.
No one knows, there's no one left.
It's over! What is wrong with you?!
Stop, stop.
- They're Russians.
- What are you doing?
I let them take me.
Tell CTU
to start tracking me from the air.
They'll lead us
to what we're looking for.
I'm unarmed, don't shoot.
We can do business.
Where's Jack?
The Russians took him. He said
you'd be monitoring him from the air.
We haven't seen anything.
Where is he?
Where are you?
Jenny girl!
You would call me
when you got clear.
I'm sorry, sweetheart, I forgot.
We got caught up
celebrating our score.
Celebrating?
You put a police officer
in the hospital.
That wasn't me, that was Nick.
Why do you got
to focus on the negative?
We're flush 120 grand.
Why don't you come down here,
have a drink, celebrate with us?
We're at a club
in Jersey City called Starlight.
We'll work out your cut.
What cut?
I don't want anything from you.
We're done.
I want you to put my key
in my mailbox
and get out of my life
like promised.
That's not going to happen.
What?
This is a sweet operation
that we got going here.
You getting the access codes
- and us pulling the jobs.
- Wait.
We had a deal.
You promised me I do this for you
and then you leave me alone.
I know and I meant that.
but things change, okay...
We can get rich off of this.
You can't do this to me.
Jenny, please...
Look, bitch,
you're in this up to your neck.
Want your boss
and your boyfriend finding out
you're not who you say you are?
You're gonna be
our golden goose, okay?
What are you doing?
We got a situation.
You need to be on the floor.
I heard you, I will be right there.
Who was that on the phone?
None of your business.
Actually, it is.
When you sneak away to make phone calls,
making me cover for you,
it becomes my business.
Who was that?
- Kevin?
- How the hell would you...
Are you spying on me?
You want to step out on your fiancé,
it's fine with me.
- I've got no love for the guy.
- You don't understand.
- I am not cheating on Cole.
- Whatever you want to call it,
tell to your boyfriend
what's going on,
or I will.
Our undercover operation
just went south.
What's happened?
Jack Bauer was grabbed
by an unknown group of armed Russians.
We think they're the ones
in control of the nuclear rods.
- Are we tracking them?
- We can't.
They're took Bauer through
an underground access.
Without aerial support,
the best we could do
was track them to a drainage junction
near Avenue Y and Ocean.
They must have had a vehicle.
Jack's cell phone was trashed.
There has to be something
to help us ID the vehicle.
Tire treads,
transmission fluid, oil residue?
There's nothing,
- the trail's gone cold.
- What about Walker?
Did she saw these people?
I don't know.
Frankly,
she's pretty messed up right now.
- Blaming herself for Jack.
- She should.
She crippled this operation
when she murdered her contact.
Without Vladimir Laitanan,
we have no lead
to finding Bauer
or the nuclear materials.
Get her back to CTU for debriefing.
I want to know what happened.
You might want to consider
running a psych eval on her.
Count on it.
You were supposed to be
coordinating with NSA,
monitoring chatter.
- I had to take care of something.
- What was so important?
It's my fault.
I asked her to recover a datalog
I deleted from archives.
I didn't have clearance.
I'm uplinking to NSA servers now.
All right.
Get on it.
Roll back any chatter
within the last 20 minutes.
Right now that's all we've got.
Let me know if something turns up.
I need to brief President Taylor.
Thank you.
Thank me by putting aside
whatever it's that's bothering you
and helping me find Jack.
He's my friend
and he's in trouble.
Take him down the hall.
- Where is Vladimir?
- Dead.
So are his men.
The German said
they tried to rip him off.
Did he also say how he knows
about the fuel rods?
Who are you?
Ernst Meier.
I've been looking for you
to make you an offer.
- You know who I am?
- No.
All I know is that there's a man
in the Russian syndicate
who's been trafficking
weapons-grade uranium,
specifically U-235 fuel rods.
After the business with Laitanan,
these men brought me here,
so I'm just assuming
you're that man.
Where did you get this information?
I represent a consortium
of priva interests.
They intercepted communiqués
within the Islamic republic.
From whom?
Farhad Hassan,
or someone in his camp.
You're doing business
with the wrong people.
Who are these people,
the ones you work for?
I'm sure you can understand
I'm not at liberty to say.
You should be more concerned
about the deal that they offering you.
I'm not interested in your offer.
250 million dollars,
half of which
is ready to be wired to you.
The other half you'll receive
upon final acquisition of the rods.
You pose a problem for me.
You show up out of nowhere,
knowing far too much of my business,
yet I've never heard of you.
You've never heard of me
because I'm good at what I do.
What I'm concerned about...
is that you're a cop.
I killed 3 people
back at that garage.
Laitanan, I stabbed in the eye.
You really think I'm a cop?
As a child, I saw KGB
throw an entire family
off the roof of a building,
two of them small children.
I know what cops are capable of.
So I ask you again.
Who do you work for?
I'm sorry, I can't ll you that.
Dimitri, work on him
until he's ready to talk.
No, we can make a deal.
We can still make a deal!
You've buried your brother's body?
It's Oleg's necklace.
You gave it to him
at his confirmation.
Keep it.
To remind you of him.
I'm glad you're back.
We may have a problem.
What is it?
There is a man down the hall
who claims to be an arms broker.
He knows about the nuclear rods.
- How could he?
- He says there was a leak
from Farhad's people,
but I wonder.
Until I know for certain
who and what this man is,
I've stopped the transport of the rods,
redirected to our weigh station
off the Wantagh Parkway.
I'm sure
Farhad can't be happy about that.
I haven't told him yet.
Perhaps we should tell him together.
- How long do you hold him off?
- That depends.
On what?
On how long it takes Dimitri
to break this guy.
Okay, Mr. Policeman.
I'm not a cop.
I swear to you.
Please, don't do this.
Tell me what you know.
We are exhausting
all efforts to ascertain
who took Bauer and where.
Until any progress is made,
we just have to hope
that Jack can find some way
of salvaging the operation on his end.
What makes you think
he's still alive?
Only the fact that he wasn't killed
at the point of abduction.
I need a realistic assessment.
What are the odds
of finding and securing
these nuclear weapons
within the next hours?
I can't answer.
The longer we're out of touch
with Bauer, the less likely our chances.
All right, Mr. Hastings.
Continue to coordinate with my office.
I want updates
- every 30 minutes.
- Yes, ma'am.
I just spoke to General Wasim.
He's worried.
Your brother's crackdowns
back home are intensifying.
Everyone is being arrested.
Our window of opportunity is closing.
- Why didn't the general call me?
- Perhaps he's losing confidence
in your ability.
This is my mission.
My plan!
Of course.
But we're running out of time.
If your brother dismantles
the opposition,
we'll no longer be able
to reconstitute our nuclear program.
- He won't succeed.
- At this rate, he will.
How much longer must we wait
for the delivery of the uranium?
Not long.
The rods should be arriving
within the hour.
Have your men ready.
I'll call you back.
Yes? What is it?
There is a man downstairs who's shown up
to outbid you for the fuel rods.
Is this some feeble attempt
to renegotiate terms?
Not at all.
This man, Meier,
claims someone in your organization
tipped him off to our deal.
That's not possible. He's lying.
At any rate,
in light of his appearance,
I'm halting delivery
for the time being.
- What? You can't do that.
- It's already done.
I can't take the risk
that we may be exposed.
The longer you delay, the more time
my brother has to crush his enemies.
If he manages to purge
everyone in the military
who opposes him,
the uranium is worthless to me.
That's your concern.
Mine is to make certain this Meier
is not a policeman.
One of my men
is interrogating him now.
That could take hours, even days.
Not days.
I can promise you that.
You promised
to assassinate my brother, too.
Your failure to eliminate him has put me
under enormous pressure, and now,
because of your people's inability
to maintain secrecy,
you break our agreed timetable
to suit your needs.
Don't speak to my father that way.
We've honored
every agreement we made
with you,
and shed a lot of blood for it.
My father's allowed you to stay here
and hide from the Feds
at great personal risk to our family.
Tell him to put the gun down.
We're not taking
any more of your demands.
Throw him out of here.
Let his own people shelter him
if he thinks we're such fools.
I'll drive him there myself
if that's what it takes.
It would seem
you have used up our hospitality.
Perhaps it's best you join your men
at the rendezvous point
to wait for delivery.
And when will that be?
When I think it's safe.
Not a moment before.
Make sure he gets where he's going.
Still got men at the scene.
In the meantime, I'll work out
the aerial sweep protocols with Arlo.
What are you doing to find Jack?
Everything we can, Ms. Walker.
Come with me.
Have you checked all the...
the traffic cams, subway routes?
You have all this technology...
comm surveillance, satellite tracking.
We're using everything
at our disposal.
Then how come you haven't found him yet?
Why don't you have any leads?
The best lead we had is dead.
I know about your suicide attempt.
You should have been honest with me.
Now O'Brian
will take your statement.
I want to know every detail
about every event
leading up to the death
of Vladimir Laitanan.
When she's done,
take her to medical.
I've ordered
a full psych evaluation.
You can write your statement here.
Hastings blames me
for what happened to Jack.
And he's right.
No, he's not.
He shouldn't have said that.
The only reason that Jack was part
of this operation was because of me.
So whatever they're doing to him
right now, it's because of me.
I have to find him.
Renee, I know how you must feel.
Just...
Just take one thing at a time.
We have to deal with what you did.
So write your statement.
Ill check back with you.
Do you have some time?
I need to talk to you.
Can it wait?
I need to review these protocols
before Arlo distributes them.
I've got it covered.
Go talk to your girlfriend.
What's up?
You all right?
No, I'm not.
I have a big problem.
And it's the reason
why I've been acting kind of weird
the past few days.
If you're calling off the engagement,
you couldn't have picked a worse day.
No, I would never do that.
Good.
So what's bothering you?
There are things about my past
that I haven't told you.
I'm listening.
I'm sure I haven't told you
everything about my past either.
I don't care what happened
before I met you.
All that matters is now
and what we have to look forward to.
I think that's all
that matters, too.
So what are you so worried about?
I don't want to lose you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Excuse me.
Mr. Hastings needs to see you.
- I'll be there as soon as I can.
- No. Go.
- Hastings can wait.
- So can this.
Talking to you has helped.
I think I know
what I need to do now.
You sure?
Maybe later you tell me
what this is all about.
Who do you work for?
Who else knows about the fuel rods?
Everybody has a limit.
Don't worry,
I'll find yours.
You're working with the police.
Admit it!
Tell me and the pain will stop.
Who else knows?
I told you...
I'm not a cop.
Please.
I'm just a businessman.
Who do you work for?
I'm an independent contractor.
I couldn't even tell you
if I wanted.
Please.
We'll see.
Wake up.
I said, wake up.
I told you
I didn't want to be disturbed.
Your daughter is still demanding
to see you, Mr. President.
She refuses to leave.
Very well. Send her in.
Kayla, my love,
I'm in a crisis,
so unless it's an emergency...
It is an emergency.
We need to talk about
you having Tarin arrested.
Tarin has been taken to the embassy
to help clarify a few questions,
strictly routine.
I know you believe
he's been working against you.
What I don't understand is why.
He refused to follow my orders.
You asked him to arrest
the family of one of your delegates.
A man you considered a friend.
Kayla, this is a matter of state,
it doesn't concern you.
It doesn't make sense.
Tarin was in the car with you...
if the assassination attempt successed,
he would've been killed, too.
The world is full of men
willing to die for their cause.
I know you consider Tarin a friend.
And your loyalty is commendable.
But trust me, I've my reasons.
We are more than friends.
We're in love,
and have been for almost a year.
You've been carrying on
with this man...
behind my back?
You say that, after driving mother away
with your infidelity.
Please, Father.
Don't let Farhad's betrayal turn you
against everyone who cares about you.
I can't think of a better way...
to completely infiltrate my life
and influence my judgment...
than getting close to my daughter.
It's not like that.
You're not to see that man again,
ever.
- Father...
- I'm done with this conversation.
I need to get back to my work.
What's happening to you?
Come on.
Damn it!
I am holding the rods until Meier comes
clean about how he knew of the transfer.
If what Meier said is true
about the leak in Farhad's team,
it will be dangerous for us.
So we must unload the rods,
finish this.
Let them be someone else's problem,
and we erase any evidence.
Once Dimitri is finished, I'm satisfied
the German is telling the truth,
I'm going to want
to hand off the rods to Farhad tonight.
Keep your men out of sight
along the perimeter.
Mikhail and his men
will stay with the cargo.
Check to see
if the rest of the street lost power.
Just us.
It's Meier.
Cover the exits.
Check the fuse box.
- CTU. O'Brian.
- Chloe. It's Jack.
Everyone's been looking for you.
Where are you?
I need you to trace this call
and send a Tac team immediately.
Trace the call.
We're sure NYPD's got
the perimeter locked down?
Everything in a block radius
is secure.
Our response team
will be there soon.
Where's Dana?
She logged out of the building
about 15 minutes ago.
Something about fixing a faulty relay
at our 17th Street station.
Why didn't she have
maintenance take care?
Good question.
She had to manually reboot
the firmware herself.
That's what she said anyway.
- Where are we with this man Bazhaev?
- It's coming through right now.
I've cross-accessed
interagency servers,
also Interpol and FSB.
I'm relaying intel as it comes in
to our response team and to Jack.
Good. Put it up on screen.
Okay, people.
We've ID'd the suspect
we have in custody.
His name is
Sergei Petrovich Bazhaev,
Ukrainian national, 61 years of age.
Now, we believe he knows the location
of the unsecured nuclear rods.
Now, tactical is on its way
to transport him here for interrogation.
Agent Ortiz will coordinate operations
from here.
Is it true?
You found Jack?
He's okay.
If you're finished with your statement,
I need to take you to medical.
I want to be here
when Jack gets back.
I'll let him know where to find you.
Come on.
This should hold you for now.
But you have to go to the hospital.
Excuse me, sir.
They uploaded the suspect's file.
- How far out is CTU?
- They're about five minutes out.
It's all right.
I got it. Thanks.
Sergeant?
I need to speak with this man alone.
I knew you were a cop.
I should have trusted my instincts
and killed you on the spot.
You can add it
to your list of regrets.
CTU's already acquired
a great deal of intel on you...
Mr. Bazhaev.
It's over. You know that, right?
You're finished.
At the very least,
we've got you on kidnapping and murder,
before CTU rips this place apart
and uncovers your criminal activity.
Lucky for you, though,
I'm only interested in one thing,
the acquisition of those fuel rods.
So,
if you were to cooperate,
help me out there,
that would go a long way
to reducing a very long prison sentence.
That offer extends
to both of your sons, too...
Josef...
and Oleg.
Oleg is dead.
He was exposed to the rods.
Became ill with radiation poisoning.
He was suffering,
and I shot him,
as if he was just a sick dog.
I murdered my own son.
For nothing.
You want to know where the rods are?
I will tell you.
But I want full immunity.
Not just for me,
but for my other son, Josef.
I don't think I can make that.
Then we have nothing to talk about.
I'll see what I can do.
CTU. O'Brian.
It's Jack.
I need to speak with Hastings.
I think he's in a briefing
with President Taylor.
Even better.
See if you can patch me in, okay?
Mr. Hastings,
it's Farhad Hassan I'm worried about.
How do we know
he hasn't the rods already?
Based on the intel we have,
the transfer hasn't taken place yet.
Excuse the interruption.
Jack Bauer is on the line.
- He wishes to be conferenced in.
- Put him through.
It's President Taylor.
You're on with Mr. Hastings
and my chief of staff.
CTU's been keeping me apprised
of your involvement in this.
I'm sorry that it's taken
this long for us to speak.
Please forgive me
for getting straight to the point,
but the man we have in custody,
Sergei Bazhaev, is willing to cooperate.
He said he would hand over the fuel rods
in exchange for full immunity.
Is that all?
Why don't he give him a parade, too?
You've been dealing with him.
Is there another way to get the location
of the nuclear materials out of him?
It says in his files that he did
12 years in a labor camp.
In the time frame that we have,
we're not gonna break him.
- I can see it in his eyes.
- Mr. Hastings, what is your assessment?
Well, at first blush, I'd say
an immunity deal is premature, but...
under the circumstances,
I'll defer to Jack's judgment on this.
Gentlemen, I have a peace deal
that's going to fall apart
at any moment
unless I can show President Hassan
we've stopped his brother from smuggling
those fuel rods out of the country.
Make the deal, Jack.
- He's going to want this in writing.
- He'll get it.
But in the interests of expediency,
put him on the phone with me.
The President wants to talk to you.
Tell me what's going on.
- What are you talking about?
- You're implying something about Dana,
I want to know.
When she came over before
and said she had to talk to you,
- what did she tell you?
- Nothing.
- She had a problem and she'd handle it.
- That's it?
Arlo, if you know something...
it's none of my business,
and I didn't want to tell you this,
but I think
she went to meet some guy.
You're out of your mind.
Take a look at this.
- Who is he?
- I checked with the gate.
They said his name is Kevin Wade.
Identified himself as a friend.
So he's a friend.
Bazhaev's given up
the location of the nuclear rods.
I've already scrambled a NEST team.
Meet your tactical unit at the helipad.
The coordinates will be relayed
to you en route.
You think you can find her?
I could
if all the drones weren't committed.
What about a cell trace?
Just do it.
I don't know where you are
or what you're doing, Dana,
but I need you to call me
as soon as you get this. It's important.
I love you.
Thank you, sir.
Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Miss Kayla, no.
Get out of my way, Nabeel,
I want to see him.
Your father forbids it.
I'm doing my job.
A job that Tarin gave you.
He brought you
into my father's security detail,
and this is how you repay him?
You're his friend, Nabeel.
You know he's innocent.
- What would you have me do?
- Just let me speak to him.
A few minutes is all I ask.
I can't let you in now.
Tarin's going to be readied
for transport to our embassy in an hour.
I will find a moment
you can see him before then.
Thank you, Nabeel.
Now go before we're both in trouble.
The NEST team's ETA
is two minutes from target site.
Now the HAZMAT crew will wait
for your signal to move in.
Be advised,
the truck with the fuel rods
is being guarded
by two armed hostiles.
We've a deal with their boss.
Why haven't they standed down?
Jack's understanding is that
these men are hard cases.
They won't roll over easily.
We cannot take the risk...
they'll flee with the rods.
- Understood.
- When you secure the nuclear materials,
you'll transport them
to Fort Hamilton.
We're clearing that air corridor
as we speak.
Command, we see the truck,
but there's no sign of hostiles.
Approaching the weigh station now.
Stand by.
Set us down there.
Picking up trace radiation.
30 millirads. It's safe.
We're clear.
Command, are you seeing this?
I am.
Where the hell are the rods?
We picked up
trace radiation signatures.
The rods were here.
Right now all we have are two bodies,
both shot.
You can have a good time.
It's okay to laugh once in a while.
You can be a happy person.
- This is Bauer.
- It's Hastings.
Our team's at the truck stop.
The nuclear rods are not there.
What?
Hold on. Say that again.
I said the rods are not there.
It's not possible.
Did your men go to the right place?
They went exactly where you sent them.
Now stop and tell us where the rods are.
I told you, they were there.
- I had two of my men guarding them.
- We found their bodies, both shot.
Something else.
Some kind of necklace hanging
on the inside of the truck's door.
Like someone wanted
to send a message.
- What kind?
- A gold cross.
What does that mean?
Josef.
I have the fuel rods.
Really?
I wasn't sure I believed
that you would betray your father.
You were upset
that he was holding up delivery,
now I've gotten them for you.
It won't take him long to realize,
so let's get this done fast.
You're worried he'll discover
you've replaced him.
I want my father to know.
- In fact, I made sure he will.
- When will you get here?
Less than five minutes.
Just have my money ready.