As we gather together
for this great occasion,
we must not forget
that we all stand in the shadow
of Omar Hassan's tragic death.
But...
the peace agreement
we're about to sign
will be his living memorial.
His courage brought us all
to this historic day,
and his vision
will continue to guide us
as we move into the future...
together.
So on behalf
of the people of Russia,
I extend the open hand of friendship
to my partners in peace:
President Taylor,
President Hassan.
Thank you.
There'll be time for questions
after the signing ceremony. Please.
If there's nothing more,
I will see you both at the signing.
It appears I am not the only one
who does not want to be here.
Mrs. Hassan is distraught.
Understandably...
Her husband was killed six hours ago.
Is that why she refuses
to look at me?
She knows.
A reporter told her
of your complicity
in her husband's murder.
Dalia came to me.
And you confirmed
this journalist's allegations.
I told her the truth.
And yet, knowing what she knows,
she's still here.
Mrs. Hassan understands
the benefits of peace.
Because you helped her
come to that understanding.
Excuse me, Madam President.
Whatever it was you said
to Mrs. Hassan to keep her here
must have been very convincing.
Take your call, Yuri.
We need to talk.
So talk.
It's a sensitive matter,
something that...
- that can't be discussed on the phone.
- All right.
- Come to my suite.
- No. You need to come to mine.
Why?
Just trust me, Yuri.
Trust you?
I don't need to remind you
that it is in our mutual self-interest
to make sure that certain
secrets stay secret.
Stop talking in riddles, Charles.
I don't have time for this.
There's a possible leak
inside of your camp,
which is why we need
to discuss this in my office.
I'll be right there.
I hope
I was convincing enough for you.
You're a world-class liar;
I would have expected nothing else.
What exactly do you think you're doing
by killing Suvarov?
Getting justice for Renee Walker?
Yes, and for the people that died today
trying to protect this country.
Now, sit at the desk
and keep the line open.
The audio file you recorded...
We can use it to expose Suvarov.
We can use the CTU servers
to distribute it to every agency
and media outlet.
Taylor's already censored the press.
NSA's putting up firewalls.
Arlo's working on getting through them.
The President can't lock down
every media outlet.
That's Cole.
If I don't answer that,
he's sending a TAC team in here.
It'll be too late.
I'm gonna finish what I've started.
You've reached
Chloe O'Brian's voicemail. Please...
- Delta groups, this is base. Come in.
- This is Delta One. Go ahead.
I need you to deploy all TAC units
to the 22nd floor of the Hart Building.
- I have intel on a possible sniper.
- You got I.D. on this hostile?
Affirmative.
It's Jack Bauer.
With regard to Bauer, sir,
the standing order
is to use lethal force.
- The order stands.
- Copy that. We're on our way.
Delta teams two and three,
this is a priority mobilization.
The suspect is Jack Bauer.
Considered armed and dangerous.
Maintain shoot-on-sight protocol.
Listen to me, Jack. Please.
Put down your rifle,
and let me walk you out of here
before they get here.
Killing Pavel and Novakovich
was one thing, but killing Suvarov?
The Russians will consider
an assassination of their president
on American soil an act of war.
He facilitated a terrorist attack
against this country.
That's an act of war.
He's a murderer.
You're provoking a war
with a nuclear-armed country.
- Shut up, Chloe!
- Or what? You're gonna kill me, too?
They need to be held accountable.
They brought this on themselves.
I don't need to remind you
of the collateral damage.
Not to mention the innocent lives
that are at stake.
Sir, President Suvarov is outside.
He says you're expecting him.
Excuse me, sir?
I heard you.
Send him in.
You're gonna start a war
because you lost someone?
This isn't about me.
Renee wouldn't want you to do this.
- I said shut up, Chloe!
- You know she wouldn't.
She would want you
to use that data card to get justice.
The last thing Renee would want
is for you to start a war in her name.
Don't dishonor her memory like this.
- We should speak alone.
- Yes, of course.
This person, the one you say
is leaking information...
who is it?
I'm talking to you.
Okay, we'll do it your way.
Promise me you'll see this through.
I'm not getting out
of this building alive.
You got to promise me
that you will see this through
and that you will do
exactly what I say.
I need to hear it!
I promise.
I'm...
I'm sorry...
for calling you so urgently.
I was, mistaken.
My concern appeared
to have been unfounded.
I got a call from my source
just a moment ago.
His information was wrong.
I'm so sorry
for wasting your time, Yuri.
See you after the signing.
Find Pillar.
Sweeping equipment 22nd floor!
The TAC team's almost here.
I need to make it to mobile command.
You won't even get that far,
and make it out of here.
You found me first
by circumventing CTU.
If Logan hasn't figured that out yet,
he will soon enough.
CTU gave you a standing order
with regards to me,
to terminate with extreme prejudice.
If you don't shoot me,
that file's not going anywhere.
Take your weapon. Take it!
And point it at me.
Point it!
When they come,
tell them I've got the rifle,
I turned on you,
- and you opened fire.
- I can't do that.
Dammit, Chloe, pull the trigger!
We are running out of time.
They are gonna find us soon.
You said
that you would follow this through.
- Pull the trigger!
- I can't!
Yes and you will!
Now, pull the trigger!
Damn you, pull the trigger!
We are running out of time!
Please don't make me do this.
If you care about me at all,
you will pull the trigger.
- Do it!
- I can't.
- Pull the trigger!
- I'm not gonna do it!
Damn you!
What happened?
I shot him first.
Jack Bauer's down with a wound
to the upper chest.
I repeat, Bauer is down.
Burke's reporting
- you shot Jack.
- I had to.
- I'm on my way there right now.
- I need you at mobile command.
What's happened?
Jack gave me the recording
of Logan and Suvarov's conversation.
So, why did you shoot him?
I'll explain later.
Make sure
that Arlo is ready to upload that file.
- What's Jack's status?
- EMT are working on him right now.
- Is he going to make it?
- I don't know.
I'll explain to you when I get there.
I'll see you soon.
NYPD found Mr. Pillar in the garage.
In the back of his SUV.
- He wants me to hold you here.
- Why?
He's been apprised of the situation,
and he wants to debrief you.
We can do it later.
I'm still running security.
- Ms. O'Brian, he was adamant.
- I've got to get back to the mobile.
His authority,
comes from the President.
If you want to call
to the White House, we can do that.
- When will he be here?
- He's on his way up here now.
I'm sure it was a terrible ordeal.
But they told me Bauer's down.
- It's over.
- No. No.
It's not over, Jason.
Bauer has a recording
that implicates me along with Suvarov.
How do you know?
Because the son of a bitch
played the thing for me.
He must've put a bug on me
when he attacked the car.
For all I know, he has recorded
every conversation I've had
for the past two hours.
I'm on site now.
I'll recover whatever he's got.
You're on the line here, too.
If this evidence gets out,
- we all go down together.
- I understand what's at stake.
I'll call you back soon.
- Is he stable?
- Yes, sir.
As you requested, I searched Bauer.
We're still combing the site,
but that's what we found so far.
- There's nothing else?
- We're still sweeping.
I believe this phone is yours.
It's a...
digital recorder,
but there's nothing in it.
Come.
Excuse us.
The data card is missing.
Bauer has a digital file
that poses a threat
to national security.
- We need to find it.
- We'll keep looking.
What happened?
He drew his gun and I shot him.
That's all.
Bauer give you anything?
Like what?
He had a digital recorder.
The data card's missing.
- I thought you might know where it is.
- I don't know.
You didn't see him
stash it anywhere?
If I did, I would've taken it
and already logged it
as evidence.
Then you don't mind
emptying your pockets.
- I just shot my friend, so...
- Unless you want me
to do it for you, I need you
to empty your pockets now.
On what grounds?
National security.
Let's go.
If I search you,
will I find that data card?
This is ridiculous.
Put your hands up here.
I just told you, I shot Jack.
Why would I be helping him?
Sorry, Ms. O'Brian,
I have to be absolutely sure.
Okay.
Hope you enjoyed yourself.
It's over, Jack.
You need to talk to me,
maybe do yourself some good.
Where's the data card?
Is he stable enough to be treated
at CTU instead of the hospital?
He should be. He got lucky.
It's a through and through.
Through and through?
Bullet didn't hit any
of his organs or his arteries.
If you're gonna get shot,
that's where you want to happen.
Son of a bitch!
Get me mobile command.
What?
You got something to say to me?
Just tell me what you got to say.
Talk to me.
What?
Get him out of here!
Lock down O'Brian!
Arlo's ready to receive the file.
- Tell me why you shot Jack.
- They'd suspect me if I didn't.
My only way out
with the evidence was to shoot him.
Medical report said
it went clean through.
That no vital organs were hit.
You meant to miss them?
How did you know
you wouldn't kill him?
I didn't.
It's uploading now.
It shouldn't take long.
I just need a few more seconds.
- What's going on?
- We have to lock her down.
- What orders?
- Step aside.
Tell me what's going on first.
We won't ask again.
Step aside.
Don't... I order you... stop!
I'm ordering you to stop!
Don't!
- Is this the data that Bauer gave you?
- You need to listen to what's on it.
- Mr. Pillar'll make that decision.
- Pillar is part of the cover-up.
That data card will never
make it to evidence.
- Hold them here.
- Don't do this!
Burke, stop what you're doing!
Think about what you're doing,
Burke, stop!
I locked down O'Brian.
Looks like she was working
with Agent Ortiz. He's in custody, too.
Get the data card?
Yes, sir.
O'Brian was trying
to upload the file at CTU,
but I stopped the transmission.
Good work.
All right, send O'Brian and Ortiz
to CTU lockdown and talk to no one.
Get that data card
to President Logan.
Yes, sir.
Take them to CTU.
This is it.
This is the recording
that Jack Bauer made.
Bauer was working with Chloe O'Brian
and a field agent called Cole Ortiz.
They were planning to use CTU's servers
to disseminate this recording
to news organizations,
and government officials
and watchdog groups
on a massive scale.
It almost worked.
My people, they never gave up,
and now it's over.
You won.
Congratulations.
- Have you listened to this?
- Yes, but it's not worth hearing.
Where is Jack now?
He's about to be transported
to CTU under heavy guard.
I realize that this
is a difficult area,
but the one thing
we can be certain of
is that Jack Bauer will never
let this go.
I don't suppose he will.
All great achievements in state...
are fragile things, Madam President.
Especially in their infancy.
They need to be protected.
Our peace agreement...
very vulnerable.
As long as Jack Bauer is out there,
the agreement will never be safe.
Then we will lock him away
in a black site halfway
around the world.
He will find a way, Madam President.
Mark my words.
He will rise out
of the deepest hole in the ground.
He will claw his way back
from the ends of the Earth,
unless we stop him
before that can happen.
Pending approval,
I have taken upon myself to...
put a plan in motion.
Of course you have.
I will take your silence
as tacit approval.
A lot of good people died today,
not just President Hassan.
Operatives from CTU, members
of other law enforcement agencies.
Who I was very close to.
These people died today
because President Suvarov
wanted to destroy the peace treaty
for his own interests,
and President Taylor knows this
because I told her,
but she's willing to cover it up
because she believes
the peace accord will serve
the greater good.
She is wrong, it won't.
Both delegations are here.
What about the secretary general?
He's just outside in the atrium.
Thank you, Tim.
Lasting peace...
cannot simply be political.
It has to be born out of trust
and honesty and understanding
and most importantly,
a will on both sides to move forward.
Currently, that will does not exist.
This peace is fraudulent,
and I cannot in good conscience
allow the people that lost
their lives today to go unspoken for.
You reminded me
of that earlier today.
That's who I am.
Bauer is being handled.
Is it done?
All right, then.
You know, I wasn't sure
the President had the balls
to see this through.
Clearly, I underestimated her.
We both did, sir.
Good luck, Madam President.
This calls for a celebration.
A little something
to numb that ear pain?
What are you drinking?
Whatever you're having.
You did well, Jason.
You kept your eye on the prize.
Thank you, sir.
Here's to...
all the political capital
the President is about to bank
downstairs.
And here's to helping her spend it.
I keep having to remind myself
that we will be home tomorrow,
and this day will be behind us.
Ladies and gentlemen, please,
please take your seats.
Honored delegates
and distinguished guests,
on behalf of the United Nations,
please allow me
to welcome you to this great occasion
of hope and peace.
Today, we bear witness
to an extraordinary act
in one of the world's
defining dramas.
If you would allow me now
to offer private words to those of us
that are fortunate enough
to be here now.
May we all pledge
to make the spirit of this moment.
A new chapter...
in the history of all nations.
The President of the USA,
please, would you join me?
The President
of the Russian Federation
and the President
of the Islamic Republic of Kamistan,
would you please join me?
Before you... is the final draft
of the agreement
that has been negotiated
by you and your representatives
in good faith.
By signing its pages, you commit
your respective countries
to abide by the terms
set forth therein, as stipulated
by international law.
I believe you are to go first.
Your husband wanted me to have this.
I cannot accept it.
What are you doing?
What I should have done hours ago.
I urge you to stop
what you are about to do.
Mr. Secretary General,
my fellow delegates.
Grave crimes have been committed
in the run-up to this treaty.
I have participated
in a conspiracy
to hide those crimes.
Before there can be
a meaningful peace,
justice must be served.
I will be...
giving a more complete statement
within the hour,
but for now,
this peace process has come
to an end.
Contact CTU and have them alert
Jack Bauer's medical transport.
He is about to be ambushed.
Just make the call, Tim!
We may already be too late.
Dispatch, this is Tim Woods.
I have an emergency.
The convoy transporting Jack Bauer
is about to be ambushed.
Alert Medical One immediately.
Do it.
Madam President, talk to me.
Tell me what's happening.
I have made a terrible mistake, Tim,
one that I can never undo...
but I need you to help me stop it
from becoming worse.
This is Woods.
Thank you.
We didn't make it.
They got Bauer.
My statement is brief,
and I will take no questions.
Moments ago,
President Taylor declined to sign
the peace accord and excused herself
from the proceedings.
She did so after making allegations
of crimes which she did not specify,
and which the United Nations
has no knowledge of.
President Taylor
will come forward within the hour
to explain
the reasons for her actions.
Until then, please,
direct all queries
to the White House
Communications Office.
That's the President
asking about Bauer.
Let it ring.
With due respect, sir,
what good will it do?
It's over.
Let's not add murder to the list
of charges already against us.
You know what?
You're right.
Go ahead. Pick it up.
This is President Taylor.
I need to speak to Logan immediately.
This was my last chance,
and Bauer took it away.
It's come to this because of him.
It's locked.
- Open the door, Charles!
- This is Tim Woods.
I'm with the President.
We need the master key
to room 2206 immediately.
Damn it, Charles!
Open the door!
I need Logan alive!
Can they save him?
They think so, but they're saying
that even if he regains consciousness,
he's probably suffered
severe brain damage.
He knew he was
the only one who could
locate Jack.
Not necessarily.
CTU's drones have been
for the last hours.
They may be able to back-trace Jack
from the ambush site
- using archived surveillance video.
- Where is O'Brian?
She and Agent Ortiz returned to CTU
ten minutes ago,
- under arrest.
- I want them released immediately.
Tell Chloe to use whatever resources
are at her disposal to find Jack.
I've already done that.
Let go of me!
O'Brian, you have no authority.
What do you think you're doing?
- Shut up and keep moving.
- What the hell is going on?
- Get your hands off.
Taylor didn't sign the agreement.
She backed out at the last minute,
- but she ordered the hit on Jack.
- Did she call it off?
She tried,
but his ambulance has been ambushed.
She can't contact the hitters.
- How does she know Jack's alive?
- She doesn't.
Everyone is cleared from the floor
except for you, me and Arlo.
Arlo's redirecting the drone.
We just got police reports
of an incident downtown.
CTU convoy ambushed, three agents
wounded, but they didn't find
- Jack's body.
- Can you pull up archived video
- of the same location?
- Already on it.
- When did this happen?
- Five minutes ago.
Shuttle forward.
Give me something.
30 seconds ago,
the van pulled off of Delancey.
Damn it. Lost it
under the Williamsburg Bridge.
Go to real time.
That's it. That's the van.
All units to the vicinity.
They're never going
to make it in time.
Hold on.
Prepare for departure. We rendezvous
with Team B in 20 minutes.
I got this!
Come on.
Right here. Turn around.
Down on your knees.
I know who you are.
So I'm going to make this
quick and clean.
Am I supposed to say thank you?
Stand down! Stand down!
I really don't want to do this,
but orders are orders.
It's all right.
Pull the trigger.
Hold your fire!
It's President Taylor.
I don't have confirmation,
but it sounds like her.
CTU has a drone.
They're got a directed microwave signal.
It's how they got through to the phone.
I am ordering you
to release Jack Bauer
immediately!
You heard me!
You and your men
are to leave Mr. Bauer where he is.
Stand down
and withdraw outside the west gate
until the FBI arrives.
If you have any thoughts
of fleeing before then,
the drone is equipped
with two AGM-114
hellfire missiles.
I will not hesitate to use them.
Are we clear?
Now, put Mr. Bauer on the phone.
Uncuff him.
I said, "Uncuff him."
We've been ordered
to stand down and evacuate.
We're rolling up and evacuating.
Everyone in the van.
Let's move. Now.
The President wants to talk to you.
You should've let them kill me...
...'cause I'm not going to quit
until this is over.
It is over.
I withdrew 15 minutes ago
from the signing of the peace treaty.
Within the hour,
I will tell the world
what happened today.
I will tender my resignation
and remand myself
to the Attorney General...
and face the consequences
of my actions.
Unfortunately, you will have
to do the same.
I wanted this peace so badly, Jack.
And for that, I have betrayed
every principle
that I have ever stood for.
And I betrayed you.
If I had listened to you,
none of this would have happened.
We've both made mistakes
we're going to have to live with.
I would give anything
to take back the time.
But all I can do is tell you
to leave the country
while you still have a chance.
The Russians will
be coming after you.
And so will we.
Jack, I am so sorry.
I don't know what else to say.
Taylor told me what was happening.
She was going to give me time
to get out of the country.
- I know. I was on the call.
- My daughter...
her family... they're going to try
and use her to get to me.
They'll be protected.
Chloe, you've gotta promise me.
Promise me you'll keep them safe.
I'll make sure they're protected.
I promise.
How much time I've got?
I don't know.
I'll get you as much time as I can.
What?
When you first came to CTU...
I never thought it was you
that was going to cover my back
all those years.
I know that everything
that you did today
was to try and protect me.
I know that.
Thank you.
Good luck, Jack.
Bring the drone back to the base.
Whatever happened here
didn't happen.
Understand?
Shut it down.
Put the gun down Team pour La Fabrique
www.sous-titres.eu