Subtitles: Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu
Someone needs to take the reins
of the IRK government.
Someone who believes
in the same ideals
and principles as Omar Hassan
and who shares his strength.
If it is the will of my people,
I will take my husband's place
at the peace conference.
Did you find him,
the man who killed my father?
Samir Mehran, yes.
He was badly wounded,
but he'll live to stand trial.
I took care of him.
So there is no connection to us.
We're in the clear?
Maybe not.
There was a woman
- who might have recognized me.
- What woman?
She may be CTU.
I'm not sure,
but I've seen her face before.
Once again,
Mr. Novakovich, you're giving
every indication
that Russia has no interest
in this peace accord.
I don't understand
how you can believe
that installing Hassan's wife
will alleviate our concerns
about the instability
of the IRK government.
I have close friends in Moscow.
Do you honestly think
your relationships
- can change their minds?
- Let's just say
I'm going to be
able to exercise some leverage.
Jack thinks that someone inside
is working for the terrorists.
I spoke to Hastings.
He cleared me through.
Stay where you are...
She entered the parking.
Who are you, you lying bitch?
Don't move.
You were on the phone
before she got shot.
What were you talking about?
Samir Mehran was given a lethal
injection at the scene of his capture.
She thought she recognized
one of the EMT from her days
undercover with the mob.
I've got to get back to you.
She didn't make it.
I'm so sorry,
but we need to move her now.
Are you the husband of the deceased?
We need to contact her next of kin.
Can you help us with that?
Do you know where her parents live?
Are they alive?
I don't know.
Sir, are you gonna be all right?
I don't know if these will fit.
I got them from an intern.
Thank you.
Jack, I heard about Renee.
I'm so sorry.
What can I do to help?
Tell me who did this.
You told me earlier Renee recognized
someone at Hassan's crime scene.
An EMT?
Let us deal with that.
Everyone's on it.
Don't try and handle me,
Chloe, not now.
Who did she see?
She thought she recognized somebody
from the Russian mob... Red Square.
- Bazhaev's group?
- Right.
- I want to talk to him.
- Like I said, I'm already on it.
He's in custody somewhere, Chloe.
I brought him in myself.
Where is he?
There's something
that you need to know.
Division replaced Hastings...
with me.
That means I'm responsible
for what happens to Bazhaev.
I know you're upset about Renee.
So am I.
But Bazhaev's our only lead.
I need someone in complete control.
- I don't think that's you right now.
- I won't interfere
with your investigation.
- You think you can stick to that?
- I give you my word.
I'm gonna ask you one more time:
Where is he?
He's in federal court.
He's being arraigned right now.
Plan was for this chamber
to be full by now.
Ethan, what in the world
are you doing here?
You should be resting.
The doctor said it was my call.
I'm fine.
I was thinking, Madam President,
our discussion
about enlisting Charles Logan.
It's done.
You've contacted him?
He's on his way to talk
to the Foreign Minister.
That was fast.
The Russians were about to announce
they were pulling out of the talks.
I didn't see a lot of options.
What's his angle?
Madam President, you said
he's on his way to talk to Novakovich.
How does he intend
to get the Russians to stay?
I assume he uncovered something
in his business dealings
with them.
But you don't know what?
Not exactly.
Madam President,
he's operating in your name.
Shouldn't we find out?
I agreed I wouldn't.
Don't ask, don't tell was the price
for Logan's cooperation.
Mikhail!
Mr. President.
The Russian people join you
in mourning President Hassan.
His death was a tragedy
for all peace-loving nations.
You can save your atitudes.
You want the truth.
Why not... for a change?
Espresso.
I assume
President Taylor sent you here
to bring my country back
to the barining table.
She is going to be disappointed.
She lured the whole world here
with the promise
that Hassan had united the IRK,
that there would be peace
for the first time in decades.
Now it is clear that was a lie.
There was no unity even with Hassan,
and now that he is gone...
His widow Dalia can pick up
the mantle.
Not in our estimation.
Hassan was undone
by his own opposition.
How could his widow
succeed where he failed?
'Cause we both know the opposition
that undid him had outside help.
Nuclear threats, assassination plots
against a heavily guarded
head of state.
This was not some
Third World malcontents lashing out.
This was a highly organized effort
orchestrated by a major rival
to the United States,
a rival convinced
that their best interest
was to stop the peace process
by killing Hassan.
If you are insinuating...
Insinuating, no. I'm saying
it was people inside your government,
first among them you.
That is an outrageous accusation.
It's a fact for which I have proof.
- I don't believe you.
- Well, that's your right.
But I'll tell you this,
you don't want to test me.
Because what I have,
I will share with President Taylor
if you and I
fail to come to an understanding here.
Espresso, sir.
At this point President Taylor
knows nothing about any of this.
I didn't see what good
could come out
of inflaming the situation
between our countries further,
not without talking to you first.
And now I have.
The president's expecting me
at the UN.
I need to go.
- What will you tell her?
- I'd would like to tell her
Russia is back at the table
and her peace process is on track.
But if neither of us
hears from you before I get there,
I'm afraid what I'll have to tell her
is the unvarnished truth.
"Sergei... Buh-zay-off."
Bazhaev, Your Honor.
We'd like to waive reading.
I'm sure you would,
given the charges here.
I can tell you right now
I'm gonna deny bail.
Judge Ruffin,
Sergei Bazhaev is a businessman
with deep ties to this community.
He's a foreign national.
That's true, Your Honor,
but he has lived
in this country continuously
since 1985.
His entire family lives here.
In fact,
several members of his family
are represented in court,
his wife, daughter-in-law, grandson,
for whom incidentally
he is the sole means of support.
According to the charges,
he's their sole support
because he killed the boy's father,
not to mention the other counts:
trafficking in nuclear materials,
assassination, conspiracy.
Like I said, I'm going to deny bail.
I'm remanding him
to Marion immediately.
Your Honor, may I have
five minutes with my client?
Fine. You have five minutes.
Court will recess for 30 minutes.
Clear the courtroom, please.
My client would like
to have a word with you.
If you touch my family,
I swear to God...
You're not sitting in the right chair
to be making threats.
Who shot Renee Walker?
I don't know her.
She was a former FBI agent.
Approximately six years ago,
she worked undercover
in your organization.
Earlier today, she recognized
one of your men as Red Square.
There is no Red Square.
Not anymore.
Let me explain myself.
This agent...
I considered her to be my family.
So take a long hard look
into my eyes
and realize
that I will have no problem
taking out each member of yours
before they even get home today
unless I get the information I want.
Whoever killed her,
had nothing to do with me.
Enjoy your time at Marion.
I'll tell your wife
and your daughter-in-law you said hello.
Wait!
If I tell you,
they'll kill my family.
We'll provide them
with witness protection.
I give you my word.
Moscow.
The Russian government...
They're behind it, not me.
Everything that happened today,
all of it, was them.
- Who inside the government?
- I don't know.
You're talking about 100,000 people.
- I need names.
- I don't know names.
They never let me get close.
The woman working for them
arranged everything.
Who?
The one they planted at CTU.
You promised.
Nerve-wracking, isn't it?
Waiting.
I only saw Novakovich's face,
but you definitely
had his attention.
It's the president.
{\Charles Logan.
Charles.
Yes, Madam President.}
I just got off the phone
with the Russian foreign minister.
You did?
- And what did he say?
- He said that the two of you
had a very interesting discussion.
And that he would be coming
to the UN in five hours
with the Russian premier
to sign the treaty
as scheduled.
He also said the credit for that
is all yours.
He was in the mood to be convinced,
Madam President.
Mr. President, Ethan Kanin here.
- So you're back on your feet.
- Yes.
And I'm curious.
What did you say
to the Russian minister to convince him
to come back to the peace talks?
I told him that peace
is in all of our interests.
Seriously,
I'd like to know how you did it.
Madam President,
those details are for me alone.
That was our agreement.
Am I right?
Yes, you are.
So, Ethan...
let's not do anything...
to sully our victory.
And it is a victory.
For all of us.
It's a good feeling, isn't it?
What?
Being of service....
To your country.
Yes, it is.
I'll see you at the UN shortly.
{\O'Brian.
Hey, it's me.}
Bazhaev's family left the courthouse.
They're going to need protection.
- I want you to bring them in.
- What did he say?
The people who are behind
Renee's murder weren't Russian mob.
Said they were people
inside the Russian government.
He claims that they're behind
what happened today.
I thought the IRK opposition
was trying to stop Hassan.
He said the Russians
were using them.
He didn't explain why they don't want
the peace accord to go through,
but he did say something important.
He said Moscow's main contact
on the ground was Dana Walsh.
Dana?
You believe that?
That would explain
how she managed to breach CTU.
- I'm on my way. I want to talk to her.
- I'll set it up.
I need your help.
Jack's on his way to interview Dana.
Dana? What about?
She's some kind of agent
with the Russian government.
He says they're behind
everything that happened today.
If she knows who killed Renee or Jack
thinks she's in any way responsible,
there's no telling what he might do.
He respects you.
You might be the only one
who can deal with things
if he gets out of hand.
I know this is difficult for you,
- but during the questioning...
- I'll be there.
It's good to be back in the game,
even if it is
through the rear entrance.
President Taylor's worried
about her image.
Believe me,
I of all people understand that.
She can't keep you
hidden away forever.
That's right.
Credit given where credit is due.
Publicly.
That's our deal.
Right.
Believe me,
the president will be grateful to know.
Who is that agent?
I want him reassigned.
- That was my contact at Justice...
- Did you hear me?
I'll take care of it.
But we have a more immediate problem.
What does he have to do with this?
He was at the federal courthouse,
the arraignment of a Sergei Bazhaev.
Bauer got to him behind closed doors
and got him to talk.
- How much does Bazhaev know?
- He knows about Dana Walsh,
- the mole the Russians planted at CTU.
- I know who she is.
Bauer's headed to CTU,
presumably to talk to her.
My sources tell me
Walsh hasn't given up anything
about Moscow's involvement.
Not yet.
But she knows enough
to bring everything down.
- If she gets in a room with him...
- Obviously, that can't happen.
We need to stop Bauer
before he talks to her.
That won't be easy.
He may have a personal stake in this.
Apparently, he was asking
Bazhaev about a Renee Walker.
She was shot dead in Bauer's apartment
less than an hour ago.
This could easily get out of hand.
You may need to ask
President Taylor to intervene.
Are you suggesting
that I tell her the truth?
If she finds out what they've done,
she'll be furious I kept her out of it.
- She might back out of our deal.
- You really need to stop Bauer now.
I don't see any other way.
You have to talk to the president.
Bauer torpedoed my presidency.
Tried to ruin me, almost did.
There's no way
I'm gonna let that happen again.
Thank you.
- Dana Walsh ready?
- Yes, I'll take you to her.
I'm so sorry about Renee.
I don't even know what to say.
Dana know I'm going to be
interrogating her?
- I didn't want to give her a heads-up.
- Good.
I'm sorry about Renee.
I have to leave the cameras on.
You think I'm gonna kill her?
I wouldn't blame.
If I wanted her dead, she'd be dead.
I'm just gonna wake her up
to the idea of it.
Open the door.
What do you want?
I want to know
who killed Renee Walker.
She's dead?
That doesn't make any sense.
It must have been a mistake.
No mistake.
I'm sorry.
Really.
You're sorry?
I want the shooter!
I want to know ordered it!
I want names!
- Stop him!
- Let it play.
Stop. Or you get nothing.
You think you get
to make demands here?
I can give you the hitter,
the man behind him,
- all the way up to the top.
- I want more,
- than just names. I want proof!
- I have proof.
An audio file,
- film.
- Where?
First I want my immunity deal back.
Soon as I start talking, I'm dead.
Your move.
If you lie to me.
I'll find you
no matter where you try and hide.
You understand that?
Good.
We've had such little good news
these last few hours,
I wanted to tell you right away.
The delegates have voted
unanimously to accept you
as the representative of the IRK
- at the signing of the treaty.
- I'm pleased.
Thank you for all your efforts.
You're welcome.
There is one proviso, of course.
That my own country accept me
as signatory of the treaty.
I know you've had very little time
to pursue this.
Jamot and I have
been making progress.
Our constituent assembly
will vote on the issue,
but as we've already
received pledges of loyalty
from most of my husband's coalition,
I believe we have a good chance
of success.
Excellent.
- We might just make it yet.
- We might.
I need a word.
Excuse me.
- Logan wants to speak with you.
- About what?
He wouldn't say
except that it's urgent.
He's waiting in your office.
Following President Hassan's death,
the expectation
was that the delegates
to the peace conference,
would have to pack up and go home.
But the latest rumors coming out
of the UN are pretty sensational.
That Dalia Hassan might be stepping
into her husband's shoes.
There are already
street demonstrations
taking place in Kamistan
in support Mrs Hassan.
- The president is here.
- Thank you.
Thank you for seeing me.
Ethan said you wanted
to speak with me.
Can we have the room, please?
- What's this about?
- Jack Bauer. He's out of control.
He's already pressured
a Russian mafioso in federal court,
and he's on his way
to question a woman
in custody at CTU.
Why does he want to talk to her?
He thinks she knows who's behind
the shooting of a Renee Walker.
Agent Walker?
She's dead?
How did this happen?
That's still being investigated,
but in the meantime,
what I'm saying is
Bauer needs to be stopped.
Why?
You're going to have to trust me.
What we need to do right now
- is lock Bauer down.
- You better tell me exactly
what's going on.
I won't do a thing about Jack Bauer
until you tell me the truth.
Elements inside
the Russian government
were behind both
the assassination of President Hassan
and the supply of nuclear material
to his enemies.
- The Russian government?
- Why they're back at the table?
Because I threatened to expose
their role in today's events.
You knew about this
- and you didn't tell?
- I protected the President.
Protected her?
You've compromised her hopelessly!
Why didn't you say anything before?
I told you that I had leverage
with the Russians.
You must've understood
it was significant.
Significant, yes!
Evidence of a sex scandal,
some kind of financial malfeasance,
not this, for God's sake!
If I find...
that you were
in a position to prevent
- anything...
- No.
This information
came to me only recently.
From whom?
- I can't tell you.
- You will.
I can't, Madam President,
because it would do no good.
My sources would plausibly deny,
even knowing me.
Bauer is about to bring out the Russian
involvement into the open?
If he talks to Dana Walsh, yes.
The Russians inserted her at CTU
months ago.
She was their agent.
If Bauer gets to her,
it will all come out,
and then this, this...
will all be finished.
It's finished anyways.
Do you think the president wants
anything more to do with the Russians
after what they've done?
You do, Madame President,
because you
are looking at the bigger picture,
the greater good.
How can you call any of this good?
Because it is good,
an undeniable good!
A peace that's escaped the world
for generations!
That's what you're on the verge
of achieving.
Do you really want
to throw it all away?
Do you really think
Dalia Hassan will sit down
at the table
with the people
who murdered her husband?
Who says she has to know?
Believe me, I know
how hard you worked for this,
how you sweated and prayed,
the sleepless nights.
I know.
The power to make a difference...
that's why we came into politics.
How few of us
get to achieve it,
but you have...
You so nearly have.
Ethan will tell you to make a stand.
I applaud his moral clarity,
but then he's on the sidelines.
- He can afford it.
- That's enough!
Is the situation ideal? No!
Far from it,
but you have a real chance
to make the world a better place.
Don't listen to this, Allison.
If the treaty's not signed today,
it's not the end.
You can build a better peace,
with honest partners.
"There is a tide
in the affairs of men,
"which, taken at the flood,
leads on to fortune."
What the hell does that mean?
The president knows.
It's from Julius Caesar.
It means "Now or never. "
Madam President,
I have Jack Bauer for you.
Where is he?
He's at CTU.
He wants to talk to you
about an immunity agreement
for a Dana Walsh.
I'll have to call him back.
There is no choice here.
But there is a choice, Ethan,
and unfortunately,
only I can make it.
I'm going to CTU.
To do what?
To see Jack Bauer.
- Has the president called back yet?
- Not yet.
Are you sure
you want to do this to yourself?
We can take it from here.
The minute Dana's immunity deal
is back in place,
we can roll up the names,
close this out.
I need to see this through.
Excuse me.
The president's on the phone,
line 3.
She asked for Chloe.
- I'm on my way to see you.
- You're coming to CTU?
Yes, I'm almost there.
I need to talk to Jack Bauer.
Make sure he doesn't leave.
Let security know
the president will be here soon.
She's coming here?
That's what I just said.
Have them standing by.
- Why she doing this?
- She said she wants to talk to you.
- Why not just talk to me on the phone?
- I don't know.
You should probably meet her
in Hastings' office.
Fine.
Welcome to CTU.
I'm Chloe O'Brian.
Thank you, Ms. O'Brian.
Is Jack inside?
Right this way.
I want to say how grateful I am
for all your efforts today.
We've taken some pretty hard hits,
but we've managed
to keep ourselves in the game.
The peace process is still alive,
and I am counting on your hard
work and your vigilance
to keep it that way.
I know you won't let me down.
Thank you, Miss O'Brian.
I'll go up alone.
I am so sorry
about Agent Walker.
I gather she meant a lot to you.
Which makes
what I'm about to ask so very,
very hard.
Please, Jack.
I need you to stand down.
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
I do not want you
to question Dana Walsh.
Madam President the information
that I can extract from Dana Walsh
is not limited
to the murder of Renee Walker.
I believe she knows the names
of the people who facilitated
the assassination of Hassan,
people working
within the Russian government.
That is pure speculation.
Then let me question her.
If she's lying,
- you lose nothing.
- I'm sorry.
I won't give Dana Walsh immunity.
I can't.
The peace process is back on track.
Dalia Hassan will represent
her country at the signing.
The Russians have accepted her
and have undertaken
to support the treaty.
They have been trying
to destroy the treaty.
- You can't trust them.
- You don't know that.
The information that I have
came from Sergei Bazhaev,
and I believe him.
If you let me question Dana Walsh,
I can prove it.
I won't allow it.
You don't want to know the truth.
What I want is to keep
the Russians at the table.
Allegations of this sort
will drive them away.
What if they are true?
If I keep the Russians at the table,
I can bring peace to a part of the world
that has known nothing but war
for generations.
That is the greater good
that I am working toward.
And to achieve it,
there have to be sacrifices!
With all due respect,
these people gave weapons to terrorists
who were willing to erase Manhattan!
You don't know that!
And I'm telling you,
we have to move on.
Even Hassan's widow
has picked up the torch
and is continuing this process.
Does she know the Russians
helped murder her husband?
Would she be willing
to sign that treaty if she knew that?
- Have you even told her?
- Enough.
- Have you told her?
- I said that's enough!
This peace treaty
is in the interests
of the United States
and of the world.
That makes it a good in itself,
and certainly
more important
than your desire for revenge.
Madam President,
I don't want revenge, I want justice.
And I want peace.
If there were another way,
I would take it, but there's not.
That's my decision.
Do you understand?
Do you understand, Jack?
I've arranged a helicopter
to fly you from CTU
to McGuire Air Force Base.
You're locking me down.
You'll be debriefed there.
Good-bye, Jack.
I'm sorry.
- I had them gather your things.
- Thanks.
- What happened?
- Nothing.
- What do you mean?
- I mean nothing.
Nothing happened.
What I need is a meeting
with Dalia Hassan
to coordinate our response
to the likely questions.
Will you set that up?
Thank you.
I'm leaving CTU now.
I'll be with you
in ten minutes.
They said you wanted to see me.
Dana Walsh is to remain locked down
until further notice.
No one gets access to her
without my express permission.
Is that clear?
I guess.
What about Jack?
Jack is going to McGuire
Air Force Base to be debriefed.
He didn't seem very happy
about that.
He was disappointed I wouldn't grant
Walsh immunity
in exchange for her testimony.
But Dana knows
who's responsible for today.
She is a sociopath.
She'll say anything.
And the last thing we need right now
is a bunch of unfounded allegations
derailing the peace
that we've all worked so hard for.
Do you understand?
We're having a press conference
at the UN in two hours
to present Dalia Hassan
as the new leader of the IRK
and to announce that the peace talks
are still on track.
What we need CTU to do
is to make sure
security is airtight.
Tim Woods speaks very highly of you.
When the situation got out of control,
he was adamant that you were the one
to take over.
I'm surprised
he even knows who I am.
It was a pleasure
to meet you finally, Chloe.
Thank you.
Cole, we're gonna be back
on UN detail.
- What's happening with Dana?
- As of now, nothing.
- The immunity agreement?
- There won't be any.
Why not?
The president says
Dana's a lying sociopath
who will wreck the peace treaty.
- What's Jack say about that?
- I don't know.
He's being choppered to McGuire
for debriefing.
Chloe, what the hell's going on?
There will be a press conference soon,
it's up to us to guarantee security.
You'll need to get your teams ready.
So Jack's being taken away
for a debrief?
- About what, may I ask?
- No.
Director O'Brian,
this is Falcon One.
- We're touching down at CTU.
- Copy that.
Security personnel en route to the roof
with Jack Bauer.
Mr. Bauer, Agent Winnick.
I have to escort you
to McGuire Air Force Base
for a debrief.
Heard a lot about you, sir.
I'm sorry we had to meet
under these circumstances.
There's no reason to be sorry.
I'm taking this helicopter.
Tell your men to drop their weapons
or you'll die.
Arlo, pull up the audio.
Something's happening.
Coming up.
Put your weapons down now!
I will kill him!
All security to the helipad now.
- What's going on?
- He's gonna steal that helicopter.
Out of the copter now!
Bauer took a hostage.
Hijacking the helicopter.
Hold your fire!
Lower your weapons!
Give me your walkie.
Land the chopper now.
You know I have to call this in.
The Air Force will force you down.
This is a bad idea.
Land the chopper
now.
Call the FAA, the Air Force.
Tell them we have a stolen helicopter
flying west over Manhattan that needs
to be intercepted and forced down.