Subtitles: Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu
Mr. Bauer, you are ordered
to turn the aircraft around
and return to CTU.
Jack's descending.
Choppers are in pursuit.
We've lost him.
If Jack gets this evidence
and exposes the Russians,
the agreement is over.
The agreement
may not be the only casualty.
You covered up
the Russians' involvement.
That's grounds for impeachment.
There's still a chance that CTU
will find Jack.
Even if they do,
the evidence is still out there.
Eventually, it will surface.
You need to control the evidence
by keeping Walsh off the grid.
Classify her as an enemy combatant
and incarcerate her
in a private facility.
I've authorized
a private interrogation team
to acquire the evidence.
Once we have it,
she'll be irrelevant.
I can't be a part
of this any longer.
Cite my health as the reason
for my resignation.
The president's ordered your transfer
to an off-site facility.
What do you mean?
It's a secure location.
Just do what he says.
Chloe, don't let them do this.
- Let's go.
- Please.
They're gonna kill me. Chloe!
Chloe, please!
You told Bauer you have evidence.
I have got nothing to tell you.
There is no evidence.
The sooner you tell me,
the easier it'll go.
Mobilizing a sting operation
to be led by Agent Ortiz.
The target is Jack Bauer.
Put your weapons down!
I can't do that!
Put your weapons down now!
I need you to help me
gain access to Walsh.
I am giving you an opportunity
to make this right,
to make the people that are responsible
for everything that happened today.
Chloe said she's in a safe house
a few miles from here.
Now it's imperative
that they think I took you hostage.
Get up!
And though fate has prevented
my husband from being here today
at the culmination
of his life's work,
I know that he is watching us now,
looking down and guiding us
as we take the last steps
towards this historic agreement.
Finally, I would like
to express my gratitude
to President Taylor...
whose integrity
and moral courage
have been unshakable
during the long course
of these negotiations.
She is someone on whom
my husband built an absolute trust.
And I want to make it clear
that her efforts and the efforts
of the United States government
to rescue him
were nothing short of heroic.
My husband wasn't perfect.
None of us is.
But he carried a perfect idea
in his heart:
that peace is possible.
On this,
the last day of his life,
may the world come together
and prove that he was right.
What a magnificent woman.
- Who was that on the phone?
- Bledsoe.
It's not the best of news, sir.
Dana Walsh isn't being
as cooperative as hoped.
She's a trained enemy agent,
she's not gonna to break easily.
I told President Taylor
what might be necessary,
and she signed off on it.
Bledsoe's a professional, sir.
I'm confident
he'll come through for us.
He better.
There was one more thing.
Bledsoe wanted confirmation.
About what?
How to deal with Ms. Walsh,
post interrogation.
- I thought we settled that matter.
- We did.
So why's he asking?
To double check
we're committed to the same outcome.
And what did you tell him?
We're still committed
to the same outcome.
Not that I have any idea
what you're talking about.
You understand?
Perfectly.
Let her up.
I'll give you a little tip.
Take short, shallow breaths.
You'll recover faster.
And then we won't have so much
downtime between sessions.
It's up to you, you know.
You can stop this whenever you want.
All you have to do
is tell me what I want to know.
I told you that I was making it up.
There is no evidence.
You told Jack Bauer
you had proof that elements
in the Russian government were behind
the assassination of Hassan.
I was bluffing.
Stalling for time.
There isn't any proof.
- Don't lie to me.
- I'm not lying.
We begin again in ten seconds.
Seven, six...
Bring it on, you son of a bitch.
Put her down.
Where's the evidence?
Go to hell.
Gag her.
They got two sentries
out in front in a black sedan,
one lookout on the roof,
maybe another across the street,
but I couldn't see him.
We can access the back
through that alley.
So, once we get Dana, what then?
As painful as it is, we got to cut
a deal in exchange for the evidence.
- You mean let her go.
- Cole, we both lost friends today.
And Dana had a hand in that,
but only a hand.
If we can get the people in charge,
the people that gave the orders,
it'll be worth it.
It's Chloe.
Answer it or she'll know
something's wrong.
If she doesn't already.
Cole, what's your ETA?
Ten minutes. FDR Drive was a mess.
We're coming up First Ave instead.
Is Jack with you?
I got him.
He's locked down in the back.
I'm glad we found him
before he got hurt.
Or worse.
I've known Jack for a long time,
I've never seen him like this.
He threatened me.
He's never done that before.
You did the right thing.
Thanks for saying that.
I'll talk to you when you get here.
We're good.
She has no idea.
Don't be too hard on her.
- She wants the best for you.
- I know.
Almost forgot.
You're gonna need these.
I'm sorry, I just couldn't
take the chance.
Son of a bitch.
Yeah, I know.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Keep your head down.
Go.
That's right, four hours prior
to the signing ceremony,
all available field units
will be redeployed to the UN.
Mobile HQ is being
set up on the first floor,
near the high commissioner's offices.
Hold on, O'Brian is on the other line.
Who's the psych officer?
That would be Melissa Anderson.
She did all the grief counseling
last night.
Make sure
she's the first person Jack sees.
I want a complete eval.
You think that's necessary?
I wouldn't have ordered it
if I didn't.
I'll let her know.
They got one man on the roof.
Wait till I get into position,
then you draw them out.
Unit two. Street's clear.
Unit three. Back alley's clear.
Command, this is unit four.
Roof's clear.
All units, copy that.
Stay alert.
We're clear.
Let's go.
You make that cover.
I'll draw him out.
I'm taking sniper fire on the roof.
Across the street.
- I need backup now.
- Unit four, stand by.
- I'm sending backup now.
- Copy that. Hurry!
All units to the roof.
Unit four is reporting sniper fire.
Command, we're on the roof.
It's quiet, there's no sign of Mullins.
Come again?
All's quiet,
but we can locate Unit four.
Unit four, come in, please.
Where's Dana Walsh?
Where is she?
Mullins is down, sir.
Last chance.
- Repeat, Mullins is down.
- First room on the left.
Thank you.
Do you copy?
Come in.
We're clear.
The first room on the left,
I've got it.
- Put your gun down!
- Drop your weapon or I'll kill her!
I'll kill you, if I have to.
You won't take the shot.
It's too risky. I'll kill her before...
Untie her.
Take her out the back.
We're gonna get company soon.
Hurry!
- Have you got her?
- Almost!
I got her!
Move!
Stay covered.
Take the stairs now!
Get going!
I'll be right behind you!
Just finishing rescanning
the field reports.
You need to hear this.
Agent Beck just checked in.
He said he's been locked down
for the past half hour,
just managed to free himself.
- What?
- Jack didn't fall for the trap.
Instead, he reversed the entire squad
and took Cole hostage.
- I just talked to Cole.
- Beck says
Jack had him at gunpoint.
Pull up the satellite
on the address: 1463312th Street.
It's where they're holding Dana.
It's where Jack's on his way to now.
What is going on?
He's been two steps ahead of me.
He probably knew
what I was gonna do before I did.
Hello, everybody!
Can I have your attention, please?
Jack Bauer's
no longer in custody of CTU.
Agent Ortiz is with him,
most likely as a hostage.
Our priority is to find them now.
- Satellite's online.
- Put it up.
Too late. Put the APB
back out on Jack, all agencies.
Get me the White House.
- Where are we going?
- You tell me.
You had a file implicating
people in the Russian government
who are responsible
for Renee's murder.
I want that file.
And I said I'd give it to you
in exchange for immunity.
That deal's off the table.
The President decided
the agreement's more important.
As far as she's concerned, that file
can never see the light of day.
But I still want it.
- What's the new deal?
- You give us the file, we let you go.
Go where, Riker's Island?
You're a small fish. I'm going
after the people who gave the orders.
You give me the evidence,
we'll let you go. I give you my word.
Your word?
I'm sorry.
I don't believe you, Jack.
Fine.
You think it's a joke?
We'll do it another way.
Get out. Get out!
Tell me where that file is. Now!
- It's the only thing keeping me alive!
- No, right now
I'm the only thing
keeping you alive.
I'm gonna count backwards from 3,
then I'm gonna kill you.
You're really not gonna
let him shoot me, are you?
Back off!
In a safety-deposit box!
Where?
First Unity Savings. Cole knows.
We have a joint account.
But the box is in my name,
I'm the only one who can access it.
- Where's the bank?
- Lexington, off East 59th.
I had nothing to do
with Renee's death.
- I didn't even know she was a target.
- Put her in the car.
Damn it! You see what's
happening here, don't you?
- He's using you.
- Using me? You're using me.
What do you think he's gonna do?
He's gonna give the file to the press
and expose everyone responsible.
Is that what you think?
'Cause I doubt that's what Jack thinks.
He's gonna
make a list of the guilty,
then he's gonna execute them,
starting with me.
This isn't about the truth.
It's about revenge!
I can't do this!
She's trying
to get inside your head.
I know that, damn it!
You got something you want to say to me,
you better say it now.
Were you gonna pull that trigger?
I need her to think I would.
Please allow me
to offer my condolences for your loss.
- Your husband was a great man.
- Thank you.
How has news of his death
been received back in the IRK?
And do people there
generally support
your decision to take his place
as head of state?
I'm confident that most of my country
is behind me.
Those who aren't, probably
never supported my husband's policies.
And what are your plans
after the treaty is signed?
Right now,
I'm concentrating all my efforts
on the pursuit of finishing
what my husband started.
But I want to return to Kamistan...
Is this true?
I'm afraid so, ma'am.
The details are sketchy,
but as of 15 minutes ago,
Jack Bauer stormed the safe house,
overwhelmed security
and took Dana Walsh.
Do we have any idea where they are?
A hard target search is under way.
Your note mentioned Charles Logan.
He's been demanding to speak to you.
He insisted that I interrupt
the press conference.
- All you'll have to do is hit redial.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, ma'am.
... the body be ritually washed
and draped...
How in God's name
could this have happened?
The important thing is not to panic.
You assured me that Dana Walsh
would be more secure in the hands
- of your private contractors.
- We didn't move her out of CTU
solely for security reasons,
as I'm sure you remember.
Do you have me on speaker?
Pick up the damn phone.
Forgive me, I wasn't thinking.
Apparently, neither was I.
It's a little late for buyer's remorse,
Madam President,
especially because I was calling
with a solution
to our current problem.
Bauer may have Walsh,
but he can't have the evidence yet.
We've still got a chance
to stop him.
- How?
- By putting somebody inside CTU,
someone whose loyalties
aren't split,
who won't hesitate
to see the mission through
no matter what the cost.
I've already replaced one director.
I can't replace another.
No, not a new director. Just someone
to supervise the manhunt for Bauer.
I'm recommending Jason Pillar.
Your aide?
He's Bureau-trained.
He was second in command at DIA
during the Daniel's administration
and he made a name for himself
in Afghanistan,
chasing high-value targets
behind enemy lines.
Of course if you have a better idea,
I'll gladly take a step back.
- Madam.
- Just a second.
- What is it?
- Mrs. Hassan is finishing up.
I'm on my way.
Look,
I'll tell Tim Woods that I support you
making an operational change.
But that's it, Charles...
no more excuses.
Thank you, Madame President.
And allow me to say that...
No, I understand completely.
And I appreciate
your confidence in Jason.
- How soon can you leave for CTU?
- Immediately.
Good. I'll handle the arrangements
on this end.
... in over late husband Omar Hassan
in an address to the press and members
of an international delegation
at the United Nations.
Congratulations, Charles.
You have recast yourself
as the great peacemaker.
I appreciate your help
in getting me this far, Mikhail.
So tell me what I'm doing here?
I had hoped
to have this conversation in private.
This is my attaché Pavel Tokarev.
You can speak freely.
He is more than well acquainted
with the situation.
There's been an unforeseen problem.
Apparently I'm not the only one
who can prove that elements
in your government conspired
to undermine the peace process.
Meaning?
The mole you installed inside CTU,
claims to have evidence
to that effect.
Not possible.
She was handled
with complete deniability.
So you say.
But, no one in this room
can take the chance
that she's bluffing.
Now... I tried to contain this.
I had Ms. Walsh detained
and interrogated.
The problem is,
Jack Bauer just broke her out.
Apparently,
he has a personal interest
in exposing this evidence.
Then you need to stop him.
Surely President Taylor
is motivated to do the same.
She is, to a point.
But I know Bauer.
And I can promise you
he will never let this go.
And I don't think
the president is willing to do
what is ultimately required.
So you expect me
to kill Bauer for you?
We both know
you have the covert assets here
to do the job.
Maybe I do...
but I don't have the resources
to find him, track him.
CTU does.
And the man in charge
of the search now reports to me.
How would this work?
This is a closed-channel phone.
It's impossible to intercept.
My man at CTU will use it to feed
your people real-time information
as to Bauer's whereabouts.
And they can put an end
to this problem, once and for all.
We have to assume that CTU's
been getting my face out there.
You'll have to take her
into the bank alone.
I'll stand sentry in the lobby.
How well do you know the layout inside?
Vault's in the back.
Tellers are on one side of the room,
loan officers are on the other.
One of them's an old buddy of mine.
He was helping us line up a mortgage.
You keep her
inside your strike zone.
If she sees an opportunity,
she'll take it. Do not trust her.
I'll be fine, Jack.
Okay, let's go.
You hate me right now,
but I don't really believe
- you want to see me executed.
- Save it.
We both saw how close he came
to pulling the trigger back there.
That's just
what he wanted you to think.
If that's what he told you,
he's lying.
Just like he's lying
about what he'll do with that file.
Jack wants to bring the people
responsible for this to justice.
- Just like me.
- Who do you think they are?
They're Russian diplomats
with diplomatic immunity.
They'll be indicted by the World Court
and hauled up in front of the Hague.
You really believe he wants to trust
some toothless international tribunal
to mete out justice to the people
who killed Renee?
- Come on.
- You're hurting me.
You'll live.
Confirm all traffic camera feeds
are being ported through us.
Up-res and route everything
through facial recognition.
Parameter-matching
on Jack, Cole, or Dana.
We don't have anywhere
near the bandwidth to do that citywide.
Then job the overflow to NSA.
Where are we on setting up
the search grid with NYPD?
In process. They're giving us
the personnel they can spare,
but they're going on record that,
unless we narrow down the search area,
it's "needle in a haystack" time.
There's a Jason Pillar
on his way to see you.
Tim Wood's office pre-cleared him.
Send him up.
He's already on his way.
He wouldn't wait.
Never heard of him.
Who is he?
He was second in command at DIA
under Daniel.
He's been working
the private sector for years.
This is my associate Eden Linley.
So why are you here?
The White House is unhappy with the way
the manhunt's been handled.
President Taylor's issued
an executive order
placing me in charge of the search.
You'll retain your current position
for the time being
with authority
over all over CTU operations.
Arlo, give us a minute?
You got it.
- This doesn't make any sense.
- Excuse me?
Why are you here?
You have nothing to do
with H.S. anymore.
All you need to know is that I'm here
under the president's orders.
You're wasting your time.
We've done all we can.
If that were true, then the trap
you set for Bauer would have worked.
- It's complicated.
- You were more concerned
not to hurt him.
It's all in the hourlies.
In fact,
the last operational command
you sent to Agent Ortiz was,
"Remember, non-lethal force. "
Not exactly
the appropriate sentiment
when the president told you
to stop Bauer.
She doesn't want to hurt him.
You both know
what he'd done for this country.
What Bauer's doing
will destroy the peace agreement.
And the president
cannot let that happen.
It's time
to take off the kid gloves.
We need protocols and encryption keys
transferred to us immediately.
As well as system overrides
and administrative privileges.
Understood?
Yeah, understood.
Re-code the all-agency bulletin
on Bauer
to "armed and dangerous"
level eight.
And change the use of force guidelines
to "unrestricted. "
Here we go.
Just make yourselves comfortable.
I'll be right back
with your safety deposit box.
Let's go.
Something funny?
This.
You and me... it's not the way
that it was supposed to turn out.
I'm serious, Cole.
Now that this is all over,
you deserve to hear the truth.
It's a little late for the truth.
If you're even capable of it.
You don't have to believe me.
I was a kid.
A kid with five years of prison
behind me and no future to speak of.
A guy came to see me...
a Russian.
Said that he could give me
a fresh start.
I had absolutely no idea
what I was getting myself into.
You could have come clean
anytime you wanted.
And go back to jail.
Not a chance.
Look, I know
that it's not an excuse,
but ever since I met you
I have been trying to dig myself out
of this mess that I'm in.
You're right...
I don't believe you.
It's why I made that video file.
I was going to use it as leverage
to get the Russians to leave us alone.
Us?
There is no "us," Dana.
There never was.
It was a lie from the beginning.
That is not true.
Just stop playing me.
It won't work.
I am not playing you.
I loved you.
Here we go... 14-05.
I'll be outside.
Thank you, Brian.
You never give up, do you?
You guys all right?
911. What is your emergency?
Hi. I'm at First Unity Savings Bank
on Lexington.
There's a guy by the front door.
I think I saw him on the news.
I think he has a gun.
Oh, my God.
He's looking in my direction.
Great. As quickly as you can.
The 911 comm center
just confirmed the call.
Bauer was supposedly ID'd by someone
at the First Unity Savings Branch
on Lexington.
- What do you mean supposedly?
- That all we have is the caller's word
that she recognized Jack
from the news coverage.
- We don't have secondary confirmation.
- Then get it.
Request access to the bank's
video surveillance system.
I've already contacted them.
I'm just trying to connect.
Having trouble getting
the CTU comm protocols to work.
- You, what's your name?
- Devon Rosenthal.
Help her.
Don't look at O'Brian.
I'm giving you the order. Follow it.
All right,
let's see what's going on.
All right, this is the...
Got it?
Here we go.
Full access to the bank's
video surveillance system.
We got him.
Call NYPD and make sure
they realize the priority here.
Tell them I want to be looped
in their operation in real time.
- Got it.
- Be right back.
- Yes?
- We found Bauer.
He's at a bank.
First Unity Savings on Lexington.
How do you know?
A 911 call confirmed
by video surveillance.
Then the police
are already on their way.
Can't help that.
But once they have Bauer,
I'll find out where they're holding him.
You'll have to take him out there.
I'll wait for your call.
Brown jacket, freeze! Police!
Get your hands up!
Get your hands up now!
Hands up!
On your knees.
Get down on your knees.
Put your hands behind your head.
Interlock your fingers, thumbs out.
Do not move.
We got him.
Take it easy.
You got no chance.
- We got units coming in.
- Shut up!
You know who I am?
Do you know who I am?!
I don't want to kill your partner,
but I will if I have to.
So here's what we're gonna do:
slowly, you're gonna
put your gun down.
Drop your weapon now!
Kick it over to me.
I'm sorry.
Call an ambulance now.
Tell them
two police officers are down.
Don't you move!
Slowly...
turn around and head back to me.
Now!
What happened to Cole?
Did you kill him?
I could never do that.
Where's the evidence?
It's in my pocket.
Show me.
- Jack, we can make a deal.
- Show me!
I want you to slowly
put it down on the floor.
Tell me what I can do.
Nothing.