Subtitles:
Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu (V 1.00)
I've thought
about what we talked about.
I want to move back to LA with you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You're coming with us tonight?
- If it's okay.
Dad, I don't know what to say.
I'm so happy!
- How the hell did you find me?
- I have information.
I'm out. I don't work
for the government anymore.
This you're gonna want to hear.
There's a big hit going down.
President Hassan at the UN,
he's getting taken out.
- When?
- Today,
before he can sign with Taylor.
My country agrees to abandon
the pursuit of nuclear weapons.
But our terms, Mr. President,
were that the inspectors themselves
would be American,
not IAEA.
This is the message you send
to the rest of the world,
and then you wonder
why we don't want to negotiate!
Please excuse my brother's passion.
We need to resolve this issue
before we can move forward.
Find a way to give him what he wants.
This man is a once-in-a-lifetime leader.
- I'm stuck outside.
- I'll take care of it.
This woman poses no threat to me
or the peace process.
But you are married.
I've done nothing reckless.
Just reinstate Ms. Reed's
clearance now.
Unless you want to destroy
everything that he's worked for,
stay away from him.
The brother revoked my clearance,
but I had Hassan reinstate it.
I know I'm behind schedule,
but it'll get done.
Excuse me, Mr. Hastings.
Jack Bauer's on line three.
He needs to talk to you.
I'm with an informant
who has intel on an assassination
attempt on President Hassan.
And what does Mr. Aruz
want in return for his information?
CTU protection and immunity.
I'll send a chopper to pick you up.
Don't stop! Keep going!
Get him out of here.
He's losing a lot of blood!
Hastings wants to debrief you
back at CTU.
I'm not going back to CTU.
I'm done.
- I got a flight to catch.
- That's it?
Get down!
Tell me what you know.
The hitter has someone
on the inside...
close to Hassan.
It's done.
Aruz is no longer a problem.
But we don't know how much
he told CTU.
We need to accelerate the hit.
Agent Ortiz is calling in.
Put him through.
I want everyone on this.
Comm channel 235.
All right, go ahead.
This is Cole.
Where are those EMTs?
They should be there any second.
How's the rest of your team?
Earley's injured.
Torres and Johnson are dead.
What happened? Look, those drones
are supposed to have antiballistics.
Why didn't they take out
the missile?
- We're still running the diagnostic.
- Sir, this should've never happened!
We should've had another team
checking those buildings!
We can discuss this at a later time,
Agent Ortiz.
Yes, sir.
Bauer wants to talk with you.
- Put him on the phone.
- Stand by.
Jack, I have Mr. Hastings
on the line.
Victor Aruz told me
right before he died
that the assassin is working
with someone very close to Hassan.
- Did you get a name?
- No, not before he died.
- You believe him?
- Normally, I wouldn't trust him.
He was dying, sir.
He had no reason to lie.
All right. We're on it.
I need you and Cole back here
to debrief.
I already gave one
of your agents my statement.
I need you back here.
Fine. We're on our way.
I may have a lead on that insider.
What do you mean?
I just picked up an unauthorized access
in the secure databases at the UN.
- How do you know it's unauthorized?
- They bypassed the main access page
and went through a back-end server.
The only reason to do that
is if you're trying
to cover your tracks.
Let me know if you trace the source.
And put O'Brian on this, too,
if you don't think
she'll slow you down.
- No. She's doing much better, sir.
- I'm gonna call the chief of staff.
They need to know this insider
could be moving against Hassan.
You are under a great deal
of pressure at home
from an active opposition
to this peace agreement.
They believe that by dismantling
your nuclear weapons programs,
you're surrendering to the West.
How do you respond to those charges?
The only thing we are surrendering
is the cloud of antagonism and mistrust
under which we have lived
for far too long.
This is a victory for my people.
It marks an end to isolation
and will bring economic stability
to my country for the first time
in decades.
How do you propose economic stability
when your people are so divided?
This is Weiss.
Did you bring in Victor Aruz?
I'm afraid not, sir.
There was an ambush,
and Aruz was killed,
along with two of our men.
Damn it.
Before Aruz died, he shared
some very troubling information.
Now, he claimed that someone close
to President Hassan has been
conspiring with the assassin.
Now, we don't have a name yet,
but we are pursuing a lead.
Tell me how,
and I'd better be impressed.
We're tracing what might be
an unauthorized entry
into one of the UN servers.
- This is the person we're looking for?
- We're optimistic.
You better hope that optimism
translates into results.
Sir, until we locate the insider,
you might want to consider
locking down President Hassan
and postponing this conference.
That is not an option, Mr. Hastings.
We are close to signing
one of the most important treaties.
You were put in charge of CTU because
you said you could get the job done.
"Lean, mean and fast",
that's what you said.
President Taylor expects you
to deliver on those words.
I'll take this to the president.
Keep me posted.
President Hassan and I
still have a great deal of work to do,
we're gonna wrap this up,
but I would like to say
that the president and I
chose the United Nations
as the venue for these talks
because the problems facing
the Middle East have become
a world concern.
And President Hassan and I
are confident
that this agreement will lay
the foundation
for a lasting peace in the region.
And we thank you for your time.
I'll see you after the break.
I look forward to resuming it.
Madam President,
I just spoke with CTU.
There's been a development
regarding the threat to Hassan.
We need to speak in private.
- That is really wonderful.
- Thank you. I'll join you later.
You were terrific.
It's not about me,
it's the message that's important.
I just hope no one
could see how nervous I was.
You hid it well.
- Are you here?
- Yes, on my way up.
Do you still have time to see me?
I've been looking forward
to it all day.
When?
- What did you say?
- When can I see you?
I've got half an hour
before the next session begins.
You meet me now, and we'll go up
to my private office together.
I'll tell my staff
that you requested an interview.
Perfect.
I'll be right there.
I just ran a systems
check on the drone.
Sensors did pick up the missile,
but the drone didn't fire.
Why not?
I won't know until I have
a chance to take it apart.
I don't want to sound
like I'm covering my own ass.
But I did tell you
that the antimissile system
had not been tested
in an urban environment.
I know what you said, Arlo.
You just find out what went wrong
and you get back to me.
Mr. Hastings, I was right.
Someone hacked into the UN database.
They downloaded security protocols,
the schematics to the UN
and Hassan's personal itinerary.
I was able to trace an IP address.
- Did you get a name?
- Chloe's into the computer's registry.
She should have it by now.
- Almost there.
- Come on, Chloe.
Saying that isn't gonna make it
happen any faster.
There, the computer's owner
is listed as Meredith Michelle Reed.
She's a reporter working
for the New York Courier.
She's doing a profile on Hassan.
Applied for a security
clearance at the UN.
- Did she get it?
- My God...
She's there now. UN Security
logged her in 15 minutes ago.
- She's at the press conference.
- Put me through to UN Security.
You're clear. Go ahead.
Okay, go ahead.
This is Brian Hastings,
director of CTU.
We have a possible on-site
threat to President Hassan.
- Do you have an ID?
- Her name is Meredith Reed.
She has a press security clearance.
We're sending a photograph
to your PDA.
We just got a call
about a threat to President Hassan.
The UN gave us access
to their surveillance feed.
Facial recognition software is
sweeping the area now.
Got a match. Northeast corner,
moving toward Hassan.
Located the suspect.
She's ten yards from Hassan,
east side of the press section.
Green top,
black skirt, black jacket!
There she is.
- Everybody, move back!
- What are you doing?
I have clearance.
I'm a journalist! I'm a journalist.
I have credentials.
We got a call from CTU about a threat
to your life. Keep moving.
You're making a mistake.
The suspect's name is Meredith Reed.
She's a journalist profiling Hassan.
Our operating theory is that
she's been using her access to gain
security intel, which she's been
feeding to the assassin.
Ms. Reed is being transported
back here right now.
My hope is that she'll give us
the name of the assassin
so that we can put
an end to this threat.
Refer to your digital
briefing packets for specifics.
Mr. Hastings, I received
a preliminary report from the team
- sweeping Ms. Reed's apartment.
- And?
They recovered the files stolen
from the UN database off her laptop.
Looks like we found our insider.
They also found a file
that couldn't be opened.
It's been encrypted
with intelligence grade software.
- Find out what's inside that file.
- It's on its way over as we speak.
Excuse me, does anyone think
this happened too fast and too easily?
Things do happen faster in here
than what you're used to.
You keep reminding me.
I might not be up to speed
on all your software.
If someone doesn't want to be found,
they don't leave code fragments
that could lead to an IP address
Unless, they were in a hurry
and improvise.
Then why would you go through troubles
and leave a huge red flag?
You mean?
It's like someone
wanted us to find her.
I think we should continue to vet this
until we're sure that the right person.
We are vetting this
from every angle.
I appreciate.
We'll keep them in mind.
- In other words, "Shut up".
- He didn't say that.
- That's what I heard.
- You made your point.
Chloe, thanks.
Last thing.
Ms. Reed has spent a lot of time
on assignment in the Middle East.
Cross-check all of her movements
with those of known
terrorist groups.
Let's get moving.
Jack Bauer should be here
any second.
I want you to handle his debrief.
- You're taking me off the floor?
- You'll be better utilized
debriefing Mr. Bauer.
Go set up.
Thank you, sir.
I'm walking in.
Give me the home phone numbers
for Torres and Johnson.
Nobody speaks
to their wives before me.
Before you make your report,
keep something in mind.
- What's that?
- You asked for more boots on the ground
but what happened happened.
There's nothing we can do.
Put your opinion on record,
it's going to flag
an internal review from division.
It's only going
to hurt us moving forward.
Mr. Bauer, Brian Hastings.
- Sorry about the loss of your men.
- Thank you.
You'll be glad to know the lead
you got from Victor Aruz panned out.
- You've already found the insider?
- Her name's Meredith Reed, journalist.
She was covering the peace conference
and stealing files off the UN servers.
We wouldn't have gotten this far
without your help. Thank you.
Chloe O'Brian's waiting to debrief you.
Shouldn't take long.
I just need to make
a phone call first.
Excuse me.
We need to be on the same page here.
- I think you can understand that.
- You're asking me to lie.
I'm asking you
to exercise some discretion.
There's an assassin out there.
We don't need people
second-guessing how we do things.
Maybe you'd like to debrief for me.
- Let's get you in here.
- Hello.
Sweetheart, it's me.
Where are you?
CTU.
CTU? It's about
what's going on at the UN?
Yes, but I promise I won't be long.
I need to give them a statement.
But I'm going to have
to meet you at the airport.
Dad, what's going on?
It's complicated.
I'll explain you later.
- We're coming there to pick you up.
- You don't need to do that.
I want to. It's on the way.
Okay, I'll have Chloe
get you a security pass.
I'll see you soon. Bye.
Who was that?
- My father.
- Everything all right?
I'm not sure.
Everyone said you were too young,
and inexperienced to head up field ops,
but I believed you could do the job.
I need you to show the same faith
in me that I showed in you.
Keep our little dispute
off the record.
Where's Chloe?
She's upstairs.
First room to the right.
Thank you.
Think about what I said.
Sorry, but we got
to do this kind of quick.
You heard
about the reporter they arrested?
I think we might have the wrong person.
Meredith Reed could be innocent.
Hastings said they found evidence.
I know, but I think those files
may have been planted.
I've been scanning
through the traffic cam footage
from outside
Meredith Reed's apartment building.
Five minutes before the intrusion
into the UN server,
this man was going
into the service entrance.
Ten minutes later, he left.
What if he used her laptop
to break into the servers?
Sounds a little thin.
Don't you think we found her fast,
and that it was a little too easy?
Why are you showing me this
instead to Hastings?
He won't listen to me.
He might listen to you.
I'm here for my debrief.
Kim's on her way. I'm leaving
to Los Angeles with my family.
I'm just asking you to talk to him.
It'll take ten minutes.
If the assassin framed Reed
to create a diversion, that means
we have the wrong person in custody.
He still has someone
inside Hassan's delegation.
I'm sorry, Chloe, it's not my problem.
Let's just continue with the debrief.
Nor will they confirm
any fatalities.
There is no evidence at this time
to support the theory
that the two incidents are related.
We're waiting for an official statement
as to why this reporter was arrested.
At this time we can confirm
that her name is Meredith Reed...
I'm so glad you're all right.
I can't believe this happened.
It's hard to believe.
I just don't understand
how this woman got so close to you.
She's a journalist.
- She had security clearance.
- Do all reporters get these clearances?
But she's writing an article on me.
You know that.
- She was given special access.
- You gave her that access?
Yes, I did.
I did it.
This article was important for me.
I wanted to get my message
across to the American public.
- That's the only reason?
- Yes!
What other reason?
If you have something to say, say it.
You should never have
let her into our lives.
- You put us all in danger.
- Please, stop.
Excuse me.
I spoke to the UN press director.
We're going to make a public statement.
Make sure I see it first.
Omar, may I speak with you alone?
Excuse us.
They've taken Meredith Reed to CTU.
I can't believe she's part of this.
What reason could she have
to help someone kill me?
What reason does any American have
to do anything? Money.
They found incriminating files
on her computer, Omar.
Whether you want
to believe it or not, she is guilty.
And she's going to talk.
I need to know what she's going
to tell them about your relationship.
Be honest with me.
Tell me everything.
It started
three months ago in B'Dar.
We met for an interview,
in her hotel room.
Dalia and I
had been fighting that day.
She used you, Omar.
She almost cost you your life.
If this becomes public,
it will destroy your credibility
and that you've worked for.
I don't need you
to tell me the consequences.
If she talks to the Americans,
you must deny it.
It never happened.
Look, I know you're thinking
you must do the honorable thing
and confess the truth.
That would be a terrible mistake.
I need to be with my family.
- Yes?
- I just spoke with my brother.
I told him to deny the affair.
- What did he say?
- He's going to consider it.
Press him harder.
The reporter's claims
need to be discredited.
CTU needs to continue to think
she's my contact on the inside.
I understand.
We only need another hour.
I'll be ready to move by then.
Arlo.
I need you decrypting that file
they found on Reed's computer.
I broke off a section.
It should be on your screen.
- What filter to run it through?
- Esquire Nine.
No problem.
And Arlo,
you can stop staring at my breasts.
When are you going to drop
Captain America and find a real man?
I'm still thinking about it.
Well, don't take too long.
I might lose interest.
Let me know what you find.
Dana Walsh.
Hello?
I like that.
You picked a good name for yourself.
Better than the one
your mama picked for you.
Whoever this is,
I told you to stop calling me.
I know what you told me, Jenny.
My name is not Jenny.
You must be mistaking me
for someone else.
Am I?
- Yes.
- That's funny.
'Cause you sound like this girl
I used to know from Rock Springs
named Jenny Scott.
She was a wild thing.
We used to do some crazy stuff.
The next time you call me,
I promise you
I will contact the police.
I got a better idea.
Let's contact them right now.
- I'm hanging up now.
- Don't hang up this phone.
I'm warning you, Jenny, do not...
I was just going to look for you.
I'm so glad that you're okay.
I'm sorry,
that I have been so distant lately.
It's just...
I don't ever want to lose you.
Don't worry.
Why am I here?
This is a mistake.
- Damn it. Who's in charge here?
- Tell Mr. Weiss
there's nothing yet. I'll call him
as soon as we have news. Thanks.
Brian Hastings, director of CTU.
I don't know
who you people think you are.
But I want an attorney, and I demand
- to know what I'm being charged with.
- We found the files, Ms. Reed.
- What files?
- On your computer.
- You searched my apartment?
- We found six documents
on your laptop that were stolen
from the UN servers.
What documents?
Relating to the security arrangements
for the peace conference.
We know that you're part
of a plan to assassinate
President Hassan.
What? What?
Please don't waste my time.
The evidence against you is clear-cut.
Listen to me.
You're making a mistake.
If there are files on my computer,
then someone put them there.
Now you listen to me.
I'm giving you a chance
by telling us what you know.
I need the name of the assassin,
how to find them.
And we talk about you avoiding
the death penalty.
You're wrong.
You've got the wrong person.
Take her to interrogation.
Full biometric package.
I'll be there shortly.
Mr. Hastings?
You're done with your debrief?
Yeah. Can I talk to you?
Not a good time, Mr. Bauer.
Meredith Reed might be
telling you the truth.
Is this coming from O'Brian?
I told her to drop this.
She didn't.
She found this.
They were taken from traffic cams
near Ms. Reed's apartment.
Check out the time stamps.
This man entering
through the service entrance
almost 5 minutes before the intrusion
into the UN servers.
He left the building
almost immediately.
- So?
- Chloe talked to the building manager.
No scheduled maintenance today,
no packages delivered.
This is your evidence?
I'm looking at an apartment building,
where dozens of people live,
coming and going by day.
I understand. But is that it's possible
that someone broke into the apartment
and steal the documents.
Send a couple agents to check it out.
I'm sorry, I just don't see it.
I can't waste valuable resources
because Chloe O'Brian has a theory.
Chloe and I have worked together
for a long time.
And trust me. She's someone
you might want to listen to.
She's very good at what she does.
And if she's right, the assassin's
got you looking in the wrong place,
and you will get bit.
Mr. Bauer, I have a suspect in hand
with a file
she felt damning enough to encrypt.
That's where I focus my resources.
Now, if you will excuse me.
I hate this place.
He's not going to help, is he?
We have to follow this lead.
If they have the wrong person...
I did what you asked.
I talked to Hastings.
If he doesn't want to listen,
it's his mistake. It's not my problem.
To be honest,
it's not yours, either.
What about the threat against Hassan?
What about the peace conference?
- Doesn't any of that matter to you?
- If he knows something you don't?
I'm sorry.
Kim's waiting for me outside.
I've got to go.
You've come to me for help many times,
and I've never let you down.
You've asked me to do crazy things,
and I've always taken your side.
Please, help me.
I can't do this by myself.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Not this time.
Not me.
- Look what I made!
- Let me see.
That's Daddy. That's Mommy.
And that's me and that's you.
See? That's you, Grandpa.
It's beautiful, sweetheart.
Dad, we need to talk.
Why don't you get Daddy to put you
in the car seat? We're ready to go.
What's wrong?
I spoke to Chloe.
- She told me what's happening.
- Chloe called you?
No, I called her because you wouldn't
tell me what was going on,
so I decided to find out for myself.
I know about the threat
to the peace conference,
that CTU might have the wrong suspect.
What's happening?
Chloe had me make her case
to the head of CTU.
He wasn't convinced,
and he thinks he's got the right person.
But if he's wrong,
then there's still someone inside the UN
who's working with this assassin?
That's what Chloe thinks.
What do you think?
I think it's not my problem.
- Dad!
- What?
I don't believe you.
I've never known you to walk away
from something like this.
If you have to stay, it's all right.
You're not letting me down.
- I understand.
- Sweetheart, I want to go with you.
I know you do.
And there's nothing I want more
than for you to come with us.
I have been waiting so long
for this day.
We both have.
But if something terrible happens,
and you could have done something
to stop it,
I don't think you'd be able to
live with yourself.
Dad,
it's okay. You can go.
As soon as I'm finished here,
I will get on a plane
and I will be in L.A., I promise.
- Just be careful, please.
- Come here.
I will.
- I should tell Teri.
- No, no.
Let me do it.
Go ahead.
Go.
Go on.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine, but we should go.
Sweetie.
Grandpa has some work to do.
He can't fly with us.
- But he'll come as soon as he can.
- But he said he was coming today.
No, not today. But soon, okay?
All right, let's go.
We need to find out where he went
after he left Miss Reed's apartment.
Start checking traffic cams.
I need to get a baseline on her
respiratory, cardio and dermal response,
so make her comfortable.
Start off with a few softball questions.
I think we need a fresh start.
Now, you claim those files
were planted on your computer.
Fine. I'm willing to give you
the benefit of the doubt,
but you need to meet me halfway.
Talk to me.
Help me understand your side
of the story. Fair enough?
So, when was the first time
you met President Hassan?
About six months ago.
At a conference of oil ministers.
I requested an interview,
and he agreed.
We met in his hotel lobby twice.
Hour, hour and a half,
at the most.
I want to thank you for wanting to
continue our negotiations.
I know it's a risk.
You are no stranger to making personal
sacrifices for your beliefs.
If the price for peace is my life,
so be it.
We are doing everything in our power
to make sure that that doesn't happen.
We've tightened
security measures here,
and CTU's top priority is to find
the people who are targeting you.
I appreciate that.
The woman you took into custody...
- The reporter. Meredith Reed.
- Yes.
Is CTU certain
that she is part of this plan?
From what I understand,
the evidence against her
is quite incriminating.
Have they found out her reasons?
Miss Reed is being questioned
as we speak.
I'll make sure
whatever information we get from her
will be shared with your people
as soon as possible.
I've searched through
all the traffic cams
within a five-block radius
of Meredith's apartment.
There's no sign of
where the suspect went.
- Can you check other sources?
- CTU has drones all over the city.
I could look their archives
see if they picked anything up.
Where are they?
The archives are in Arlo's station.
I don't have the clearance.
Can you hack in?
Do it.
I'm glad you're here.
Thanks for staying.
This will all be over soon
and you can get to California.
Okay. I'm in.
One of the drones picked him up
leaving Reed's apartment.
Play it forward.
Well, he hailed a cab when he left.
- Can you track the cab?
- It's beyond the drone's search grid.
Okay, back it up.
Stop.
Move in closer.
There, that's what I want to see.
Closer.
See the medallion?
Call the cab, find out where it went.
I'm not tracking him without a weapon.
The Armory's on Level C.
I have to input your palm print
through the hand scanner.
Erase this as soon as I'm clear.
I'll call you
as soon as I'm on the road.
Hello?
Ruth, it's me.
- Jenny?
- I need to talk to you, are you alone?
Just my kid.
What's going on?
Haven't heard from you
since Christmas.
Kevin Wade found me.
He's been calling me
at work the last two days.
Damn it, Ruth,
you told him how to find me?
No, I didn't!
You're the only one
who knows the truth.
The only one who knows where I am.
I never talked to him.
I didn't know he was out of jail.
- Then how did he find me?
- I don't know!
And what does he want, anyway?
Why is he calling you?
He didn't say.
But he's threatening to tell everyone
the truth about me.
It'll destroy my career.
I'm about to get married, Ruth.
To a really great guy.
There's gotta be something you can do.
You can't let him ruin your life.
I don't know what to do.
I'm afraid
I'm gonna lose everything.
I gotta go, I'll call you later.
Where you been?
I've been trying to find you.
Did you decrypt the file?
I'm still working on it.
I found something weird, though.
Someone hacked into my station
and it came
from inside CTU.
- What were they doing?
- Scanning the drone archives.
Track it down,
see who it was.
And when you were in B'Dar,
profiling President Hassan,
were you ever approached by anyone
who was hostile to his regime?
No one paid you?
Pressured you into cooperating?
I said no.
So all you did was interview
President Hassan, that's it?
That's all.
Her answer prompted
a level-five autonomic reaction.
You're lying.
- I'm not. I...
- Tell me what really happened in B'Dar!
How is it connected
to the assassination plot?
I don't have anything to do
with any plan
to assassinate President Hassan.
- My God, why would I?
- Your reasons are irrelevant.
All I care about
is stopping the assassin.
So do I.
So if someone really
is trying to kill Hassan,
you need to stop wasting your time on me
and find them.
Mike, what's going on?
Maggie, I'm so sorry
for dropping by without calling first.
- Mind if I come in?
- Sure, come on.
Did Jim leave for work yet?
- Just got out of the shower.
- Good.
'Cause I need to ask him something.
Kind of a favor.
Babe?
Mike Farmer's here.
Says he needs to talk to you.
Mikey!
You're not on shift till tomorrow.
That's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
I'll be right down.
Take your time.
- Want coffee?
- Sure.
... during President Taylor's
press conference earlier.
I wouldn't want to speculate
at this time, Bob, but as you know,
President Taylor's
peace negotiations
with IRK president Omar Hassan
are highly controversial...
Sit down.
Thanks.
Did you hear
anything more about what happened?
Only what they're saying on TV.
I gotta tell you,
I'm so proud of you and Jim and...
all those boys down at the precinct.
You're gonna be part of history.
I don't know.
We're just directing traffic,
really.
You're on the UN security detail.
That's more than directing traffic.
You might even get on TV.
Wouldn't that be something.
It would!
Right.
I need to speak with Mr. Hastings.
- We're in session.
- It's important.
Excuse me,
I have Dana Walsh out here.
She says it's important.
You're not leaving this room...
until you tell me the truth.
No matter how long it takes.
I'm sorry,
but I didn't think that this could wait.
What's this about?
Jack Bauer.
I spoke with the dispatcher.
His driver logged the drop-off
at West 23rd Street
at the northwest corner
of Broadway in Queens.
Anything more specific?
An address?
No, but I'll keep sifting
through the aerial footage.
Broadway and West 23rd.
I'll call you when I get there.
Hands in the air!
Now!
Against the wall!
Don't move.
He had this.
We'll take it from here.
Stand down.
I told you to leave this alone.
Chloe tracked the man in the photo
to a second location.
We didn't think
you'd follow through.
So you steal
weapons from the armory.
Would you have followed through
if I'd asked?
I'm not debating.
You shut down a lead before you could
assess whether it was good or bad.
Take him to detention.
Take him!
Let's go.
I'm sure President Taylor
will be interested to find out
- what happened to my informant.
- Excuse me?
Cole tried to secure
that landing zone with more men,
but you sent a drone, which failed.
My informant
and two of your men are dead.
Cole hasn't said anything about it.
And neither will I,
as long as you let me pursue this.
So now you're blackmailing me?
You forced my hand,
now I'm forcing yours.
You don't want to this.
I wanna be on a plane to Los Angeles.
But you're not giving me another choice.
You want to waste your time
chasing ghosts? Knock yourself out.
I've got to stop an assassination plot.
Give him the bag.
I need Chloe to run ops.
Fine, she's all yours.
Thank you.
Anything to what he's talking about?
The only viable lead
is sitting in our interrogation room.
And she's the only way
we're going to get to the assassin.
What's going on?
Listen, something came up.
I can't make my shift tomorrow.
So, I was wondering if we could swap.
I'd be happy to, except Maggie and me
have a meeting with Sean's teacher.
She said he's acting out in class,
but I don't believe it.
Jim keeps making excuses for him,
but if he needs help,
I want to give it.
Where is he?
He's at his grandma's tonight.
I'm not making excuses.
So, what are you saying?
You can't trade shifts with me?
This is kind of important,
so I'm sorry.
Me, too.
I want you to sit down.
There's a roll of tape in my bag.
Tear off a strip
and put it over Maggie's mouth.
Do it.
I'm sorry, baby.
Now,
pick up the phone,
call Captain Ravello.
Tell him you're sick
and I'm filling in for you.
Now, listen, there's no way...
What's the matter with you?
What are you doing?!
Next time, I won't miss the bone.
Make...
the call.
All right.
All right, I'll call.
Please, just leave my wife alone,
all right?