Subtitles: Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu
Let's get cleaned up
before we head back to CTU.
I'm trying to locate an individual
by the name
of Kevin Wade.
Kevin's probation officer
just called me.
He has records that show him
calling my cell several times.
You have to handle this.
I don't know if I can do this.
Lie.
We both know you're good at it.
Put your hands where I can see them!
Do not move!
Marcos is out of the chamber.
Hang up and transmit the fail safe!
What's happening?
I don't know
if I could do this in time.
How will they smuggle the rods
into the city past the detectors?
Damn it, give me a name!
President Hassan's head of security,
Tarin Faroush.
Call U.N. security
and have them take Mr. Faroush
into custody until we get there.
- He's not here.
- Where is he?
Somewhere with my daughter.
Tarin is working
with your father's enemies.
You must tell me where you are.
The Teodore Hotel,
suite 514.
Just stay where you are.
The police will be there shortly.
We agreed
you weren't gonna take her calls.
I'm sorry,
I just didn't want her to worry.
- Did you tell her where we are?
- Of course not.
We're arriving at the landing now.
Soon we'll be able to transport
the rods into Manhattan.
- Are CTU's radiation sensors down?
- Not yet,
but we'll be ready.
Listen up!
This is what we know.
IRK nationalists are targeting
New York with a dirty bomb.
We have one lead:
Hassan's former head of security,
Tarin Faroush.
We believe he wants
to disable our defenses
so they can smuggle the bomb
into Manhattan.
Latest intel is that Tarin
is staying at the Teodore hotel
with president Hassan's daughter.
Kayla has been warned by her mother
that he's with the terrorists.
She'll be trying to keep him
at the hotel until our tac teams arrive.
What's our ETA on that?
NYPD is approaching the staging area,
CTU still ten minutes out.
Chloe, you liaise with NYPD.
Actually, Dana is better
at the inter-agency protocols than I am.
Fine.
Jack Bauer's heading field ops,
Dana's on point with NYPD,
Arlo will run aerial.
Let's get to it.
All the changes
going on around here,
who do I report to exactly,
you or Dana?
What does it matter?
- I just like to be clear.
- The only thing you need
to be clear about is that there's a bomb
about to go off in Manhattan,
so just do your job.
Drone's in position
over the Teodore hotel
awaiting your instructions.
Kayla, we have to go.
Nearly ready.
Are you all right?
It was nothing, I'm fine.
The Americans got Marcos to talk.
He may have compromised you.
Did the girl
receive any phone calls?
- One... Her mother.
- Get out now.
And bring her with you.
We're moving to the next phase.
- I'll need a vehicle.
- Hamid is on his way.
We must go now.
Just one more minute.
Hurry up, please.
I'm uploading Tarin Faroush's file
to you now.
Copy that.
We're gonna need hotel schematics
and access to their security systems.
Coming to you now.
Target is in room 514.
Hotel security is standing by
to give NYPD access.
Jack, Brian Hastings.
What's your ETA?
8 minutes. Can you patch me through
to our point man at NYPD?
We're doing that now.
Name's... sergeant Amis.
Sergeant Amis, Dana Walsh, CTU.
Been waiting on you, Ms. Walsh.
We're in our staging area already.
- Go ahead, Jack.
- Sergeant Amis, Jack Bauer.
Our target, Tarin Faroush,
is in room 514.
He has a female hostage,
Kayla Hassan.
She's the daughter
of president Hassan of the IRK.
We'll handle him. We'll make sure
that girl doesn't come to any harm.
The priority is to take Tarin alive.
He's our only lead to a major threat
- against New York.
- Like I said, we'll handle him.
Don't underestimate this man.
He was Hassan's head of security.
He knows what he's doing.
I want your men to set up a perimeter
and wait for us.
We're monitoring hotel security.
We'll tell you if we've got any action.
My friend from the state department
is waiting for us! We must go now.
One more second.
What are you doing?!
Stop this.
We walk out now.
- No, I'm not going anywhere.
- Just move!
Where are you taking me?
Believe me, the last thing I want to do
is hurt you, but I will.
- Got movement on the fifth floor.
- Are you getting this, Jack?
Someone must've tipped him off.
Sergeant?
Yes, I know, target's on the move.
I'm going in.
We're five minutes out.
Hold your position.
I'm on the ground, Mr. Bauer.
It's my call.
No, it isn't, this is a CTU operation.
I am telling you to hold your position.
I'm going in.
Tarin's at the elevators.
- Lost picture on the fifth.
- Sergeant,
target has taken out
elevator security camera and is armed.
I am ordering you to stand down.
- I'm right on him.
- Sergeant, that was an order!
Sergeant Amis, can you hear me?
- Chloe, have you got anything!?
- Nothing.
We have shots fired.
All NYPD units report status.
Repeat, report status.
This is Faulkner.
I'm hit.
- Amis and Martin are down.
- Where's the target?
He's heading toward the fire escape
on the south side. He's got the girl.
ESU, this is agent Ortiz.
Cover the south fire escape now!
Medics, men down on the fifth floor.
- That doesn't make sense.
- What do you mean?
Tarin just took out three men.
He should be heading down the stairs.
Son of a bitch.
NYPD,
target is impersonating an officer.
He has the girl.
Fall back and cover all exits.
I repeat,
target is impersonating an officer.
Cover all exits!
- Chloe, do you see anything?
- Nothing.
- Send us back the drone feed.
- Roger that.
Drop the gun!
Put it down!
Drop it now!
Target's at the Allen Street exit.
- He's got the girl.
- We need that drone feed.
Coming through.
There's a cab pulling up.
Officer Bellow, behind you!
- They're heading for the cab.
- All ESU,
we have two officers down
in the alley.
He's moving to Allen Street.
- He's escaping in the yellow cab.
- Tracking the cab.
Go!
Advise all NYPD mobile units,
we cannot lose that vehicle.
- On it.
- Taxi's in the delancey underpass.
- I'm blind. Do we have traffic cams?
- Not in the underpass.
We're two blocks from delancey.
- Any sign of the cab?
- Still in the underpass.
He's less than half a click.
Where the hell are they?
NYPD mobile units, 90 seconds out.
Go left, go left right here!
There it is. I got the cab.
Driver!
I want you to slowly open your door!
Open the door now!
It's empty.
Backtrack drone footage. Trace
every vehicle that left the underpass.
Get NYPD to set roadblocks.
They were here less than 30 s ago!
Got it.
- We should join the sweep.
- No, they're gone.
- You don't know that.
- Yeah, I do, they're gone.
I'm gonna need a kidnap
and an electronic intercept package.
- Have it meet me back at the UN.
- Copy.
I need to talk to president Hassan.
That's who they're gonna contact next.
That's why they kidnapped his daughter.
Tarin just called.
He has the girl.
Hello.
- Ahman.
- Samir, where are the rods?
They're still outside the city.
We haven't disabled
the radiological detectors yet.
Then how will you
bring the rods to me?
It's been taken care of.
We've backtracked through drone
and traffic cam footage.
Nothing's come up yet.
- What's Bauer's status?
- He's two minutes from the UN.
An electronic intercept team
is en route to him.
- Keep me informed.
- Copy.
There's a Mr. Prady here to see you.
Says he spoke to you on the phone.
Thank you.
Would you mind covering for me
for a few minutes?
A pleasure.
It'll be quieter in here.
This is...
This is some impressive facility.
What...
What is it you do here?
Intelligence analyst.
We've got a major situation...
I won't take up much of your time.
It's 3:00 in the morning,
you're 2,000 miles from home.
You mind telling me
what's so urgent?
It's about the young man
I mentioned on the phone...
This is him.
You know him, don't you?
I should have been
honest with you on the phone.
I met Kevin...
- a couple days ago at a bar.
- Was there another man with him?
He was traveling
with an ex-con named Nick Coughlin.
Bad news.
Done time on robbery,
attempted murder.
I've never seen him.
So, what happened...
With you and Kevin?
We talked for a while.
I drank more than I should,
- and we ended up back in his van.
- You had sex with him.
Do you know where he is now?
I didn't see him again.
- The whole thing was a mistake.
- Why so?
Because I am getting married...
in a few weeks.
It was the pressure.
I don't know.
All the wedding plans.
I went out for a drink.
I didn't intend to...
Maybe I did. I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore.
But if my fiancé finds out,
- he will never forgive me.
- I'm not looking to ruin your life.
I just want to retrieve Kevin
before he gets in more trouble
than violating his parole.
I understand.
I hope that you find him.
Thing is, Miss Walsh,
I got a call a couple hours ago
from my NYPD friend, Tom Hardiman.
Seems like there was... a break-in
at a police evidence lockup.
Again, bad business.
Officer got beaten up, left in a coma,
but guess whose prints
were on the assault weapon?
That nasty sob, Nick Coughlin.
Now,
what I'm afraid of is...
where Nick is, Kevin is, too,
and I really need to find him.
Like I told you,
I only saw him the once.
I have no idea where he is.
And you're sure about that?
We are in the middle
of a national security crisis.
I have to go back to my desk.
I'm sorry.
Perhaps, if I talk to your supervisor,
he could let you take
a few minutes off.
Or I could...
wait here,
stay out of your way
till you have some time.
Fine.
- You have to stay here, though.
- Of course.
I don't understand.
The Americans knew where Kayla was.
How did they lose her?
Before we blame them, remember...
It was our own people
who kidnapped Kayla,
not the Americans.
Mr. President, CTU is here.
I'm Jack Bauer.
You already know Cole Ortiz.
We deeply regret not being able
to find your daughter,
but I promise you,
we'll do everything to recover her.
How did you lose her?
How did that happen?
Tarin had been warned.
We arrived too late.
- It was your people...
- Please.
- What do they want with Kayla?
- We were hoping you could tell us, sir.
Faroush was your head of security,
so he knows everything you know.
He took your daughter
so he can leverage something from you.
Do you have any idea
what that could be?
I don't know.
We believe the kidnappers
will contact you directly.
We need to monitor your phones
so we can track their call.
Do what you need to do.
Just, please,
get our child back.
- Please.
- Thank you.
With me.
Set up tech here.
Tarin! Don't.
Please.
Don't.
Do what he says,
and you won't get hurt.
Who is he?
Another traitor?
The only traitor is your father.
Tie her up.
- Do you recognize the number?
- There isn't one.
A call
- coming in on the mother's cell phone.
- We're working on it.
Answer it.
Keep them on the phone
as long as possible.
Your husband is a traitor
to the people of the republic.
He alone has made our actions
necessary.
He cannot be trusted.
Where is my daughter?
I want to talk to her.
Whether you ever see her again
depends on
what your husband does right now.
Put him on.
- They want to talk to you.
- Give me the phone.
- We need to be hearing this.
- We're still working on it.
We've got it.
You should have audio.
This is president Hassan.
Who are you?
I'm a loyal servant of the republic
you are trying to destroy.
Now, shut up, Omar, and listen.
I want to talk to my daughter.
Let me tell you what I want.
File 33.
That is the price of your daughter.
I don't know what that is.
You had to say that.
Of course.
You're a vain man,
concerned about appearances,
and the Americans are listening.
But please...
Do not insult me
by saying this again.
I won't say anything
until I talk to my daughter.
Fine.
If that's what you want.
I'm sending you an IP address.
Give it to one of the people
listening in.
Got it.
Don't hurt her.
It's me you want.
I told you what I want.
File 33.
I told you...
I don't know what that is.
Take me instead.
You have 15 minutes.
No excuses, no stalling.
15 minutes or she dies here, like this,
- while you watch.
- Stop it.
Stop it!
I'll find the file.
Whatever it is, I'll get it for you!
What is file 33?
Brian Hastings is on the line.
You know anything about this file?
No, but I'm with president Hassan.
I'll put you on speaker.
- Go ahead.
- Mr. President, this is Brian Hastings.
I have no intel on that file.
Can you tell me what this is?
They gave you 15 minutes.
If you want to see your daughter again,
you don't have time to waste.
Omar, what is this file?
Show them.
Show them!
I'll do anything for Kayla.
- I would give my own life.
- Then give them this file.
Put it up on the screen,
mirror it over to CTU.
Are you seeing this?
Yes, I am.
This file appears to contain
operational details of all US.
Anti-nuclear defenses.
- That's correct.
- And our radiological detection arrays.
This is highly classified
D.O.D. material.
I need to know how you got this.
How do you think?
For 20 years,
your nation has threatened mine
with everything from economic sanctions
to military attack.
We gathered intelligence
and found weaknesses in your defenses.
We did...
what any other country would do.
That file shows the fatal flaws
of our nuclear detection capabilities.
If the terrorists were to get that,
they could smuggle
the fuel rods into Manhattan.
Surely you understand,
we cannot let you do that.
- A lot of human lives are at stake.
- What of my daughter?
What of her life?
With all due respect, madam,
your family brought this threat
to my country.
We're doing the best we can.
- You still on?
- We all are.
We may have a lead
on the daughter's location.
Arlo isolated a subway noise
from the video feed cross-referencing it
with the train positions
as of this moment.
There aren't a lot of trains,
especially within the radius
- they could've traveled to.
- They were heading southeast.
They've got to be near the F train stop
by the Williamsburg bridge.
Cole and I will head down there now.
We'll bring TAC from here.
- You need a second team?
- Yes, everything you've got.
Have your men ready
in 5 minutes. Right away.
- We're going to need you to stall them.
- How?
We'll set up a fake file.
They'll see through that.
Right now we need you to stall them
long enough to locate your daughter.
Any way you can,
- but make this work.
- We'll do whatever we have to.
Thank you.
- Please, don't...
- Why are you doing this?
- Please don't say anything more.
- Is there trouble?
- Why would there be?
What's the problem?
They'll never hand over that file.
- They have to.
- If they don't?
- Killing her was not part of the plan.
- You were willing to die
in Hassan's limousine earlier today.
- To do anything for our cause.
- I still am.
You assured me your feelings for her
would not get in the way.
So tell me,
do I need someone else?
Stay strong.
We're almost there.
What's the status
on our target area?
Still looking
at almost six square blocks.
- How far out are Jack and Cole?
- Six minutes.
We've got 30 seconds to find her
and to narrow this down.
- Where's the second TAC team?
- Leaving now.
Who is that?
Nobody.
This is a secure area.
Wait in holding or you have to leave.
I'm sorry.
I had a question.
I'm in the middle of a situation.
I don't have time.
I just got off the phone
with my NYPD friend.
He said I have to ask you
about the security cameras
at the police evidence lockup.
Because you know what?
It turns out
they malfunctioned
for the exact duration of the incident.
Somebody obviously
disabled the cameras.
But not Nick and Kevin.
A crowbar is about as high-tech
as those two get.
That's what I wanted to talk to you.
See, I'm thinking
that someone must have helped them.
Now, my friend says
that all the raw video
from every government facility
feeds right here into CTU.
That right?
- Yes.
- He also said...
Correct me if I'm wrong...
That the digital images are archived
every eight hours,
and metadata...
Is that what it's called?
That allows you to trace
the exact source
of any service outage.
Everything I need to solve this
is right here.
You can get it for me, right?
We don't just give data
to people off the street.
Now, that's right.
You need, an IDRAN...
An interagency data request
authorization number.
Hardiman gave me one of those.
He said everything should fit
on a 100-gig thumb drive.
So is that going to be a problem,
getting that for me?
Good.
They reprocessed the subway noise,
managed to narrow down the grid.
- How big?
- About 12 buildings total.
Apartments, offices, retail.
It's still too much ground to cover.
It's over.
I'm not sure I heard you.
The parole officer looking for Kevin
is here at CTU.
Knows about the robbery,
the cameras, everything.
Are you sure?
He's after the raw feeds.
He's got an interagency request.
I'm going to give it to him.
I'm sorry to call you.
I just thought that you should know.
- Why don't you wait?
- Do you hear me?
He knows.
He'll go to Hastings.
Don't do anything.
We'll talk about it when I get back.
I can't wait.
You'll get in more trouble
trying to protect me.
I can't let that happen.
I love you, Cole.
You got a problem?
'cause I need you
to keep your head in this.
You got it.
We're running out of time.
The technicians have...
prepared the file I'll be sending.
But these people who have Kayla...
They won't believe a fake file.
But they might believe you.
You have a gift, Omar.
When you talk, people listen.
You need to convince them,
for our daughter.
Say whatever you need to
to buy time.
I have seen you move so many people.
You can do this.
I know it.
I'm sorry.
It's time.
It's the deadline.
Your father has not responded.
You hate him that much,
you would do this to me?
I don't want to die.
Please.
Then let us pray for once your father
does the right thing.
Tarin, you can't let them do this.
I know you.
This is not you.
And I know in my heart
that you love me.
In my heart I know.
And so I don't understand why...
Nearly there, sir.
The uplink's ready.
Let's go.
Stop them!
Wait.
Follow me.
This way.
My father will help us.
He's surrounded by traitors.
We have to get to CTU.
Here, the number is in this cell phone.
Call them.
What has happened to her?
Did the Americans stop the call?
I don't know.
Maybe they were afraid
we'd hand over the real file.
They could have gotten
our daughter killed.
Why aren't we seeing anything?
We're not sure.
Arlo's been scanning the source.
Four minutes ago there was a spike.
- Like a gunshot.
- Did Jack hear anything?
He's still a quarter of a mile out.
You better take this.
Kayla Hassan,
- she's in a car, she's escaped.
- What?
Brian Hastings, director of CTU.
- You all right?
- I'm not all right.
I'm driving.
They might be chasing me,
I don't know.
- Where are you?
- I don't know!
Track her cell phone, patch Jack in.
We're tracking your phone.
Do not turn it off.
- Just tell us what happened.
- They tried to kill me,
but Tarin got me out.
He found a car, but they caught us.
They shot him.
He's dead.
He told me to call CTU,
that it was the only safe place.
My name is Jack Bauer.
We need to know
where you were being held.
I don't know.
I know you've been through
a great ordeal,
but please, this is very important.
Can you try to remember
what the building looked like?
It was dark, and it was empty.
It had a vault, like a bank,
but abandoned.
- Chloe, you get that?
- Got it.
You need to tell my father
that Tarin Faroush helped me escape,
that he sacrificed his life for me.
We've the location.
Republic Commerce Bank,
9621 East Broadway.
It closed a year ago.
It's the only bank on the grid.
We'll need drone support,
and send a second team over.
We got 'em.
We've got you
on First Avenue and East Fifth.
Continue going straight,
I will tell you when to turn.
Cover this exit.
Send the second team down.
Cole, you're with me.
Let's take the door.
Chloe, it's Jack.
We're in the basement of the bank.
There's some kind of tunnel system.
I've got the schematics,
I'm seeing it now.
We're going to head down a spur
southeast from the vault.
- How many exit points?
- Two exits...
No, three.
Have the drone cover
all the exit points.
I'm sending you my screen now.
Can you get eyes on the exits?
Ascending to 5,000.
I got movement at the south exit.
I've got four hostiles
approaching Division Street on foot,
heading northeast.
You copy?
Cole, they double-backed up top.
We're moving to intercept.
Where's Kayla?
Approaching the tunnel entrance,
she'll be with us in two minutes.
Security is standing by.
Good work, people.
- Good work.
- Thank you, sir.
If you'll excuse me
for a few minutes...
Targets are heading north
on Orchard.
They're getting into an SUV.
Do you copy?
- Stay with them, we'll follow.
- Owen, King, you're coming with us.
You take King's vehicle,
you two double-back around Orchard.
I've got a shot
for facial recognition.
Send it to me.
It's Tarin Faroush.
He's supposed to be dead.
Kayla said they shot him.
You did the right thing, Tarin.
I know.
She will die for a good cause.
Jack, Cole, come in.
Go ahead.
We ID'd one of the targets.
It's Tarin Faroush.
Kayla said he sacrificed himself
to save her, but he's still alive.
Are you absolutely sure?
What the hell's going on?
They wanted a file
they knew we would never give them.
They never expected us to.
- You got to put Hastings on now.
- I'm on, Jack.
You cannot let Kayla Hassan in.
The terrorists faked her escape.
- They wanted to get her to CTU.
- For what purpose?
What's the best way to disarm
New York's radiological defenses?
Taking out CTU.
There must be something in the car,
some kind of a bomb.
You need to stop her now.
Where is she?
She's in the tunnel.
Security!
Dana, with me!
The car that Tarin got into,
where is it now?
Crossing into Brooklyn,
taking the first exit
off the Williamsburg Bridge.
We cannot lose it,
do you understand me?
Copy.
Stop the car!
Put your hands
where we can see them!
Dana, call the bomb squad!
Get out of the car!
Take her.
Bomb squad to the tunnel entrance.
- Get her away.
- Have you stopped that car?
Not in time, Jack.
Hold on, just hold on.
It's an EMP.
It's an EMP!
Shut down your systems
to protect the drones.
There's no time.
- Get away from the car!
- I can move it.
Come on, get out of there!
Get out of there!
Can you hear me?
Those drones are our only way
of tracking down those terrorists.
You need to pass them off
to the NSA.
Damn it, we're blind.
Chloe, did you cop...
What the hell is happening?
We need to contact NSA.
The terrorists just took out CTU.