Subtitles: Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu (V 1.00)
Vladimir attacked you, you defended
yourself. That's what happened.
- I don't know.
- I do.
If anybody else ask you questions,
I'll be right there to answer them.
You were implying something about Dana,
I want to know what it is.
I think she went to meet some guy.
- Take a look.
- You think you can find her?
You promise me I do this thing for you,
and then you'll leave me alone.
That's not gonna happen.
It's a sweet operation
that we got going here.
You getting the access codes,
- and us pulling the jobs.
- You can't do this to me.
You know who I am?
All I know is that there's a man
in the Russian syndicate
who's been trafficking
weapons-grade uranium.
- Who do you work for?
- I'm not at liberty to say.
Work on him,
until he's ready to talk.
It's over, you know that, right?
You want to know where the rods are?
I will tell you.
But I want full immunity.
- Command, are you seeing this?
- Where the hell are the rods?
We picked up trace radiation signatures.
The rods were here.
I told you, they were there.
- I had two of my men guarding them.
- We found their bodies, both shot.
I wasn't sure I believed
that you would betray your father.
You were upset,
now I've gotten them for you.
- When will you get here?
- Less than five minutes.
Just have my money ready.
- CTU. O'Brian.
- It's Jack.
Do you have Hastings there?
- Are you ready to trace the call?
- Yes.
As soon as Bazhaev gets his son
on phone, we can begin to triangulate.
Okay, hold on.
Farhad, where are you?
You're late.
It's me, your father.
Don't hang up. Stay on the line.
Please.
I know you have the rods.
- I wanted you to know.
- The police know, too.
- They're here.
- You told the police?
Of course not.
It was Vladimir's buyer...
he's a Federal agent.
Just so we're up front,
I'm here with your father.
I'm Jack Bauer. I work with CTU.
Do what you want.
I don't care.
Maybe you don't but your father
cares about you.
He negotiated immunity for you.
All you need to do
is bring the fuel rods in,
and you can put the rest behind you.
It's the only way you'll be safe.
Safe? Did my father tell you
about my other brother?
- What he did to him?
- Oleg was dying, you know that.
We could have saved him.
He would be alive
if not for your precious deal.
You are right,
maybe you are right, I don't know,
but... that doesn't bring Oleg back,
and I cannot bear
to lose another son.
Don't worry about me.
- I'll be fine.
- No, you won't be.
You won't be anything.
It's over.
Federal agents are here
going through everything.
The entire city is under guard.
If you don't bring the rods in,
they will hunt you down.
They will kill you.
I won't be able to protect you.
I don't want to see you hurt.
If I hand over the rods,
how does this work?
Tell us where you are,
we'll bring you in.
Just like that?
After everything we've done?
Yes, I told you...
They have given us immunity.
Please, Josef, please.
This is your last chance.
Are you there?
- Yes, I'm here.
- You need to bring him in now,
before Farhad gets there.
Did you hear that?
You need to move.
I'm on my way.
I'll call you
to let you know where to meet me.
Careful.
- Sounded like shots fired.
- You need to help him!
- Where is he?!
- I don't know.
Did you get a trace on that call?
It looks like he was in central Queens
near Flushing Meadow Park.
I want units combing that area.
Bring your suspect back to CTU.
Copy that.
Get him ready for transport now.
Is he dead?
We need to hurry.
The boat is waiting for us at the port.
- The port may not be the right thing.
- What do you mean?
The authorities know.
We need a new plan.
Did you get that?
Yes. We're trying to get
an I.D. off the voice print.
So far, no luck
locking down a location.
Copy that.
We're on our way back now.
Hurry.
Take the van and get the rods...
We've got a match for the voice
at the end of the call... Farhad Hassan.
So, he got his fuel rods.
Any I.D. on the other man weeard?
No, sir.
Mr. Hastings, Rob Weiss for you.
Tell him I'll be right with him.
Give me an ETA on Bazhaev.
- Yes, sir.
- Start the interrogation
as soon as he gets here.
Jack, it's Chloe.
Hastings wants your ETA.
- He's anxious to interrogate Bazhaev.
- I'm about 15 minutes out.
But I wouldn't count
on getting anything from him.
If he could have told me how to get
to them, he would have.
Jack, I heard about
what you went through.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Thanks.
How's Renee?
Pretty worried about you.
They've still got her in medical.
- Could you patch me through to her?
- Hold on.
Rene, I have Jack.
How are you?
- I'm fine. What about you?
- We had a line on the fuel rods.
We lost it.
- What's the plan now?
- It's Hastings' call.
I'm bringing the prisoner,
then I'm out.
They ask you about what happened,
about Vladimir?
- Yes, Chloe did.
- Chloe did the debrief?
I mean...
I wouldn't really call it a debrief.
We talked...
mostly and...
- I wrote a statement.
- You explained it was self-defense?
- Like we agreed.
- That's how it happened.
You've got to stick with that.
Yeah, I'm gonna try.
I know this is hard for you,
but you did nothing wrong,
you need to start believing that.
I don't know how to say this,
so I'm just gonna say it,
I need to make sure
that I'm not misunderstanding...
- When you say that I "have you"...
- I meant it like it sounded.
What do we do now?
We'll figure it out.
I'll be in in 15 min.
- Rob, it's Brian.
- I got a flash from your office
how the immunity
the president authorized played out.
It's not good.
Really not.
Now, as I understand it, Bazhaev's son
swiped the rods before we got there.
- That's correct.
- And now the son is dead.
- Do we know who has the rods now?
- Apparently, it's Farhad Hassan.
- And where is he?
- We're looking.
Meaning you have no idea.
I pushed the president
to resurrect CTU with you at the helm.
Now, you tell me you can do the job,
I believe you.
- I can do the job
- Good to ear it.
When things
get this colossally screwed up,
people look for someone to blame.
- So what are you saying?
- I don't want that person to be you.
I put you there, you're my guy.
If you fail, I fail.
And that cannot happen.
Are we on the same page?
What have you got in mind?
She killed one of our main leads,
that's correct?
He was a psychopath.
- She was defending herself.
- She stabbed him 15 times.
- Are you saying it was murder?
- That's for lawyers to decide.
She put her life on the line
when she didn't have to.
- I'm sure that will weigh in her favor.
- You know what a conviction would mean.
- She'd go away for years.
- Someone has to pay for this.
So you tell me,
who do you want that to be?
I'm sending someone over from Justice.
Kristin Smith.
She'll take care of everything.
What do you need from me?
Just open the door
and get out of the way.
We did a sweep, sir.
No trace of any hazardous materials.
- Fine. Finish up, get back to base.
- Yes, sir.
- Find Dana yet?
- I think so.
I'm tracking her phone.
Send them to my PDA.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
There could be a reasonable
- explanation...
- You stuck your nose in all this.
Just do it.
- Coordinates are on your phone.
- Thanks.
- I'm sending everyone back to CTU.
- What are you going to do?
I'll be there within the hour.
If Hastings asks,
just tell him
I'm following up a lead.
I know Dana means a lot to you,
but do you really think
- this is worth going AWOL over?
- She's my fiancee, Arlo.
Jim, I'm taking your vehicle.
Find Owen,
have him take SWAT back to CTU.
- Say I'll be right behind them.
- No problem, sir.
Is Dana back yet?
I don't think so.
Do you need her for something?
Do I need her for something?
Yes, Arlo,
she's my chief data analyst.
I need her to do her job.
You track her down,
and you let me know when you find her.
Kristin Smith
from the Justice Department is here.
Thank you.
- Rob Weiss brief you?
- Yes,
I have to interview Renee Walker.
I read her statement.
Did it appear to you
that she's guilty of murder?
Mr. Weiss warned me
you might have issues with this.
With hanging a brave woman out to dry?
Yes, I do.
There are major discrepancies between
her statement and the forensic evidence.
All I'm asking her to do
is to set the record straight.
I feel it would be prudent
to restrict
- surveillance access to this interview.
- Fine.
I would also like a video record of it
in the event of legal proceedings.
Can I ask you to provide that?
Right this way, please.
This is a transcript
of your statement.
You should review it
before you sign it.
- How far out did Jack say he was?
- 15 minutes.
This is Kristin Smith from Justice.
She needs to talk to Renee,
- if you'll excuse us, Chloe.
- Talk to her about what?
Now.
Thank you.
What's she talk to her?
She was about to sign her statement.
- I already debriefed her.
- She needs to fill in details.
- I already did it.
- I know that you protect her.
- I respect that.
- Than let me sit in.
Why?
Was your debrief
not a full and honest?
We've nuclear materials
in the hands of terrorists.
I need you back at your desk
focused on that.
Yes, sir.
Where are we?
A staging area.
It belongs to a businessman
who supports us.
I don't want to delay too long.
We need to find another way
to get the rods out of the country.
You heard what the American said
to Bazhaev's son.
- They know what we doing.
- So we need to move quickly.
The Americans are not stupid.
If we go near any airfield
or harbor now,
the radiological detectors
will spot us.
Who are they?
These are men I've recruited.
- Our men.
- What are they doing here?
To unload the rods.
We need to get rid of the van.
And then what?
You should rest.
I don't need to rest.
I need to know what we're doing.
We can't get the rods
out of the country.
Let's use them.
Use them?
How?
As a weapon.
A radiological bomb.
We'll show the Americans
how strong we are.
Show them?
Are you out of your mind?
If we use the rods against them,
they will destroy our country.
They'll bomb us, invade.
And if we do nothing,
they'll do it anyway.
That's what this peace treaty
with your brother is all about.
They're trying to turn us
into another corrupt,
Mid-East regime
with your brother as dictator,
kept in power by American guns
and money.
Isn't that
what we came together to prevent?
Is there no other way?
America will always be our enemy.
Remember...
even a giant can be toppled
by a single stone.
We need to make them fear us.
I'm with you.
You said in your statement
that you killed Vladimir Laitanan
in self-defense.
Is that correct?
Yes, it's in my statement.
What I didn't see was any mention
of your history with Laitanan.
You did have a history.
I worked an undercover operation
with the FBI.
Laitanan was the target.
During the course of that operation,
you had to get close to him.
He became obsessed with you.
He tried to rape you.
But you were able to stop him.
I fought him.
Put me in the hospital
with two broken ribs.
That's in there, too.
You were able
to fight off a stronger, violent man.
It's impressive.
But this time when he attacked you,
you didn't fight him off.
I couldn't.
His hands around my neck
trying to strangle me.
I understand.
You thought
he was going to kill you.
You were in fear.
What happened next?
He was choking me.
I stabbed him.
In self-defense?
You stabbed him in self-defense...
15 times.
The first blow alone
could have stopped him,
but you didn't stop.
Look at me, Renee.
You were an investigator for the FBI.
One of the best they had.
Put yourself
on my side of the table.
Look at what I'm looking at.
There's a dead body.
On the one hand,
you saying you acted in self-defense.
On the other, I have these.
Evidence of a sustained
and furious assault
with clear intent to kill.
As an investigator, you know
which version is true, don't you?
I acted in self-defense.
Let me tell you
what I think happened.
You used an operation
of unparalleled importance
to seek revenge
against a target without any regard
- for the final outcome.
- He attacked me first.
I'm well aware of your sacrifice
in service to this country,
but I do not think
that it is fair or right
that CTU should be taken down
because you used this operation
to seek out your own vendetta
against Laitanan.
I looked at your file.
This isn't the first time
you lost control.
You almost killed
Alan Wilson.
That's why you got fired
by the FBI, isn't it?
I can see what this is doing to you.
It is tearing you up inside.
Let it out.
Tell me the truth.
You killed Laitanan
because the thought of him
touching you again was intolerable.
Do the right thing here.
That's what happened, isn't it?
Is that right?
Put him into holding.
- No phone calls.
- I would like to see my son's body.
We haven't found him.
- What's wrong?
- It's about Renee.
She's being questioned again.
- You already completed the debrief.
- I did. Hastings ordered it.
He called in some woman
from the Justice Department.
- Where's Renee now?
- She's in medical.
Can you get eyes in that room?
He cut off all access.
What is going on?
They're setting her up to take the fall
for the failure of this mission.
Sorry. No one's...
They're setting you up.
Don't say nothing.
- Too late.
- What you're doing?
Get out of here.
How dare you?
After everything she sacrificed.
After everything she's lost.
Have you no decency?
This is over.
Hands in the air.
Do it now!
You better put that down
or you're going to get hurt.
It's all right.
Go.
Hands in the air.
Do you have what you need
to turn the rods into a bomb?
We're gathering materials.
Must be difficult
at such short notice.
Explosives, no.
Detonator?
We're working on it.
I might know somebody.
A professor in the city.
With expertise in electronics.
- You sure he can be trusted?
- Yes.
He will help.
He will do whatever I ask.
But still...
I will bring this up very carefully.
I need to talk to him in private.
Very well.
There's a phone in the office.
Ali will take you.
What is the target?
Is that decided?
So many targets in New York.
It will be hard to choose.
It was Farhad.
He escaped.
Find him!
Now!
Cuffs off.
Give us the room.
Sit down.
I'll stand.
This is the new CTU.
You hang your own.
If you mean Renee Walker,
we're asking some questions.
- Standard procedure.
- It's a debrief, which completed.
But instead, you've got some hack
from Justice trying to initiate
- a criminal prosecution.
- We're establish the facts.
You're trying to save your ass.
I was there when you askeher
for her help.
And she gave it to you,
and we acquired the target.
This is how you pay her back.
I'm not going to let you do this.
- I'll call the White House first.
- They knows.
Rob Weiss sent that woman.
Maybe I wasn't clear.
I'd call the president.
Good luck, I think the president
takes murder pretty seriously.
My recollection?
She prosecuted her own daughter.
I'm not asking.
Sit down.
- Sorry.
- We're busy.
I've got Farhad Hassan on the line.
The voice prints match.
- Can you tell where he is?
- No. He's on a secure line.
Can I just put him through?
Mr. Hassan.
This is Brian Hastings,
director of CTU.
There are people chasing me.
- They've the rods.
- I thought you had the rods.
No more.
They turned against me.
They have their own plan...
an attack on New York.
An attack on New York?
When, exactly?
Soon.
Very soon.
- Who are these people?
- IRK operatives working in USA.
I need names.
Just get me out of here.
I'll tell you everything I know.
We'll get you out.
I give you my word.
Now, where are you?
Forest Hills.
Some kind of boat warehouse.
Hurry. I'm injured.
- They're hunting me.
- Hold on and keep this line open.
- What do you want?
- Pinpoint his location and get me Cole.
- I can't.
- What do you mean?
His team came back.
He didn't.
Owen said he was following a lead.
All right. Get me Owen.
Tell him he's going to be leading.
- Owen? Are you sure?
- Just do it, Chloe.
They'll take you down
and process you.
I want you out of this building.
Fine.
Come on.
What's the hurry?
Your friend's a total freak show.
I know, but come on.
Don't go.
I'll make it up to you.
At least let me give you
a ride back into town.
We'll walk.
Night, ladies!
- Gonna take a leak.
- All right.
Why are you here?
You're asking me that?
We're in an operation. You can't leave.
I can explain.
You can explain later.
Right now,
I'm taking you back to CTU.
We can deal with this
- after we secure the materials.
- It's not what you think.
- What do I think?
- I am not sleeping with him.
Save it.
I saw the pictures.
What pictures?
Get in.
- I am not leaving!
- Why the hell not?
Because if I leave,
this will never end.
What will never end?
- You do not understand.
- Then make me understand, damn it!
I can't.
Try.
We don't have a lot of time.
So you better start talking.
My name is not Dana Walsh.
It's Jenny Scott.
- You find Farhad?
- Still looking.
I injured him badly.
He won't get far.
We don't know
who he might have contacted.
I'll be traveling with the rods
to a secure location.
Do you want me to come in?
You stay here,
and you find him.
It's a six-acre warehouse complex
in Forest Hills.
Farhad is in one of these buildings.
The rods must be there, too.
Drones are airborne,
but they won't have eyes for 12 minutes.
- And the police?
- They're redirecting their resources,
but it's a big area,
it's gonna take a while to cordon off.
You wanted to see me, sir?
In the absence of Agent Ortiz,
I assume you're ready
to take charge of the operation.
- Three units standing by.
- All right. I'll walk you out.
- There's a lot of pressure on you.
- I can handle it, sir.
Talk me through it.
What's the attack grid?
Our working theory's that the materials
are still in the proximity of Farhad.
Teams Alpha and Bravo are tasked
with locating and securing the rods.
- What about Team Charlie?
- They're responsible for the evac.
A standard urban search-and-rescue...
we're in, we're out.
Nothing standard about it.
Wait here.
You've got something to say.
Think about it.
The people that are chasing Farhad
know they've got a big security problem,
so by the time your men get there,
those fuel rods will be long gone.
You're down
to one team covering Farhad?
- What if they run into resistance?
- What if they do?
At that point, you shoot
at people with a intel value
than the man you'll save.
Agent Owen knows the priority
is to take all hostiles alive.
Under fire?
No assignment's more difficult.
Agent Owen has my full confidence.
If that were true,
you wouldn't be talking to me.
You offering to bring in Farhad?
If you drop the criminal investigation
against Renee Walker.
Look,
I know you don't want to prosecute her.
I can be your out.
I hear what you're saying,
but I can't help you, Jack.
I've sat in that chair before.
The chair you're sitting in now.
I know what it's like.
There's a lot of demands on you,
many of them unreasonable.
But the people that last here,
the ones that mattered...
they knew when to say no.
It's the White House,
you don't say no.
You are the head of CTU...
you have more juice than you think.
Especially
with a nuclear weapon in play.
If we do this, Jack,
it's not for one rescue operation.
It's still this whole thing
is over and done.
You want Renee freed up,
you're not in and out anymore.
I want you in with both feet.
Deal.
I found an NYPD evidence warehouse
in Queens
with $120,000
from a drug bust just sitting there.
It was only a matter of getting them
in and out between patrols.
Wait,
you actually committed a robbery?
Put yourself in my place, Cole.
Kevin was going to tell Hastings
I'm a convicted felon.
He was going to ruin my life.
What would you have done?
Not this.
Kevin promised...
that if I went along,
he would never bother me again.
Let me guess.
He didn't keep
his end of the bargain.
That's why you're here, isn't it?
What do you mean?
What's in your hand?
- You were going to kill them.
- I don't know.
You were going to shoot them
in cold blood.
Cole, listen to me.
I was wrong.
I see that now, but I was scared.
I thought
that I was doing this for us.
For us? Are you crazy?
I love you, Cole.
Don't say another word.
Not one more word.
Cole, where are you going?
Stay in the truck.
Cole, don't do this.
Please, I am begging you.
This is my problem, not yours.
Stay back.
What?
Go for it.
I have to deal with one of you.
You got the wrong address.
Do I?
I don't think so.
- You should tell us what you want.
- Shut up and listen.
Come on.
Let's just get out of here.
I thought you looked familiar.
Looky here, Nick.
It's soldier boy.
No kidding.
You know,
it's a shame that you and I
can't go grab a beer sometime.
You know, just the two of us.
I'm sure
we'd have a lot to talk about.
I said shut up.
The way I see it,
you guys have two choices.
One:
you go back to prison for grand larceny
and aggravated assault.
I go back to prison,
she goes back to prison.
I think
she's prepared to live with that.
Choice number two:
I let you walk.
You keep your 100 grand...
or what's left of it...
and you go back
to wherever it is you came from.
That's it?
That's it.
But if I ever see you
in this city again...
if I even hear about you
crossing the state line,
I'll skip the formalities
and kill you myself.
Do we have a deal or not?
We got a deal.
Better be sure.
I don't want to see
either one of you ever again.
- What are you doing?
- Going after him.
Why?
We get rid of him,
we're right back in business with her.
Come on, man.
We got what we came for.
We got more.
Now, let's just...
let's not push our luck.
All right?
Come on, all right?
We're just getting started.
We're done.
You got me?
What you did back there,
- I'll never forget it.
- Let's just get back to CTU.
Cole, I'm serious.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have come back.