Subtitles:
Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu (V 1.00)
President Hassan's forces are still
cracking down on the opposition.
They're not showing any signs
of letting up.
The rumors have already started
that the British are pulling
out as signatories to the accord.
Assemble the representatives.
I want to appeal to them myself
to stay the course.
One of the suspects
has family connections
to a member of our delegation
here at the UN.
Who?
Jamot.
Are you arresting me?
I want to speak
with President Hassan.
He is the one who gave this order.
- What's wrong? You sound upset.
- We must talk about your father.
I have to go to the embassy.
I'll meet you after.
This has the address and schematic
of the evidence lockup.
This keycard will get you access.
- How do we find the money?
- The evidence bins are numbered.
Do exactly what I tell you to do,
and no one will know you're there.
The authorities know
about the nuclear material.
Putting Oleg in a clinic
would lead them right to us.
No doctors.
The doctor said
that Oleg could be treated.
He showed me how.
Who are you to question my judgment?
Never disobey
an order from your father.
I'm sorry, my son.
Tell me about this buyer.
His name is Ernst Meier,
German arms dealer.
- What's he looking to buy?
- Weapons-grade uranium.
I have to meet this Meier,
and I need a good-faith
payment up front.
I'm not going to tell you again.
Leave me alone and let me get dressed.
Damn it, come here
or the deal's off.
That's right.
Where is the $5 million?
The money is in your account.
Drop the weapon. Now!
You think
you can roll me for $5 million?
Let me talk to him.
Bring him here.
He wants to see you.
Get up.
Thank you so much.
That went well.
Unanimous support for the treaty.
Nearly unanimous, anyway.
I have the distinct impression
that I am running out of goodwill.
Maybe, but you bought yourself
some breathing room.
These people are already up
past their bedtimes.
We won't be hearing any more grousing
until tomorrow morning at the earliest.
Congratulations, Madam President.
- Thank you, I appreciated your support.
- Good.
Now I hope you'll explain to me
what's really going on.
I thought I did.
You invoked national security,
which is not an explanation.
It's saying "Don't ask".
Our countries
have a unique relationship
based on a trust
developed over nearly a century.
Anything you say to me
is in the strictest confidence.
You may tell
your prime minister and no one else
that President Hassan's crackdown
isn't just a response
to the attempt on his life.
There are unsecured
nuclear materials in play.
Apparently a faction
inside his country
was disturbed
by the prospect of disarmament,
they decided to take matters
into their hands.
- Where are the materials?
- Here on our soil.
CTU is running
an undercover operation
to retrieve them as we speak.
Who is that?
My guess is, it is my backup.
No calls till we get to Vladimir.
Does this look like a situation
where you get to make demands?
It's Meier.
I lost my sight line on you.
I'm leaving the building.
- I understand.
- Everything okay?
The money's been transferred.
- We'll soon be at his office.
- I'll follow with a backup team.
- That might not be necessary.
- After what they just pulled,
you're sure you're comfortable
without backup?
There are other considerations.
- You mean they have Renee.
- That's right.
We'll stay back.
I'll let you know.
What was that?
- Let him know what?
- Shut up and drive.
I got 'em on traffic cam.
Is everything okay?
Jack seems to be in control.
Looks fine, all things considered.
Driver looks a little worried.
Who is this guy anyway?
Do I pass him on to facial recognition?
I've got to take this.
Yeah, sure, no biggie.
Just unsecured nuclear materials.
We're there,
outside the evidence building.
You're in the side alley, right?
We parked out front so everyone
can see us. What do you think?
I need to walk you
through this step by step.
- I know, we're ready.
- I need you to hang on
for a few minutes.
Here?
We're kind of exposed, Jenny.
You'll be fine
if you just stay still.
We have 30 minutes
before the next security pass.
I will be with you the second I can.
Arlo, Hastings wants us in his office
for a field update.
Can I ask you
a hypothetical question?
If it's about Dana,
it's not hypothetical.
If your fiancée was cheating on you,
would you want to know?
Hypothetically, who'd be asking...
some creepy stalker about to get fired?
I'm serious.
So am I. Just go upstairs.
It's none of your business.
Cole just called.
Jack's almost to Laitanan.
Hastings wants us in his office.
Pass me back the keys.
Slowly get out,
put your hands on the roof.
Let's go.
So this is how you do business?
I wire you the $5 million
like we agreed,
and then you try and take me out.
I did not think you were for real.
It was a misunderstanding,
but it's past.
We are here.
As an act of good faith, Vladimir has
already started calling his contacts,
inquiring
about the nuclear materials.
I don't care what he's done.
- I want to talk to you.
- So talk.
I want to talk
to my partner alone...
now.
Look, he's upset,
understandably.
It will be fine.
Yeah?
This is our chance.
We should take him out now.
We need him to do this deal.
Don't risk everything for a whore.
You ever talk about her
like that again,
I'll kill you.
You understand?
- What the hell are you doing?
- I have authorization to pull you out.
No, that's not possible.
You've taken us this far,
I'll finish it.
Jack, you can't.
He doesn't trust you, first of all.
The only reason he's agreeing
to continue this is me. I'm fine,
really.
You want to make calls, let's go.
You don't have a say in this.
I am pulling you out.
No, look, it's not a big deal.
I know what he did to you
six years ago,
- and it is a big deal.
- If we stop this now,
then everything that I have done
is for nothing.
We're running out of time.
Let's go.
We're almost there,
it'll be worth it.
Are you there?
I thought you forgot about us.
I wish I could.
Don't be like that.
Are we good to go?
Yes, move now.
Let's go.
There's a security panel
next to the door.
Use the keycard I gave you. The code
is 1668.
1668.
Keep moving,
it will stop in a second.
If you want the $120,000 you will be
out of there in less than 20 minutes.
Which door is it?
It's the last one on the left.
The code is 4...
... 660.
It's like Christmas...
with chain link.
Okay, how do we find the money?
It's in section 3101.
It's down the aisle on your left.
The code is 28...
... 24.
The last one on the left.
3101... do you see it?
- What the hell?
- What the hell is going on?
What number is it?
Is it 3101?
3101... this is 3110.
- Come on.
- What is wrong with you two?
It's called a mistake.
Back off.
So where is it?
3101 is down the aisle on the left.
- Down here, down here.
- The code is 2824.
Bin number's 4301.
4301.
Man, it's too many numbers.
Boom! Got it!
That's beautiful, man.
That's beautiful.
Just shut up and get out of there.
The next patrol
is in less than 15 minutes.
You've got the money.
Close the doors and leave.
- 15 minutes. We're leaving.
- Call me when you're clear.
I sure will, Jenny.
Let's go!
Not yet.
Check out some of this stuff.
Seriously, come on, man.
Patrol's on its way.
Yeah, 15 minutes.
Are you sure, then?
You haven't heard of anyone
dealing in these materials?
All right.
Thank you for your time.
I'm sorry to trouble you.
Nothing. They did not appreciate
being called so late.
Renee, cut me some bread.
You might want to ease up.
You've got some calls to make.
I drink what I want.
Where's the bread?
Coming.
Drink.
What is this?
It is too thin.
It should be thick.
Nice and thick.
There we are.
She's changed, you know?
Six years ago,
she thought she was too good for me.
Now, she is much more friendly.
Maybe I should thank you.
All that time you were together
in Mexico City.
I see how you look at her.
- Didn't you?
- Keep talking, but do it on the phone.
Otherwise,
the nuclear materials will be gone,
and this deal will be dead.
Fine, but I don't like
you rushing me.
Get him out of here.
And I'm running out of my vodka.
Go get me some more.
Sit down.
I won't be long.
My younger son.
I wanted to bury him, Father Gregor.
Of course,
but that will take a time.
The cemetery workers
- need to prepare the grave...
- You'll do it now
out back.
My men will dig his grave.
Sergei Petrovich,
- this isn't right.
- Then make it right.
Like a soldier
who died on the battlefield
and must be buried there.
Is that how he died?
In battle?
You just make it right.
Say all the prayers.
Where I end up, I don't care.
But this boy is with the angels.
My men will be with you soon.
Leave us.
Get up.
Look at me, Josef.
Understand that everything I've done,
I've done for you
and for our family.
You killed my brother.
Because I loved him,
because I couldn't bear
to see him suffer,
because there was no other way.
There's always another way.
Not when we are dealing
with nuclear materials.
We cannot take no risk.
You know that.
You don't know why I'm doing this?
Because when I die,
I want to leave you
and your family a worthy inheritance.
Wealth,
respect,
consequence.
Can you understand that?
One day you will.
As your son grows older, you will.
And you will understand
how much I love you.
My only son.
Father Gregor is here to bury Oleg.
Will you help him?
He's my brother.
Thank you.
Call when you are ready.
What is it?
Vladimir Laitanan.
He says it's important.
What do you want?
Sergei Petrovich.
I apologize for calling you
out of the blue like this, sir.
- Your family is well?
- I said, what do you want?
I have a business proposition.
Then call me in business time.
This can't wait.
I hear there are materials for sale,
expensive materials, dangerous ones.
What materials?
Nuclear rods.
Highly enriched uranium.
So what?
If anyone has the organization
to pull off such a deal, it's you.
- I'm flattered.
- I have a buyer here,
a German.
He's willing to pay
a great deal of money for them.
- Double any offer you have.
- Then he is as stupid as you are.
Are you out of your mind?
Nobody deals in nuclear rods,
nobody.
I'm sorry.
A misunderstanding.
Don't call me again.
There will be no deal.
Then we call the next person.
You're not listening.
He says nobody sells these things.
Nobody.
You're close
to the biggest deal of your life.
He's just jealous
that he's not in on it.
Come here.
Later.
Once you've made more calls.
Come on.
We have a problem.
Vladimir Laitanan knows
about the fuel rods.
What are you going to do?
Mr. President, it's Allison Taylor.
We were scheduled
to resume our discussions.
I'm late, I know. I apologize.
The events of this evening...
This events make it
more important than ever
that we complete
our work on this treaty.
I need to know your intentions.
My intentions?
The crackdown on your countrymen.
You've even arrested
one of your own delegation.
That's an internal matter.
No, it is not.
I assured delegates
from two dozen countries
that you were still
our best hope for peace.
I personally guaranteed them
you'd observe
the letter and spirit
of this agreement we're signing.
And I will.
Do I have your word?
Within the next few hours,
the arrests will stop.
I'm taking measures to assure that.
And the delegate
you've taken into custody?
Will be released or charged.
You have my word.
Thank you.
How he sounded?
Not like himself.
Did he talk?
No, sir.
Jamot denies
all knowledge of the plot.
How forceful was the interrogation?
Very.
I did it myself.
I don't believe he's involved.
You know Jamot has connections
with the extremists.
A cousin in the opposition party.
That's all.
If he won't talk,
we have to force the issue.
He has a family back home,
is that correct?
A boy, nine.
A girl, seven.
Have the Security Services
arrest them.
Apply whatever pressure's necessary
to make Jamot talk.
A problem?
I do.
You rallied us on the promise
that you would put an end
to such tactics.
I'll do everything humanly possible
to find your brother but,
do not ask me to violate
the principles that you and I
both stand for.
Thank you.
With my wife gone, I've no one
to speak the truth to me anymore.
Check everyone's computer
and phone records again.
- See to it that nothing was overlooked.
- Of course.
Let's go.
Nabeel can stay
and pack up these files.
Forget it.
Call the Security Services
and have them round up
Jamot's family as I asked.
I don't understand.
You just told Tarin...
I gave you a direct order.
You obey it or not?
- I'll call Security Services.
- Good.
And find Tarin's records
in that mess.
He might have his own reasons
for not wanting Jamot to talk.
Come on. A patrol will be soon here.
- Give me the money.
- What?
The money, dumbass!
- We're going to split this.
- I ain't gonna ask you again.
Serious?
Bitch! Knock it off!
Come on, let's go!
Jackass!
I told you we should've gone!
Such an idiot.
I received a call
from the hazmat lab at Fort Hamilton.
They've analyzed the traces of uranium
found on Hassan's assassin.
- Did they identify where it came from?
- Sample's too small to be precise,
but the uranium is of Soviet origin.
They're recalibrating their tests.
Great. Keep me informed.
- Kevin, are you out of there?
- No, not exactly.
What?
You told me you left there
20 min ago.
We didn't.
Okay, now somebody's here.
Idiot!
Fine, all right, just hurry.
Somebody's in the hallway.
I can't believe you let this happen.
If you get caught, I am dead.
We all are.
All right,
so just find us a way out of here.
Hang on.
Stay calm.
It's a cop.
He's in the hallway
right outside the room you're in.
There's another exit.
In the corner right behind you.
Come on!
My God, what have you done?
Damn it! It's locked!
He's coming inside right now.
You're going to have
to slip past him,
go out the door you came in.
Control, this is ten post 11.
I'm at the warehouse...
No!
Kevin, stop him!
Come on, come on.
He called it in.
We gotta go!
Come on!
- Kevin, stop him!
- Come on.
We'll call you when we're clear!
Are you all right?
When did you get back?
Just now.
May I come in?
What is it?
It's only me here.
It's safe.
What's wrong?
Your father
has had many people arrested,
including Jamot.
Now he's having Jamot's wife
and two children detained back home,
so they can be used
to force him to talk.
- There must be a mistake.
- He gave the order himself.
I thought I'd convinced him not to,
but he was lying to me,
he went behind my back.
Kayla, your father is a great man.
I respect him
more than anyone I have ever known.
But Farhad's betrayal
has changed him.
What can we do?
Open up, please.
- What are they doing here?
- I don't know.
Open up.
Tarin, stay here.
- Yes, Nabeel?
- Miss Kayla,
we've been looking everywhere for Tarin.
Have you seen him?
Is there some problem?
- What do you think you're doing?
- We have orders.
I said he wasn't here.
- I'm sorry, but I don't believe you.
- You can't just barge in here!
I need to talk to my father!
You need guards
to come looking for me?
The president says
you may be involved with his brother.
Based on what?
Nothing.
Only that I would not allow
an innocent family to be tortured.
He's ordered me to detain you.
I have no choice.
You do have a choice.
Tell my father he's made a mistake,
that there's no one
more loyal than Tarin.
It's insane and you know it.
Don't make this worse, please.
Don't you see? My hands are tied.
Let me talk to my father.
He's given orders
not to be disturbed.
Even by you.
I'll talk to him!
I'll get him to change his mind!
I understand, Roman.
We'll do business some other time.
That's it.
Last one. He also knows nothing
about nuclear rods.
He also said
it's suicide to deal in them.
Meier has wasted our time.
Meier's intel is good. We need to think.
Who else can we call?
I've called everyone
who could possibly deal in these things.
One of them has to know something
- Renee, it's done.
- Maybe they don't want to admit it.
Maybe they don't know
how serious you are. Call them back.
- No.
- Tell them that you have the money.
Shut up!
Just because I like your face doesn't
mean I have to put up with your crap.
We made $5 million.
A good night's work.
Why settle for 5
when we can have 50?
When did you get so greedy?
$5 million is plenty.
Plus we have each other,
that's not too bad.
It's not bad.
But it could be better.
Call them again.
Do it for me.
I said no.
Come on, push them harder.
- Somebody knows something.
- What is your problem?
There's no one left to call.
Now you tell Meier to leave, okay.
I'm not telling him anything!
- What?
- Not until you try again.
- It's over! What is wrong with you?
- I need this deal.
That is why you're here? The deal?
Why else?
Do you think I'm here for you?
Get up.
Stop! Stop!
It's all right. It's all right.
It's over.
It's okay.
Laitanan contacted everyone he thought
might have information on the rods.
No one responded.
That's when he said he was finished.
Renee kept pushing him,
and it got ugly.
Laitanan's dead.
- He attacked her.
- And so, what, you took him out?
No, she did.
She did?
Half an hour earlier,
she was having sex with the guy.
How does that even happen?
- What, she lose it?
- She was defending herself.
We knew he was violent
before we even went in.
- He's violent? He's dead on the floor.
- Yes, he is.
Wwe still don't have
the nuclear materials secured,
- so I suggest we move on.
- Move on?
He was our only lead, Jack.
Where do we move on to?
We can working
the phone calls that he made.
There's physical files
and a computer to go through.
Cole, are you getting this?
We're en route from the staging area,
five minutes out.
We need forensics
to rip this place apart.
Bennett can coordinate
till the full team arrives.
Do what you can.
And bring Laitanan's body
back here for autopsy.
I want to know what happened.
Any other good news?
- Excuse me?
- I said, anything else?
We'll see you when you get here.
Our entire operation
just went south.
You think you could
show a little interest?
Pull it together!
You didn't have to do that.
Do what?
Cover for me with Hastings.
All I did was tell him the truth.
When they see Vladimir,
they'll know what happened.
What do you think happened?
It's like you said.
I couldn't handle it.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
It's not.
I could have killed you.
I've made such a mess of everything.
I just thought that if...
if I did this,
I could make it all right.
I could have my life back.
You can have your life back
any time you want.
You just need to want it.
How?
I've tried, and I don't know how.
I don't...
I don't have anything, anyone.
You've got me.
Look at me.
I didn't want it to end like this.
I know.
Look, we're a lot farther ahead
than we were three hours ago.
Every call Laitanan made
is a solid lead
that we can follow up,
because of you.
You did your part.
Now let CTU do their job.
Please?
Let me take you home.
They must have been moving.
CTU's here already.
Listen to me. This is really important.
He attacked you, you defended yourself.
That's what happened.
- I don't know.
- I do,
and if anybody wants
to ask you questions,
I'll be there to answer them.
Let me go talk to them.
They're Russian. Vladimir must
have contacted whoever's got the rods.
They just didn't want him to know.
Hold on to this.
What are you doing?
I need to let them take me.
We have to get out.
You want everything
you've done so far to matter?
I need to do this.
Tell CTU to tracking me from the air.
They'll lead us
to things we're looking for.
They will kill you.
They'll have to vet me,
find out how much I know.
It should buy us enough time.
Hide in here.
Take this.
If this door opens again,
you start shooting.
Don't shoot!
Please!
I'm opening the door.
I'm unarmed.
See?
Both my hands.
No problem.
I'm unarmed.
Don't shoot.
What happened?
- What happened?
- They tried to rip me off.
But you and I, we can do business.
Wait!
Don't shoot.
If you kill me,
you're gonna cost your boss money.
Who else is with you?
No one.
Everybody else is dead.
All I want is business.
Mikhail!
Hansen, upload to CTU.
Site is secured.
Video's coming through.
Three bodies.
Are you getting?
Yes, we are.
- Any sign of Jack or Renee?
- No, sir.
I'm here.
Here.
It's Renee, sir.
She's alive.
Where's Jack?
The Russians took him.
The ones
that have the nuclear materials.
How?
We've been monitoring.
No vehicles left.
I don't know.
They just suddenly appeared, but...
Jack let himself be taken.
He said that you'd be monitoring him
from the air.
We haven't seen anything.
Our drones have been overhead
all the time.
They saw nothing.
Where is he?
We don't know.
Step up.