Subtitles: Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu
Can I assume there is no change
in the status of president Hassan?
I'm afraid not.
Then he is still being
held by terrorists.
If Hassan dies,
- there is no treaty.
- If I didn't know better,
I'd think you were hoping
for that to happen.
Jack thinks that someone inside
of CTU is working for the terrorists.
Jack recovered Tarin's phone.
If someone did call and tip him off,
we can get the number off the memory.
It's Dana's.
I spoke to Hastings.
He cleared me through.
Stay where you are
and keep your hands...
She entered the parking garage.
The only reason
you've got any leverage right now
is because Hassan is alive.
So stop screwing with me!
They are gonna force him
to make a statement,
and then they will kill him.
Just read the statement, Omar.
You will renounce
the peace agreement.
I will never do that.
He's stronger than we thought.
Bury him.
I will tell the world of his crimes.
This man is not our president!
Looks like Samir's grabbed him.
We need you to get in there!
I have a visual on Hassan.
Ready to engage.
I'm sorry.
I have Jack Bauer
on the line for you.
Put him through.
Madam president,
I don't know what to say
except that I'm sorry.
I trust there was nothing
you and your team
could have done differently.
President Hassan was dead
before we even got there.
Then you don't owe me an apology.
I failed you, ma'am.
It was Hassan's choice
to surrender himself
in order to save American lives.
It was out of your hands.
Don't put this responsibility
on yourself.
You need to keep
this peace agreement alive.
There can't be any agreement
when the IRK is without a leader.
The hardliners there
will take advantage of the vacuum
and reverse all the progress
we made with Hassan.
I'm gonna have
to address the delegates
in a few minutes and announce
the dissolution of the peace summit,
and formally release them.
If you give up, it means they win.
I don't see another choice, Jack.
I wish to god I did.
Good-bye, Jack.
- What's his condition?
- He took a round to the shoulder,
another through the abdomen,
but it exited clean. BP looks steady.
We need this guy for questioning.
Will he make it or not?
Doesn't look like any vitals were hit.
He'll live.
We'll transport him back to CTU.
Medical will take him for now.
President Taylor is going to announce
the end of the peace conference.
- You did everything you could.
- It wasn't enough.
We should get back to CTU.
Why?
The fuel rods have been recovered.
The peace conference is over.
Everybody who was responsible
is either dead or in custody.
How's Samir?
Still unconscious,
but the EMTs say he'll make it.
Stay with him.
I'm handing over complete authority
and responsibility
for his transport to you.
Are you heading back to CTU?
We're going home. We're done.
Hastings is still gonna want
to debrief both of you.
I'm sure he will.
He knows how to find me.
I'm sorry it ended up like this.
Me, too.
You're a good agent. I wouldn't be
standing here without you.
I hope everything works out.
I'll pack my kit up downstairs.
The delegates are assembled
in the lounge, as you requested.
Let's get this over with.
... discontinue the peace summit
that was to be
a cornerstone of her administration.
President Hassan apparently
had been kidnapped earlier,
- and then taken to...
- Jamot.
On behalf of my country,
you have our deepest sympathy
for this terrible tragedy.
Though, on a personal level,
I imagine
you have mixed feelings right now.
Beg your pardon?
Hassan had you arrested without cause
during his purge of suspected enemies.
Allowed you to be
brutally interrogated.
I would think
you have little love for the man.
President Hassan
was under tremendous duress,
and he lost his way,
but I never stopped
believing in what he stood for.
Of course.
I meant no offense.
I'm sure you didn't.
Excuse me.
Minister Jamot.
If you can spare a few moments,
I need to speak with you.
I will be happy to sit down with you
after I have addressed the delegations.
I know you're intending to announce
the end of the peace summit,
but there may be a way
to prevent that from happening.
Before you do anything,
I need you to hear
what I have to say.
All right.
- Ma'am, what about the delegates?
- Just give me a moment.
- Let's go in here.
- Please.
Samir's men were all dead,
thanks to the Americans.
Samir was the only one left,
but I took care of him.
So, there's no connection to us?
We're in the clear?
Maybe not.
There was a woman there
who might have recognized me.
What woman?
She may be CTU...
I'm not sure... But...
I've seen her face before.
Where?
Six years ago,
when we were using that mobster,
Vladimir Laitanan,
to smuggle military weapons
out of the country,
she was with him.
Are you sure it was her?
I don't forget faces.
Where is she now?
In a taxicab,
just ahead of me, with Jack Bauer.
Are they going to CTU?
I don't think so, no.
Then, it seems unlikely
she recognized you.
Better not to take the chance.
I'll take out Bauer, too,
while I'm at it.
The Americans believe the IRK
were solely behind the recent attacks.
Killing Bauer and this woman
would only alert them
to the fact that others
were involved.
How long before they discover
that it was us?
It will take even less time
if this woman remembers me.
What are my orders?
Continue to follow them...
Keep them in sight...
And I'll get back to you.
I don't have the words
to tell you and Kayla
how sorry I am.
I know you did
everything in your power.
Jamot, I wasn't aware
that you were here.
I only arrived a short time ago.
I want you to know that,
in our last few hours together,
Omar expressed his regrets to me,
not the least of which
was his treatment of you.
I appreciate that.
I realize our timing is intrusive,
but there's something
we need to discuss privately.
Did you find him?
The man who killed my father?
Samir Mehran.
He was badly wounded,
but he'll live to stand trial.
And, believe me,
he would pay dearly for what he's done.
Kayla, darling,
I need to speak
with president Taylor alone.
Give us a few minutes.
What is it
that you wish to talk to me?
As you know,
for almost a year, your husband and I
worked to make
this peace agreement a reality.
In that time,
I saw the kind of leader he was.
He managed against difficult odds
to bring a fractious and contentious
parliament together.
Now that he's gone,
your country is going
to be thrown into turmoil.
I am aware of the challenges
that we are facing.
Why are you telling me this?
Clearly, someone needs
to take the reigns
of the IRK government.
Someone who believes
in the same ideals
and principles as Omar Hassan,
and who shares his strength.
Minister Jamot believes
that person should be you.
What?
I'm not the only one who believes it.
I've spoken to our delegation,
as well as with the other members
of our cabinet back home.
You represent our best.
Our only real chance
to preserve our government
and your husband's agenda.
You are out of your mind!
I am no politician.
But you are a martyr's wife.
And history has proven
that to be something far more powerful.
You have always been popular
with the people.
The vast majority of them
want peace.
They'll rally around you.
The council of guardian
will have no choice
but to recognize you
as successor to the presidency.
But I have a choice.
You assume too much of me.
I realize
that this is a lot to consider,
especially now
while you're grieving,
but without a unifying figure
to hold your country together,
everything your husband worked for,
will be for nothing.
My marriage to Omar
was far from perfect.
We had many problems
for a very long time.
I know only too well,
how difficult it is for a marriage
to survive a life in politics.
But through it all,
I never stopped loving him.
Or sharing his desire
for better relations with the west.
If it is the will of my people
and of my government,
I will take my husband's place
at the peace conference.
It will be my honor
to stand with you.
We'll make the announcement together
from the United Nations.
Thank you.
- She's going to do it.
- That's incredible news.
I want every delegate
contacted personally.
Tell them to cancel any plans
to leave the country.
We are returning to the UN.
I'll also call CTU
and implement those changes
if you still agree.
That's your decision.
Do what you think is best.
Where's Bauer?
He left the scene,
took Renee with him.
Hassan's death hit him pretty hard.
Samir's been taken to medical.
- Is he conscious?
- Barely.
Let me know
when he's ready for questioning.
All right.
Put him through.
This is Tim Woods
with homeland security.
I'll put you through
to Mr. Hastings.
Actually, I'm calling
to speak with you.
Me? Are you sure?
I know this is unusual,
so I'll get straight to the point.
President Taylor and the dignitaries
are returning to the UN
where she'll announce her intent
to move forward with the signing
of the agreement.
Excuse me, but how can she do that
without Hassan?
I'm not at liberty to say just yet,
but our immediate concern
is whether CTU is capable
of handling security
for the rest of the process.
It's already been infiltrated,
compromised more than once today.
We cannot have any more mistakes.
Are you suggesting
I'm responsible for those mistakes?
On the contrary.
I reviewed the hourly reports,
you've made some astute calls,
and have proven
to be very resourceful.
Why are you calling me?
I'm relieving Brian Hastings
of his post effective immediately.
We're now in the process
of suitable candidates to replace him,
but until we find someone,
you'll have provisional command.
You're putting me in charge?
For the time being.
I know your record at CTU,
L.A. branch,
and how important you were
during the Sangala crisis.
Nobody in that building
has more experience.
This is a mistake. What happened
with Hassan, and everything else.
It wasn't Mr. Hastings' fault.
I don't have time
to debate this with you.
Division feels
you are the most qualified, and I agree.
My decision's made.
Now accept it, and let's move on.
Does Mr. Hastings know?
Division's informing him
as we speak.
Just try to make the transition
as quick and painless as possible.
I'll be in touch.
Come in.
I want you to know, I don't think
it's fair what they're doing,
laying all the blame on you.
Everything that happens here
is my responsibility.
The successes and the failures.
I recruited Dana Walsh
into this agency,
I let the snake into the garden.
I need to review protocols with you.
Let's not waste any time.
- Did you live here long?
- Just during my recovery.
I still think
I got some coffee around here.
What's her name, your granddaughter?
Teri.
Kim named her after her mom.
Listen,
I know that we've said
a lot of things to each other,
and you've made promises
to me about...
I want you to know
that I'm not gonna hold you to them.
It's been a terrible day,
and I know that we say things,
I don't want you to...
Hello?
Somebody there?
Take my briefcase to marine one,
and tell the secret service
I'll be ready to leave shortly.
And send Mr. Novakovich in.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Novakovich.
Thank you for seeing me.
Not at all.
What can I do for you?
I just had a curious phone call
from Tim Woods
indicating that you are intending
to move forward
with the peace initiative
with the IRK.
- That's correct.
- May I ask
how you propose to do this,
considering their leader is dead?
I intended to answer that question
during my address to the assembly,
but since you're asking...
Dalia Hassan will be signing
the agreement in her husband's stead.
That's... an interesting idea,
madam president,
but I don't see how she would have
the authority to sign such a document.
She's getting it
from her government now.
Their parliament called
an emergency session
to ratify her
as provisional president.
The letter confirming that
is forthcoming.
Madam president,
I appreciate your optimism,
but I don't understand how you can
believe that installing Hassan's widow
as some kind of figurehead
will alleviate our concerns
about the instability
of the IRK government.
With president Hassan dead,
the opposition
will only get stronger.
Hassan's death
will galvanize his supporters
and every advocate
of this peace process
to endorse her as his successor.
You can't be certain of that.
Once again, Mr. Novakovich,
you're giving every indication
that Russia has no interest
in this peace accord.
I'm sorry that you feel that way,
but the fact remains
that we are no longer confident
that any meaningful progress
can be made.
Respectfully,
my country will be declining
to sign your peace document.
Excuse me.
Do I need to take this up
with president Suvarov myself?
If you like, but I can assure you,
I have full authority
on this matter.
Any decision that I make
represents the formal position
of the Russian government.
Good day.
Agent Peters,
I need to see secretary Kanin now.
Liberty's on the move.
We managed to clear a blockage
in one of your coronary arteries,
and the x-rays show the heart damage
to be less than we expected.
In other words,
I'm a tough son of a bitch.
You're a lucky man,
I'll say that for you.
So I can resume my duties.
Although the procedure
was noninvasive,
take it easy for a little while.
That isn't a no.
Hello, Ethan.
How are you feeling?
I've seen better days.
Would you give us
a few moments, please?
Thank you.
You heard about Hassan?
Tim Woods told me.
He also filled me in on the IRK plan
to install Dalia Hassan.
What do you think?
Her family's well connected
and powerful.
It's an inspired idea.
Well, the Russians don't.
Novakovich told me in no uncertain terms
they won't accept her.
They're using it as an excuse
to pull out of the signing.
Even if the IRK has a new leader,
the peace agreement won't stand
without Moscow's endorsement.
I need your help, Ethan.
You got the Russians to the table.
What can I do to keep them there?
There may be someone
who can help us here.
But you're not gonna like it.
Who?
Charles Logan.
Logan?
Ethan, you can't be serious.
The man's a criminal.
I don't care if he was pardoned.
I didn't agree
with Daniels' decision, either,
but the fact is he's left
several messages at my office
over the past hour.
Apparently, he's aware
of the Russian reticence
in signing the agreement.
He's offered his assistance.
How could he possibly know
about this?
Despite his political downfall,
he's managed to maintain
a uniquely close relationship
with Moscow.
His messages indicated he has
information which might prove useful
in keeping the Russians
at the table.
What information?
He didn't say.
Allison...
I don't trust this man
any more than you do,
but I'd be remiss if I didn't urge you
to at least... hear him out.
Listen up.
I've never been very good
at good-byes.
But I want to tell you
what an honor it's been
for me to have served
with each and every one of you.
Division is now vetting names
to replace me.
In the meantime, Chloe O'Brian
will be in charge,
and I'm sure you will show her
the same loyalty and commitment
that you've all shown me.
Thank you.
Don't worry, Chloe, you can do this.
I hope so.
I just want say,
we had a rough start,
but I eventually really enjoyed
working for you.
I'm happy to say
that I was wrong about you.
If I had listened to you
in the beginning,
maybe things
would have been different.
I doubt it.
I'll be at division debriefing.
But I'm available
if you have any questions.
Thank you, sir.
Good luck.
Mr. Hastings.
I have agent Ortiz on the line.
They have a situation in medical.
This one's all yours, Chloe.
Ms. O'Brian.
- It's Chloe.
- Where's Hastings?
He's not here.
What happened?
Samir's just gone
into cardiac arrest.
Four milligrams epinephrine
and 275 lidocaine.
I'll be right there.
Clear!
Going again at 360.
I thought that was not serious.
So did I.
Where is Hastings?
- He's been removed by division.
- Who's in command?
I am.
Until they find a replacement.
You were with Samir?
From the scene, yes.
What about at the scene?
He may have been out of my sight.
Emergency personnel were with him.
We got to move his body
for an autopsy.
Not yet.
Order a preliminary toxicology panel.
- They'll run a full panel.
- I want it now!
He was barely conscious.
He couldn't have taken something off.
Somebody could've given it to him.
Do what she says.
I'll be in Hastings' office...
My office.
Let me know when you find something.
A few of the more conservative members
of our delegation
may continue to resist you.
But...
we can persuade them.
Perhaps if I spoke
to them personally.
A very good idea.
Miss Kayla,
I didn't get a chance to tell you
how deeply sorry I am.
Thank you.
I will see you both back at the UN.
The UN?
I thought you were going home.
Not yet.
There are new developments.
I'll explain them to you on the way.
What is going on?
Why did President Taylor and Jamot
want to speak with you alone?
They have asked me
to consider staying on...
to complete your father's work.
I don't understand.
What does that mean?
Our party wishes to appoint me
as the new President.
What was your answer?
You told them you couldn't accept,
not after what's happened.
Our country
is on the verge of a coup
by the people responsible
for the murder of your father.
Someone must lead.
You can't beat them,
don't you realize that by now?
I don't believe that, I won't.
The greatest blow I can strike
against them is to sign the agreement.
- This will be your father's legacy.
- It will be a death sentence for you!
You want peace to live,
but all these people want is anarchy.
They'll kill you!
Enough!
You are not the only one
who has suffered today.
This was not
an easy decision for me,
but it was mine to make.
I don't need you
to remind me of the danger.
I need you to help me be strong.
Now, pull yourself together.
There is a car waiting for us.
I'm sure the media
does want a response, but I'm not ready
to give them one just yet.
They'll have to wait.
All right.
Thank you.
The press secretary says the Russians
are leaking to the news channels
their intention to reluctantly
pull out of the talks.
They don't like wasting time.
Has my guest arrived?
I had secret service bring him
and deliver him discreetly
to conference room number three,
as you asked.
Thank you.
Let me convey my condolences
on the loss of President Hassan.
I know you worked closely with him.
This must be very hard for you.
Thank you, for your sympathy.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to talk to you alone.
This is my executive assistant,
Jason Pillar.
I assure you he can be trusted.
Forgive me if I don't give much weight
to your endorsement.
He needs to leave.
Will you excuse us?
Let's get something straight.
I agreed to this meeting
only at the behest of secretary Kanin.
Now, I'm not sure
you're entirely aware of the situation.
My understanding is,
the Russians are rejecting Dalia Hassan
as a legitimate successor, as a result,
won't sign off on the peace agreement.
You're well informed.
I have close friends in Moscow.
In some ways, people there
appreciate me more
than people in my own country.
It wasn't their constitution
you trampled.
The Russians have been trying
to back out of this agreement
from day one.
Do you honestly think
your relationships
can change their minds?
I'm certain I can.
- How?
- Let's just say
I'm going to be able
to exercise some leverage.
What kind of leverage?
If it gets the job done,
does it really matter?
- It does to me.
- I can promise you
no laws will be broken,
nothing will tarnish you,
but the details
really must stay
between me and the Russians.
You and Hassan created the framework
for the most significant peace
in a generation, and you...
got the entire world behind it.
To let the Russians tear down
what should be the crown jewel
in your administration...
Don't play me.
This is about you
trying to repair your reputation.
Is that so hard to understand?
You participated in a conspiracy
to cover up the assassination
of David Palmer.
I was trying to protect the country
from an unnecessary trauma...
You were doing
what was best for yourself.
You're right.
I suppose I've spent so many years
trying to justify my actions
that it's become difficult for me...
to own up to the truth.
I made mistakes.
Terrible mistakes,
that stained
the office of the presidency.
And for which I will be paying
the rest of my life.
But I still can be of value
to my country.
I can still do some good.
We both know you wouldn't
have called me
unless you were out of options.
So we can continue
to do well on the past, or you can
let me pursue the only chance you have
of resurrecting the peace process.
Please.
Let me help you.
All right.
Thank you.
What do you intend to do first?
Arrange a meeting
with the Russian delegate Novakovich.
Get a message to him at his hotel.
Tell him that you are sending
over your official emissary
to have a talk with him.
What if he doesn't agree
to this meeting?
Make sure he knows it's me.
He'll agree to it.
God help you
if you make me regret this.
You okay?
Perfect.
Promise?
I am so thirsty.
Me, too.
Do you want something to drink?
Sure.
I'll be right back.
Don't move.
Your cell's ringing.
Don't worry about it, let it go.
Hello.
Jack's phone.
- I need to talk to Jack.
- What's wrong?
Samir Mehran is dead.
I think he was assassinated.
What do you mean, assassinated?
I ran
a preliminary toxicology report.
It showed traces
of an unidentified toxin
in his bloodstream.
Someone must have injected him
with it, probably at the scene.
There was an EMT there.
He looked familiar.
There was so much going on,
I didn't take much notice.
Familiar? From where?
I need you to get my FBI case files.
Get me everything on red square.
You think
he was from the Russian mob?
He looked like somebody
who was with Laitanan
during the time I was under.
That was six years ago.
Are you sure?
Honestly, no.
Just send me the case files,
all the surveillance photos
and I'll see if he's in there.
You need to hear this.
Are you there?
Don't talk,
I'm gonna get you to a hospital.
- Did something happen?
- Who is this?
Renee's been hit by a sniper.
I need a trauma team
at St. Andrew's now.
Hold on, stay with me.
Let's go.
Keep everybody in the lobby.
There's a sniper.
Call 911.
Now!
Move!
We need to get to the hospital,
on the 22nd and ninth.
You can make it.
Wait... Just wait.
We're gonna make it. I promise.
Come on!
We've got to get there now!
Come on, come on.
I got you.
You'll be all right.
We're almost there.
They're near from your hospital
and should be there any minute.
Make sure she's given priority care.
Thank you.
Pull up satellite.
Isolate the areas
between 8th Avenue
and West 18th street.
- What's going on?
- Walker was just shot.
- What?
- Just do what I asked.
Jack said the sniper
was positioned at his apartment
at 1145 west 18th street.
- Roll back the feed 3 minutes.
- Is she gonna be okay?
He's rushing her to the hospital.
I don't get it.
Why would anyone want to kill Renee?
Help!
She's been shot!
No exit wound!
We got a gunshot wound to the chest.
Let's move.
- What's her pulse?
- 110, respiratory is still ragged.
- Check her carotid.
- BP is 80 over 50.
- Five is epped.
- How many gunshot wounds?
- One in the chest.
- Is patient typing crossed?
Call the blood bank,
send up four units of O-negative.
It's Chloe.
How is she?
Not good.
We rolled back satellite.
The shots were fired
from an office across the street.
PD reported finding a body
at the scene.
What about the shooter?
We don't have anything.
We lost him.
You were on the phone with her.
What were you talking about?
It's not important right now.
- Be with her.
- She's in surgery, I can't.
What were you talking about?
I told her Samir Mehran was given
a lethal injection at the scene
of his capture,
probably to keep him from talking.
Renee thought she may have
recognized one of the EMT.
- She didn't say anything to me.
- She wasn't sure.
She didn't think
it meant anything at the time.
Where did she say
she remembered him from?
From her days undercover
with the Russian mob.
She asked me to get her
the red square file.
Did you pull up the file?
I gotta get back to you.
She didn't make it.
There was just too much
arterial damage and blood loss.
I'm very sorry.