The FBI believes
they've detected where the
next attack will take place.
The chemical plant just
outside Kidron, Ohio.
What's our time frame?
The tank could rupture
in less than 15 minutes.
Right now our best chance to stop this
is by finding Dubaku and the CIP device.
400 psi.
How long before the tank ruptures?
Seven minutes.
We've got a problem.
I thought you killed Almeida and Bauer.
Damn it! How did they find us?!
I don't know!
 They're in the building.
Disengage the CIP module.
Begin the offload.
Go!
Jack, I've got the CIP device!
It's been destroyed.
The Matobos are safe. I'm
taking them to the van.
Copy that.
You and Bill do a sweep.
See if you can find Dubaku.
We are not equipped to look for one man
in a city of millions.
We need additional resources.
The government? They can't be trusted.
We can't trust anybody.
That's why we're working on the outside.
President Taylor can be trusted.
Madame President, you
need to listen to me.
The people who rescued us, they
have acquired the CIP device.
It's being destroyed,
and your country's no longer
under immediate threat.
Who are these people?
I'll tell you everything in person,
but I must speak to you alone.
Please get Henry on the phone.
Henry's unreachable.
I've been trying to reach Agent Gedge,
and he hasn't picked up.
He said he was outside
Samantha Roth's apartment
waiting for the First Gentleman.
You're telling me my
husband's gone missing?
Gedge is dead.
What happened?
Something went wrong.
Taylor killed Gedge,
I don't know how.
Don't kill him.
Bring him to me.
You're certain you weren't followed?
Yes. Come on. Help me get him inside.
We can confirm at this point
the tragedies that unfolded
in the skies over Washington
and in Kidron, Ohio, were
indeed acts of terrorism.
But I am here to assure
you that those responsible
are no longer a threat to this country.
Their attempts to stop
us from intervening
in the Sangalan genocide have failed.
We will not give in to terrorists.
A short time ago, I gave the order
for our troops to begin operations
that will liberate
the people of Sangala.
We are confident that the Juma
regime will collapse swiftly,
and that democracy will be restored
under the leadership
of Prime Minister Ule Motobo.
You, you, come.
Well done, Agent Vossler.
I've got to go now.
I've got a shift that starts at 4:00.
Then go. Your money will be
wired to the usual account.
The room is soundproof, Mr. Taylor.
There's no point in screaming
or trying to call for help.
Elimu, remove Mr. Taylor's gag.
You son of a bitch.
You're behind my son's death.
He was poking his nose
where it did not belong.
You'll never get away with
this. You must know that.
Everyone in the city is
going be looking for me.
You should be concerned with
just one question, Mr. Taylor.
Does your wife love you enough
to call off the invasion of my country?
For your sake,
I hope the answer is yes.
Activate the scrambling device.
Our law enforcement agencies
will hunt down the people responsible
and bring them to justice.
I ask now that your thoughts and prayers
go to those who lost their lives today,
to their families and loved ones,
and to our troops who
are putting their lives
on the line in the name of freedom.
Thank you.
Good afternoon.
Motobo's arrived.
He and the others have
been brought in secretly
through the underground entrance
by agents I personally know and trust.
Motobo told me the
people he's bringing in
are responsible for saving his life
and recovering the CIP device.
Who are they?
Bill Buchanan, whom I believe you met
when he headed up CTU L.A.,
FBI agent named Renee Walker
and Jack Bauer.
Bauer...
He was one of Motobo's kidnappers.
Doesn't make sense.
I know.
Motobo asked me to listen
to what they have to say,
and I'm willing to do so.
Send them in.
The president's ready.
Ule.
I can't tell you
how thankful we are that
you and Alama are safe.
Thank you. She's with
Mr. Buchanan's people now,
recovering.
That you were subjected
to such an ordeal
on our soil is a source
of shame both to me
personally and to my country.
Madame President,
my chief concern is
for Sangala, not myself.
May I ask what your timetable is
for the invasion?
I've issued the order
to our military to proceed.
I thank you with all my heart.
You're doing my people a great service,
much as these people have
done for your country.
Now forgive me, Prime Minister,
but I'm finding that hard to believe.
I assure you, none of
this is as it seems.
But they're here to explain themselves.
Now, if you'll excuse
me, Madame President,
I must meet with my people
to discuss post-invasion plans.
Of course.
I want an explanation and I want it now.
What the hell is going on?!
Madame President,
six weeks ago, Bill Buchanan discovered
that key members of your government
were working with General Juma
and Colonel Dubaku in an effort
to undermine this
nation's foreign policy...
your foreign policy
with regards to Sangala.
You realize that that is
an outrageous accusation?
Yes, ma'am.
Unfortunately, it's the truth.
It explains why during this crisis,
every effort you made
to stop Dubaku failed.
Bill, why didn't you come to me?
I didn't know who I could trust
or if you'd even believe me.
So I formed
a small group to locate
and neutralize Dubaku.
Tony Almeida and ultimately, Jack,
joined me.
Tony Almeida was the one
who put the CIP device
into Dubaku's hands
in the first place.
Using the CIP device
as bait was necessary
to the undercover operation.
We had to follow it back to Dubaku.
A lot of people
died on those planes, never mind what
could have happened at the
chemical plant in Kidron!
Madame President, if I may, I was part
of the FBI task force assigned
to recover the CIP device,
and I can personally vouch
for what they're telling you.
The loss of life was tragic, yes,
but in my opinion,
everything these men have done
saved the lives of thousands.
If I choose to believe
everything you're telling me,
where would you go from here?
Dubaku is the only person
with the names of the
people who betrayed you
within your government.
It's imperative that we find him.
We would have to work under the radar.
Any word of an investigation,
people would start running for cover.
You're saying we can't even involve
the FBI and Homeland?
Yes, sir, that's correct.
Madame President,
Tim Woods is on the phone.
He says it's urgent.
Put him through.
Have a seat.
Yes?
Madame President, I'm
sorry to interrupt.
There's a call for you from Ike Dubaku.
Voice I.D. confirms that. He
says it's about your husband.
My husband?
Yes, ma'am. I'll connect you.
This is President Taylor.
I'll come straight to the
point, Madame President.
I have your husband.
Let me demonstrate.
Say something.
Allison...
Henry, are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry about this.
For God sake, don't let them use me
to influence you in any way.
Our demands are as follows:
You will have your forces
withdrawn from around
my country, Sangala,
immediately and permanently.
Also, Motobo must be delivered to my men
who will be stationed at the east lot
of the Stanswick Power Plant.
If he's not there by 4:00,
or if anybody attempts
to follow or impede my men
when they leave the plant,
your husband will die a
slow and certain death.
You wouldn't dare!
Cut off his finger.
Stop it!
Meet my demands
or I will send him back
to you one piece at a time.
Do you understand, Madame President?
Yes,
I understand.
Any attempt
to find your husband
will be known to me very quickly,
and I will kill him immediately.
Madame President, I just heard back
from the team I sent to
Henry's last-known location.
They found Samantha Roth's
and Secret Service Agent Gedge's bodies.
Oh, God!
Gedge had possession
of a paralytic drug.
That and other evidence on
scene suggests he was complicit
in Henry's abduction,
which, of course, confirms
the corruption you just told us about.
Madame President, time is tight.
We need to decide how to respond.
I don't think anyone would blame you
for holding back, at least temporarily,
the invasion of Sangala.
How many people died on those planes?
How many?!
About 300, ma'am.
All because I refused to
change course in Sangala.
How can I ask the American
people to make sacrifices
that I'm not willing to make myself?
I can't give in.
I can't.
Madame President...
we can still try and find your husband
before the 4:00 deadline.
Dubaku has specifically forbidden that.
And according to you,
I can't trust any of my
law enforcement agencies.
You can trust me.
Right now everyone believes
that Agent Walker is dead,
and I have no status at all.
Which means that Dubaku's spies
cannot track us because
officially, we don't exist.
You resigned from government service,
and the Senate regards you as
having been a renegade agent.
How am I supposed to know
where your loyalties really lie?
With all due respect,
Madame President, ask around.
What could you even do
on such short notice?
I couldn't make you any promises,
but we will do everything
possible to save your husband.
Right now, we need you to go along
with Dubaku's demands.
Help buy us some time.
Madame President, you
don't have another choice.
All right.
Find him, please?
Yes, ma'am.
We're gonna need a secure hard line.
You may use this room if you need to.
I'll have you escorted back out through
the underground entrance
when you're ready.
I'm gonna need a copy of the president
and the First Gentleman's
Secret Service details.
I'll have them brought to you.
Thank you.
Okay, we'll start off with Agent Gedge.
We need access to his phone records.
I want to know who he's been
talking to over the last few hours.
Obviously, we can't use any of
the president's security people.
Thank you.
Phone logs are highly classified,
especially for agents
assigned to the First Family.
Can Chloe O'Brian get access?
It'll be faster if we can get someone
who's already got clearance.
Larry Moss.
He doesn't strike me
as someone who's willing
to work outside the system.
That's true, but I think I can
persuade him to do what we need.
You really trust him?
Yes. We know each other pretty well.
Fine. Try him. We don't have much time.
Agent Moss.
Larry, it's Renee. I'm alive,
but you can't let anyone
know. Do you understand me?
Oh, my God.
Renee? What... Where are
you? Are you all right?
I'm-I'm fine. I'll explain later,
but right now we need your help.
Who's, who's "we"?
Myself and Jack Bauer.
What?!
He's on our side,
Larry, just like he said.
Everything that he did, he
did to preserve his cover.
Renee, this whole time I've
been thinking you were dead.
Why didn't you tell me?
The Bureau is compromised.
Larry, just like he said,
and on one there can know
about this operation. It has
to stay completely off book.
What operation?
Jack and I are at the White House.
The First Gentleman has
been kidnapped by Ike Dubaku.
I don't, I don't know
anything about that.
It's true. The president's
asked Jack and me to find him.
Very few people know about this,
and that's the way that it has to stay.
If we don't find him by
4:00 p.m., he'll be killed.
Larry... if you've ever trusted me,
trust me now, please, and help me.
What do you want me to do?
Looks like the First
Gentleman's Secret Service agent
was involved in all of
this... Brian Gedge; he's dead.
You need to check his phone logs
and get all the information you can
about who he's been in
contact with recently.
I need to see you to
make sure this is real,
that you're not under duress.
No, there's no time for that.
That's not negotiable.
You want my help, we meet.
The Capitol Reflecting Pool,
as soon as you can get there.
Okay, fine.
He'll help us, I think,
but we need to go.
President Taylor emphasized
the terrorists are no longer a threat
and says the invasion will begin.
She also says
former Prime Minister Ule
Motobo will be reinstated
to work towards building a
new democratic government.
I don't get it.
What?
The president's talking as if
the CIP device and Motobo
have been recovered,
but how could that have happened
without us knowing about it?
Well, it just means
whatever agency's responsible
hasn't let us know.
What other agency?
We're being kept out of the loop,
and I don't like it.
So am I seeing you later?
I don't know. I've got
some things to figure out.
What does that mean?
It means I have to
get home at some point.
I haven't seen Christina in a week.
All right.
Sean, are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm sensing a little distance.
I just have to get back to work.
Excuse me.
Could you be a little
less obvious, do you think?
What are you talking about?
Give me a break.
Just hold up a sign that says,
"Hey, world, we're sleeping together."
Are you stupid?
I know it's stupid and wrong,
and I'm gonna end it.
Yeah, you'd better, fast,
before Larry notices.
Where is Larry?
I don't know. That's not the point.
The point is, if he
finds out about this,
he's gonna transfer your
ass to Juneau so fast,
your head will spin.
Larry.
Oh, my God.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Were you able to access
Agent Gedge's phone records?
Yeah.
Yeah,
over the last three hours,
Gedge spoke repeatedly
to another Secret Service
agent named Edward Vossler.
I checked out Vossler's
personnel records.
Before he was a Secret Service
agent, he was Special Forces,
and for two years, served in Sangala.
So we can assume Vossler's
working for Dubaku.
Did you bring any of his files with you?
Yeah.
Does Vossler have a family?
Why do you need to know that?
Does he have a family?
He's been married for
five years to a paralegal.
They have an
11-month-old baby boy.
She left her job to
stay home with the kid.
Okay, we're gonna need to split up.
I need you to help me track Vossler.
I need you to go to his home
and hope his family is there.
Vossler was Special Forces.
There's no way we're gonna break
him in the time that we've got.
The only way to get him
to cooperate is to make him
think we're gonna hurt his
family, his wife and his kid.
No, absolutely not. Renee?
That's stepping over the line, Jack.
You stepped over the line
the second you interrogated Tanner.
Tanner's a murderer.
As far as we know, Vossler's
wife is completely innocent,
let alone a small child.
When are you people gonna stop thinking
everyone else is following your rules?!
They're not!
Dubaku is gonna kill Henry Taylor
within the next 45 minutes
unless we find him.
You've got one of two choices:
Now you can either phone the
president and explain to her
that your conscience won't allow you
to do what is necessary to save him,
or you can simply do what is necessary.
Pick one!
Renee?
Larry!
I'm gonna need your vehicle.
Start tracking Vossler
through his cell phone.
Utilize his Secret
Service deployment grid.
Look at yourself.
You've lost everyone and
everything you ever had
by doing what you think is necessary.
I won't let you do it to her, Bauer.
Renee will not end up like you.
Are you gonna give me your keys or not?
Jack.
Jack!
The rules are what make us better.
Not today.
Even those who oppose
the plan to invade Sangala
can't deny the atrocities
committed by that regime.
I slowed down Taylor's bleeding,
but I can't get it to stop completely.
Tourniquet is as tight as possible?
Yes.
Then cauterize the wound.
Mikali has a blowtorch.
You risk Taylor going into shock.
Just put something in his mouth.
I don't want him biting his
tongue off with the pain.
Hey, what are you doing at home, huh?
I thought you'd be at work.
I was. Rosa called me at the diner.
She was having one of her episodes.
You know your sister.
She's just manipulating you.
You don't have to go to
her every time she calls.
I'm all she has, Samuel. Be kind.
You know, you're kind
enough for both of us.
I just wanted to make sure
that you were still
coming to dinner tonight.
Um, look, I'm really sorry, but I can't.
I'm looking at a stack
of shipping manifests.
Oh, no! Isn't there some way?
We could do it as late as you want.
I really wish I could.
I'm sorry, Marika.
Uh, listen, baby,
I'll make it up to you, okay?
Okay. Well, I'm gonna make extra
just in case you change your mind.
You're too good to me.
You're right.
I have to get back to the diner, Rosa.
Are you gonna be okay?
Who was that on the phone?
It was him, wasn't it?
All right, stop.
I know you don't approve
of Samuel, but I love him.
Oh. You love him?
Why?
Because he spends money on you?
Because he pays our rent?
You've only known him
four months.
What difference does that make?
You don't know anything about him.
What if he's not the
importer he says he is?
Or that he's in this country illegally?
Not this again.
I'm just trying to protect you, Marika.
I don't need your protection.
Yes, you do.
This man isn't...
Isn't what?
Nothing.
Forget it.
I'm sorry, I don't have time for this.
I'll be home after my shift.
We can appear to comply with
the first part of Dubaku's demand
by pulling the fleet back.
Then we simply launch the
invasion from farther out at sea.
Now, the second part of his
demand is more complicated.
If we were really turning Matobo over,
we'd be putting him in
a car right about now.
That's out of the
question. We need him safe.
Agreed. But we can send
a car with a look-alike.
If we handle it right, Dubaku
won't be aware of the deception
until the last minute.
By then, hopefully,
we'll have found Henry.
Madame President, do we have
your authorization to proceed?
Yes.
This is Bauer.
Okay, I've got Vossler.
He's on the Beltway
near Bethesda, moving south,
about seven miles from you.
Copy that. I'm on my
way. Where's he headed?
According to the Secret Service log,
his shift starts at 4:00 p.m.
He's meeting a foreign
dignitary's plane at Andrews.
Jack, I don't have to tell you...
once he's through that
gate and onto that base,
you're not going to
be able to touch him.
Okay, he's going to have
to double back on the 337
if he wants to get
through that main gate.
I should be able to make up
time by taking Connecticut.
Just keep sight of him.
Have you heard from Renee?
Do we know if she's arrived
at Vossler's house yet?
No. But she knows how
to get in touch with us
if she's in trouble.
Coming.
Can I help you?
Who are you?
Shut up. Do what I tell
you, and there's a chance
you'll live through this.
Don't move! He's scared.
Stay where you are or I will
shoot you where you stand.
You're going to kill me for
trying to comfort my baby?
Sit down.
What kind of a person are you?
Doing this to us.
You should ask your husband that.
What are you talking about?
Edward is a good man.
Maybe you don't know him quite
as well as you think you do.
I know he would never point
a gun near a child. Shut up!
Put the cuff around your wrist.
Don't do this.
Now!
Okay, where is he now?
He just got off the Beltway.
He's stopped in traffic.
Okay, I'm coming up on the intersection
of Allenford and Auth. I
should be there in 30 seconds.
Just let me know if he moves.
He's moving.
Damn it!
What's the next street north?
Baxter Drive.
But, Jack, it's a one-way street.
Copy that.
He made the light at Allenford.
I'm on Baxter.
He's 15 seconds away, Jack.
Ten seconds.
Five seconds.
I got him.
Let me see your hands!
Now!
Get out of the car. Get out of the car!
Move. Move!
Where is he?
Where is Henry Taylor? I don't
know what you're talking about.
Where is he?
Fine,
we'll do this your way.
Yes.
I've got Vossler. You got his wife?
And his child. You ready?
Yes.
Put your phone on speaker.
Talk to your wife.
You son of a bitch... Talk to your wife!
Carol, ar-are you all right?
There's a woman with a gun.
She's threatening to kill me.
Why is Conner crying?
Oh, my God, Edward.
What's happening? Who are these people?
You are running out of time.
I didn't want to have to do this.
No, you wouldn't...
What's happening? I don't
know. She's got Conner.
Oh, my God, she's doing
something to Conner!
Let go of my baby!
He's just a baby! Please!
What the hell are you doing? You can
stop this. Just tell me where he is.
For God's sake, Edward, tell
them what they want to know!
Damn it! All right, all
right, I'll tell you!
Stand down. I'll get back to you.
Your baby's fine.
You're a monster!
Where is he?!
You tell me now, or the situation
for your family goes from bad to worse.
Where is he?
How do I know you're just
not going to kill them anyway?
You don't.
Fine.
There's a greengrocer,
12451 Arlington Avenue.
They're holding him in the basement.
Access.
There's a staircase in the back,
but it's always locked.
Is Dubaku with him? He was.
How many guns are guarding him?
At least four. Get out of here!
Get away from the car!
Walk away... now!
Damn it.
Stop!
Get out of the car now!
Move! Move!
The goal is to make it look like
we're going to hand Matobo over
for as long as is reasonably possible.
When you get to the rendezvous point,
keep your distance from Dubaku's men.
Let them see you in the backseat,
but do not get out of the car.
Don't let them get any closer
than you feel comfortable with.
As soon as you start to feel
that the risk is unacceptable,
get the hell out.
That's straight from the president.
Clear? Clear.
Good luck.
Jack?
I got an address
for Henry Taylor.
12451 Arlington Avenue.
It's a storefront. He's
being held in the basement.
If you get there before I
do, I want you to stand down.
Dubaku's got at least four gunmen there.
All right. Meanwhile,
I'm going to call Bill,
pull him up to speed.
I want you to do the
same thing with Larry.
And what about Vossler? He's dead.
He attacked me. I didn't have a choice.
Are you okay?
No, I don't think I am.
What do you mean? What's wrong?
Agent Walker, are you still there?
I'm not...
Listen to me.
We could not have gotten
this far if it wasn't for you.
Okay?
No one would blame you if this was
just too much for you to handle.
Maybe you should get out.
Maybe I will.
Yeah.
Tomorrow.
Agent Masden and I are on our way.
We'll be tracking you via satellite.
Check in with me when you're
approaching the power plant.
Yes, sir.
How much time do you
think this will buy us?
Until Dubaku realizes
Matobo's not in the limo.
Ten minutes, maybe 15.
That's 15 minutes more than we had.
Madame President, I just got
off the phone with Jack Bauer.
He and Agent Walker think they
have a location on your husband.
Where?
Arlington Avenue.
They're on their way now.
How long will it take them?
Ten, 15 minutes.
Thank you.
This just came over from Homeland.
Like you said...
we're being kept out of the loop.
Thanks.
Did you see this?
Homeland's preparing to
lower the threat level
at the president's request.
Yeah, I saw the flash.
Don't you think that's odd,
considering we don't know anything
about the CIP device being recovered?
Yeah. I'll talk to Homeland.
All I'm saying is... I get the feeling
like there's something going
on behind our back here.
Like I said, I'll talk to them.
Excuse me. Yeah, sure.
Where are you?
On my way to where we think
Henry Taylor's being held.
So you got Vossler to talk.
It gave us our only chance to
rescue the president's husband.
What's the address?
I'll send a SWAT team to meet you.
You know you can't do that.
The Bureau's compromised.
It will jeopardize any
attempt that we make.
But there is something
else I need you to do.
Okay, what's that?
Keep an incident quiet
until what Jack and
I are doing goes down.
What incident?
Vossler's dead.
Jack killed him at the
hotel on 18th and Riggin.
It was self-defense.
Is that what he told you?
Larry... Damn it, Renee, what the
hell are you doing with this guy?
We're supposed to bring
suspects in, not murder them.
Larry, please...
And until we know who
Dubaku's source is there,
you've got to handle this
outside of the Bureau, okay?
There's a guy at D.C.
Metro I know I can trust.
I'll have him deal with Vossler.
Thank you, Larry.
I understand. I will let him know.
According to our sources,
a vehicle containing Matobo
just left the White House. Good.
What is the state of the
American invasion forces?
The fleet is withdrawing
from Sangalan territorial waters,
and has set steam for the 23rd Meridian.
Excellent.
Hello.
It's Rosa.
Rosa, if you're looking for
Marika, she's not with me.
I'm looking for you, Samuel.
Or whatever your real name is.
What are you talking about?
My sister may be naive, but I'm not.
I checked with someone I
know at Immigration Services,
and no one named Samuel
Aboa emigrated from Sangala
in the last year, or
in the last 15 years.
Well, they've obviously made a mistake.
You're making a mistake.
Now I don't know who you
really are, and I don't care.
I just want you out of my sister's life.
Does Marika know about this?
No, not yet.
And I'm willing to keep it that way.
So you've not reported me to anyone?
No. I don't want Marika to
know anything about this.
What do you want?
Break up with her,
and this stays between us.
You just end it tonight,
and we won't have a problem.
I have to take care of a little problem.
Call me when we have Matobo.
Yeah.
The vehicle that's supposed
to be delivering Matobo
is arriving at the power
plant. If we delay any longer,
Dubaku is going to get
suspicious. What's your status?
I'm almosthere. How much time
can you buy us? I dot know, Jack.
Okay, Agent Walker and I will
move in as soon as I get there.
I'll keep you posted.
All right, good luck.
This is Agent Smith.
We've got a visual on
Dubaku's men. Understood.
We have it on satellite.
Bring him to us.
They've ordered us
to get out of the car.
Now one of them is making
a call. Hang tight, Agent.
Their car arrived,
but nothing is happening. What
do you mean nothing is happening?
We ordered them to
hand Matobo over to us
but no one's getting out of the vehicle.
The Americans have been playing us.
Destroy their vehicle.
Yes, sir.
That's long enough. Get them
the hell out of there. Retreat.
Get out now. Roger that.
You ready? Yes.
Let's go.
Get out from behind
the counter. Now! Move!
Okay, I want you to unlock that door.
And I want you to ask those
men what they want to eat.
You do one thing I don't like,
and I will blow your head
off, you understand me?
Open the door.
Want anything to eat?
No. Some cold beers. Okay.
Yes.
Kill Henry Taylor.
Then we have nothing to
hold over their heads.
We don't have anything now.
The president was
willing to let him die.
We are done here.
Kill Taylor,
and have your men pack everything up.
Understood.
Oh, my God.
Sir... sir...
We're going to get you help.
Just stay with me.
Get an ambulance!