Subtitles:
Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu (V 1.00)
Hassan's security forces
in the Islamic Republic
are sweeping through the capital,
arresting opposition leaders.
And if he continues,
it may delegitimize the peace accord.
I can't vouch for you as a reformer,
Mr. President,
if you renege
on your human rights obligations.
My brother tried to kill me,
helped by elements
within my own government.
Apparently, killing President Hassan
was only part of his brother's plan.
CTU now believes he's also trying
to acquire weapons-grade uranium.
When can I take possession
of the rods?
As soon as we have the money.
- I found a doctor who can treat him.
- No doctors.
The authorities know
about the nuclear material.
Putting Oleg in a clinic
would lead them right to us.
- Dr. Levine.
- How did you get in here?
- My brother is sick.
- I call you an ambulance.
No. No one can know about this.
What do you want from me?
You're a data analyst for CTU.
You got access
to all sorts of good stuff.
- Yeah, but not unrestricted access.
- Payout's got to be at least 6 figures.
You were undercover for nearly two years
with the Russian Mob.
You're asking me to go back in?
Laitanan was obsessed with her.
It turned violent.
- Did he rape her?
- He tried a couple of times.
- Can we talk about this deal now?
- I wish it were that simple.
- Tie her up.
- What?
You're making a mistake.
This is the chance of a lifetime.
It's over.
Vladimir didn't take the bait.
Renee, it's Jack.
I know you can hear me.
I'm on my way now.
You don't want to do this deal,
then kill me,
because this deal
is the only thing that I have.
Do it!
Pull the trigger!
I had to be sure.
Jack, are you there?
What's going on?
She's in.
They bought her cover.
I've got a visual on you.
I'm going off comm for a minute.
You all right?
Chloe,
I want you to monitor Renee's comm.
- I need to speak to Hastings.
- I'll put you through.
Go ahead.
- We need to pull Renee Walker out now.
- Based on what?
She's a danger to herself.
Laitanan threatened to execute her,
she said she was sick of living,
- and wanted to die, she meant it.
- She must've been playing him.
She doesn't care what happens to her,
that's what makes her dangerous.
She's like a bomb ready to go off.
We need to get her out of there.
I understand your concern,
but we can't roll up this operation
before we find those nuclear rods.
We can arrest Laitanan. If he knows how
to find the rods, I will make him talk.
If you're saying what I think you are,
we don't do that anymore.
Then you people do what you do well.
- Offer him immunity or something.
- This is the Russian Syndicate.
They're very secretive,
they protect their own.
It is highly unlikely
- that Laitanan would cooperate.
- You better find another way,
I am not gonna let Renee die
because CTU did their job badly.
I will not let that happen.
Do you understand me?
If you can think of something,
I will listen. But right now,
Renee's the only hope we have
of neutralizing this threat.
And on my order, she stays in play.
I'll find a way to get her out
when I go in as the buyer.
I'll stay under in her place.
Do we have a deal?
As long as you can do it
without risking the mission.
- I give you my word.
- Agent Ortiz will meet you
at the staging area with a TAC team.
He'll have everything you need
for your cover.
Hold on. They're moving.
I need to get back on comm.
We'll go back to my shop,
and we will discuss this buyer of yours.
Dana...
Start forwarding mission
status reports to the Nuclear
Emergency Team at Fort Hamilton.
I want them ready to go in
as soon as we find these nuclear rods.
I'm on it, sir.
It's me.
I've got something.
Damn, you're fast.
Okay, hold on.
Okay, go.
Let's hear it.
It's an NYPD evidence lockup.
According to the manifest,
a local vice group
just impounded a stash of drug money.
It'll be held there
for the next 48 hours.
- How much?
- $120,000.
- All right, what's the plan?
- You go in and take it.
Break into a police station?
Are you out of your mind?
It's a warehouse.
Most of the security is automated.
I can manipulate it from here.
You walk in, you walk out with the cash.
I'll talk you through it.
I need to access
their security codes,
work up a keycard
to get you inside the warehouse.
- How long?
- Meet me outside CTU in 30 minutes.
Did you take care of your situation?
- Situation?
- The mystery you had to leave work for.
It's fine.
What do you need?
I'm getting five percent lag
in my Drone's ABS controls.
With everything going on,
I'm running hot.
Okay, I'll make sure
to free up some memory space
on the auxiliary servers.
Thanks.
You know,
if there's something bothering you,
you've always got
my shoulder to cry on.
Or any other body part.
I will keep that in mind.
For now, why don't you focus on running
aerial support for Walker and Bauer?
Lugo, take a break.
I want to talk to her alone.
All right, you have my attention.
Tell me about this buyer.
His name's Ernst Meier.
German arms dealer.
- Never heard of him.
- He does most of his business in Asia,
he just started branching out
into America.
- What's he looking to buy?
- Weapons-grade uranium.
- You're serious?
- Very.
Someone in the Russian Syndicate
smuggled nuclear fuel rods
out of the Ukraine.
They're planning on selling them
on the open market.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- I don't, Renee.
- But you can find out.
You're very well connected.
I have always admired...
your ambition,
but you're chasing the devil.
Dealing AK-47s...
no one really cares.
But nuclear material?
The profit is worth it.
You need money?
You can always come work for me.
I'm doing this so I don't ever have
to work for anyone.
Have a seat.
If I could find out,
what would it be worth?
30% of the deal.
I don't have to tell you,
that is more money
than you could possibly know
what to do with.
Meier says these rods
are going to be sold soon,
so if we want to make a counter bid,
it has to happen fast.
If you don't know anything, tell me,
so I can go somewhere else.
How well do you know him?
You trust him?
There's no one I trust more.
I've been with him for two years.
- What do you mean "with"?
- It's professional.
Can you help us or not?
I'll make a few calls,
see what I can find out.
I'm going to have
to meet this Meier.
And I need a good faith payment
up front.
- How much?
- Five million.
That's a lot of money.
I'm taking big risk
just making these calls.
5 million is nothing compared
to what your buyer will have to pay
for nuclear fuel rods.
Fine.
I'll ask him,
but I can't make any promises.
If he wants my help,
that's the price.
There's a garage
on the corner of 12th and Market Street.
Someone will meet him there,
on the roof.
Once the money is in our account,
they'll bring him back here,
we will talk.
I'll give him a call.
It's good to see you.
You're going to make me
start losing sleep again.
I'll let you know what Meier says.
I'll tell my men.
I'll give you privacy for your call.
- Were you listening?
- We're ready to wire the money.
- When can you be there?
- As soon as I finish prepping my cover.
I'm almost at the staging area.
30 minutes tops.
How you holding up?
It's hard to be in the same room
with this son of a bitch.
- I can handle it.
- I'll be there as soon as I can.
Morphine will take effect
in just a few moments.
Don't worry, Oleg.
You're going to be fine.
It might help me if I knew exactly
what happened to your brother.
How did he get exposed
to weapons-grade uranium?
Don't worry about that.
Just make sure he lives.
It's him again, isn't it?
The second time he's called.
You should answer it.
Why aren't you picking up your phone?
I called you twice.
Must have been in the tunnel.
Ulana says you're not at the house.
- Where are you?
- Stuck in traffic.
- Tell her it's going to be a while.
- How's Oleg?
He's okay.
Sleeping.
Let me know
when you get to the house.
I will.
It was him?
Don't worry, okay?
By the time he finds out,
you'll already have been treated.
Then it won't matter.
It's just the test results.
You say or do anything
that I don't like,
and my men will kill
your wife and daughter.
Open the door.
- The blood work you ordered.
- Thank you.
I noticed there was no patient name.
You're right.
I forgot to put that down.
I'll take care of it later.
Is everything okay?
Fine.
I'm just working a little later
than I expected.
You did good.
What does it say?
Your brother has been
exposed to at least 400 rems.
The chemical toxicity
of the radiation is causing
- renal failure.
- I know it's serious.
Can you help him or not?
He needs a bone marrow transplant.
That requires a surgical team
in a fully equipment.
There has to be something
you can do right here,
right now.
Drugs could help him
to flush out the radiation
and stimulate white blood cell,
but that's a half measure.
I can't guarantee
he'll recover.
My brother is not going to die.
It's up to you, Doctor.
Now get to work.
Okay, got it.
That was CTU.
Your offshore account's in place.
They're forwarding instructions
to your PDA on how to wire the money.
Excuse me.
Hastings said,
as soon as we have confirmation
that Laitanan can get us
to the rods,
we're pulling Walker out.
That's right.
What's going on, Jack?
Hastings said she's unstable.
I don't have time to explain it.
Just follow my lead.
How do we do without breaking cover?
- I don't know yet.
- All right.
I got 2 teams
running coordinated drive-bus.
They'll be ready when she's clear.
They own this neighborhood
and have eyes everywhere.
- Your men could be spotted.
- I've done this before.
I ran an operation like it
in Fallujah.
And I'm in command.
You're going to do
exactly what I tell you.
Stand by.
I hear him coming.
Laitanan's back.
I need to listen to this.
Excuse me.
I spoke to my men.
Did you get your buyer?
He agreed to the money.
He'll be at the garage in 20 minutes.
Very good.
We've a little time to catch up.
- Do you still like your single malts?
- Not right now.
- You sure? It's a 30 year.
- No, thanks.
What you said earlier...
down at the river.
You were tired of living,
wanted to die.
What happened to you?
Not important.
It is to me.
Don't worry about it.
Once I make this deal,
none of it will matter.
You're not the only one
who's been suffering these last time.
It's hard for me to admit,
I never forgave myself
for what I did to you.
It's in the past.
Forget it.
I don't want to forget it.
I had too much to drink that night,
I wasn't thinking clearly.
Never heard you
apologize for anything.
It's definitely a first.
I'm trying to make things right.
Don't be such a bitch.
Was I being a bitch?
I should apologize.
You're something else.
You never back down, do you?
I've missed our little arguments.
You're still nervous around me.
I shouldn't be surprised.
It's not you.
Someone else?
- What is it, then?
- I'm just...
I'm nervous about the deal.
Could be a lot of money at stake.
There's more for you here
than just money, if you want it.
I didn't come here for this.
Really. All the people
you could've gone to,
- you knocked on my door.
- Because you're connected.
That's the only reason?
I don't believe you.
Not my problem.
You should watch your tongue.
You might lose it one day.
You said I could get cleaned up.
- Bathroom has a shower.
- Thank you.
Agent Ortiz, we need to move now.
Renee called her buyer.
He agreed to pay.
I want you to meet with him.
Take a couple men.
It's a mistake.
Getting involved in nuclear arms.
It doesn't matter
how much money is at stake.
I have no intention
of pursuing this deal.
What?
When you've picked up the buyer,
when the money has been transferred,
you kill him, put him in the river,
keep the money for ourselves.
What about Renee?
She'll be working
with us from now on.
We are going to kill her buyer.
She's not going
to be happy about that.
You heard what she said.
She's got nothing left.
Nowhere to go.
Desperate woman.
I give her reason to live.
I'll take care of it.
President Hassan's security,
still cracking down on the opposition,
and not showing any signs of letting up.
Your warning to President Hassan
has fallen on deaf ears.
- Who filmed this?
- The BBC bought it from an eyewitness.
They've already seen it
on Downing Street.
That's why Ethan wanted you
to see this now.
The rumors have already started
that the British are pulling out
as signatories to the accord.
I need to talk
to the prime minister.
It's not just the British,
Madam President.
The Germans and Egyptians
are also positioning
themselves to pull out,
- if we lose their support...
- The peace deal is dead.
Maybe if they understood
the circumstances that Hassan's trying
to prevent his brother
from acquiring a nuclear weapon.
With respect, Madam President,
sharing that with the delegates
might spread a panic.
You're right,
but I still need to buy some time.
Assemble the representatives
from every signatory country
attending the conference.
I want to appeal to them myself
to stay the course.
What about President Hassan?
Shouldn't we include him?
Not until I've taken the temperature
with the delegates.
I don't want to push him too hard.
What is it?
As you requested,
these are backgrounds
on all the detainees.
Our security police have completed
their initial sweep of the capital city.
65 known members have been arrested
- and are being questioned.
- You learned anything?
Were any of them
working with my brother?
It's too early to tell.
What's wrong?
One of the suspects...
has family connections to a member
of my delegation here at the UN.
Who?
Jamot.
They're cousins.
That doesn't mean
that Jamot's involved in any of this.
We need to make sure.
We'll check his phone records
and other recent activities.
Good.
But I want him into custody.
- Sir?
- Arrest him.
Take him to our embassy.
Mr. President, with respect,
Jamot is a trusted member
of your inner circle.
The evidence against him
is purely circumstantial.
I trusted my brother as well.
Are you sure?
He is a public official.
It will not go unnoticed.
I don't care!
I don't care what anyone thinks.
I was almost killed today.
Or have you forgotten?
I was in the car with you, sir.
Then you should know
what needs to be done.
Yes, sir.
Forget about me?
What?
My name's Arlo Glass.
I'm one of your coworkers at CTU.
You said you'd free up some memory space
on the auxiliary servers.
I'm getting to it.
When?
We're in the middle of an operation
and my aerial feed
is running in slow-motion.
It's next on my list.
- Where are you going?
- To the bathroom.
Is that okay with you?
- You notice anything about Dana?
- Miss Perfect?
She seems distracted,
always making excuses to leave.
- Maybe she's avoiding you.
- What?
That's what I would do
if someone were drooling over me.
- You're lucky she hasn't reported you.
- If you weren't so jealous,
you'd see I was asking you
a serious question.
I'm jealous.
Please, won't you stare
at my ass as I walk away?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Stay here.
This has the address
and schematic of the evidence lockup.
You'll go through
the southeast entrance.
This keycard will get you access.
How do we find the money?
The evidence bins are numbered.
You're looking for 4301.
This is a dedicated comm unit.
You'll be able to hear me.
Do exactly what I tell you to do
and you'll be in and out.
No one will know.
I help you do this
and you never call me again.
That's the deal, right?
Sure Jen,
that's the deal.
I'll call you
when we get to the lockup.
You look thin.
Be out in a minute.
I don't want to wait.
Vladimir please,
just let me get dressed.
Why waste the energy?
I'll just have to get you
undressed all over again.
I already told you
I didn't come here for this.
That's what you say,
but part of you came here to see me.
Admit it.
There's nothing to admit.
Why is it so hard for you
to admit the truth?
You want this just as much as I do.
I'm not going to tell you again.
Leave me alone
and let me get dressed.
Come here.
I said come here.
Come here
or get out.
I call my men and the deal's off.
I'll take that drink now.
Dry yourself off.
Come out when you're ready.
Renee, do you copy?
You don't have to do this.
We can get you out of there now.
Where would that leave us?
I've got to stay under.
We'll find another way.
There is no other way.
Don't do this.
Go meet Vlad's men.
- See you when you get here.
- Why won't you listen to me?
- I'm going dark.
- Wait...
These arrests are making it
very difficult for my government
to continue to support
the peace agreement.
President Hassan can't ignore
the repercussions of what he's doing.
I know President Hassan.
He is a rational man, a good man.
There must be a reason
for these actions,
and I'm not just speaking
as his delegate but as his friend.
As his friend,
you need to let him know
that my government is not the only one
with grave concerns.
- This conference could fall apart...
- Excuse me, I'm sorry to interrupt.
Mr. Jamot,
may I speak with you privately?
Yes, of course.
Excuse me.
Of course.
What is it?
I've been ordered to escort you
to the embassy for some questions.
- Regarding?
- An internal security matter.
Please come with us.
- What is this about?
- We'll explain at the embassy.
It will have to wait.
I am about to go into a meeting.
It cannot wait, sir.
We need to go right now.
Are you arresting me?
It would be best
if we kept this discreet.
This is outrageous.
I demand to speak
with President Hassan.
President Hassan is the one
who gave this order.
I will not ask you again.
Come with us.
Very well.
Take him to the car.
I'll be right there.
- Is everything all right?
- Fine, sir. Please excuse me.
It's me. Are you alone?
Why do you sound upset?
I didn't want to burden you,
but we need to speak about your father.
- What is it?
- I have to go to the embassy now.
I'll meet you in private
when I get back.
You're going to give him vindesine
twice daily, morning and night.
Inject it right into the I.V. bag,
just like I'm doing.
You're going to want to be careful.
Radiation poisoning is transferable
through bodily fluids.
- Are you paying attention?
- Yes, I see.
He's also going to get
cisplatin every other day,
but he can take that in pill form.
I'll give you three weeks' worth.
How will I know
if he's getting better?
If the treatment's working,
his symptoms will begin to subside
in seven to ten days.
We're going to be leaving soon.
- Where?
- To the country house.
The doctor's giving me
everything I need to treat you.
You're going to get better.
That's the nurse
with the rest of the medicine.
Throw down your weapon, Josef.
Do what I said.
Don't make this worse than it is.
Drop it!
You son of a bitch.
Who else knows
about Oleg's sickness?
- Who else knows?
- Just the doctor.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
Undo him.
Wait, stop.
What are you doing?
Your father sent us
to bring you home.
Now, Josef.
It's okay.
Just do what he says.
I have him.
- We found them.
- Where were they?
A clinic in Mount Vernon.
How many people found out
about Oleg?
Only one... a doctor...
but we've taken care of him.
- Nobody will know we were here.
- Good.
Now, bring my sons to me.
Let's go.
That's right.
You are from Germany.
Bremen.
But I grew up traveling
with my father.
Are we going to do business or not?
Where is the $5 million?
You don't see any money
until I talk to Laitanan.
If you have questions,
ask me.
I don't want to talk to you.
Get him on the phone
or I drive away.
Now.
Meier's here.
He won't transfer the money
until he speaks with you first.
Put him on.
This is Meier.
Yes, Mr. Meier.
- What's the problem?
- After you get your money,
- how long till I get my information?
- Not very long.
I just have to make a few calls.
No more than an hour.
Where is Renee?
She's busy.
I would like to talk to her.
You can see her when you get here.
We have nothing more to discuss
until the money's in place.
Now, get Lugo on the phone.
Fine.
Go ahead.
Once the money is confirmed
into our account, you know what to do.
I need your account number.
I'm transferring through multiple
accounts so it can't be traced.
This will take a moment.
We'll wait.
Is it done?
- Not yet.
- My partner's good for the money.
You should be making calls,
tracking down the rods.
I won't make any calls, there isn't
going to be any deal with your partner.
What are you talking about?
Once we have the money,
it's over.
We don't need him anymore.
And we'll be $5 million richer.
You son of a bitch.
I'm not about to get involved
with people who traffic in nuclear arms.
Vladimir, you can't do this.
Why?
This man mean something to you?
I worked for more than a year
to make this deal.
I won't let it go
because you don't have the guts.
This isn't about guts.
This is about being smart.
Really?
Is it smart to keep selling small arms
for the rest of your life?
I bring you the score of a lifetime,
and you piss it away?
For what, $5 million?
- How long is that going to last you?
- Long enough.
You're more than all this.
I know it.
It's why I brought this deal to you.
We can do this.
Together.
Once we've made the deal
and we have the money,
we can be together.
We could start over.
Make our own moves.
But I need my buyer.
Alive.
Sorry.
This is the way I want it.
You'll see.
It's for the best.
What are you doing?
Making a call.
Put down the phone.
I said put it down!
Don't ever go against me!
Renee, you should know that by now.
How much longer?
It's almost done.
There.
The money's in your account.
Thank you, Mr. Meier.
Drop the weapon.
Now! Drop it!
You think I'm that stupid?
That I'd come here alone?
Call your man. Do it!
Give me the phone.
I see we have the money.
Is Meier dead?
No,
I've taken out three of your men,
and I'm ready
to take out the fourth.
You really think
you can roll me for $5 million?
Where's Renee?
She's right here.
She's fine.
I want proof now!
Say something to your partner.
Meier, are you okay?
Satisfied?
Renee told me you were ready to take
your organization to the next level.
- Apparently, she was wrong.
- Not necessarily.
I'm willing
to reconsider the situation.
The only thing
you should consider yourself is lucky.
And I still want this deal to happen.
Otherwise, you'd be dead.
You try something,
we're going to war,
that's the last thing you want.
Let me talk to my man.
Fine.
Bring him back here.
Are you sure?
He wants to see you.
Get up.
Move to the driver's-side door.
Slowly.
I'm sorry, Oleg.
Leave us.
I couldn't let him die.
He's my brother.
And he's my son.
Do you think
this is any easier for me?
It would've worked.
The doctor was treating him.
You disobeyed me, Josef.
You put this family at risk.
You put this family at risk
when you sent those men into the clinic.
They killed three people!
What do you think's gonna happen
when the police start to investigate?
Who are you to question my judgment?
You are my first-born.
You, of all people,
should give me respect.
I do respect you.
But this time you're wrong.
The doctor said
that Oleg could be treated.
He showed me how!
All we need is the medicine!
There are rules, Josef.
They are simple rules.
And they must never be broken!
Never endanger the family, never.
And never disobey my orders.
No, please.
You made me do this, Josef.
Please don't.
I'm sorry, my son.
Get up.
Now, call Father Gregor.
He'll pray over Oleg.
When he's finished,
we'll bury your brother.
Never disobey me again.