Previously on 24
We need to pick him off to
try to save the president.
I'll make a run for
the lockdown room.
There are five
canisters of ch-4.
All we need is
one stray bullet.
A suicide play,jack.
We don't have a choice.
Don't you move!
We have the president!
The president is secure!
I'm so sorry,jack.
I know that he was your friend.
It was supposed to be me.
Juma and his men were
not working alone.
And right now,the only lead
we've got is ryan burnett.
He knew about the attack
on the white house,
And chances are,he's gonna
know who juma was talking to.
I'm thinking about
Bringing olivia on
As a special advisor.
Nobody's forgotten what she
did during the campaign.
Leaking damaging
personal information
About your opponent
to the press.
She's changed.
It's not the past
that concerns me.
Do you think any of this
Would've happened if my
mother had a chief advisor
Who knew what the hell was
going on in her administration?
I just got off the
phone with ethan kanin.
He's ordering me to let
bauer interrogate burnett.
Look,i didn't want to
go behind your back,
But you didn't
leave me any choice.
I want you to clean
out your office
And hand in your badge.
I'm suspending you.
Jack bauer's on his way to
kennedy memorial hospital.
Burnett will tell
him everything.
I have already sent
somebody to the hospital
To deal with burnett.
He can take care of
bauer at the same time.
You lay one finger
on him,it's over.
Right.
Juma's attack failed.
He's dead,so are his men.
Somebody get me the
hell out of here!
You're not going anywhere.
What happened?
What's going on?
Damn it,bauer,open the door!
I want a high-priority
apb issued for jack bauer.
Larry,it's jack. listen to me.
I'm being set up.
Don't let them get
away with this.
This threat is not over.
The following takes place between 9 p.m.
and 10 p.m.
I dropped my wife off
here five hours ago,
And now no one can
tell me where she is.
Mr. o'brian,the white
house has been attacked.
We're in the midst of
an urgent protocol.
Exactly. that's why i'd like to
know if my wife all right.
She is; she's fine.
Where is she?
Tell me.
She's in a holding room
on the third floor.
What...? she's been arrested.
That's absurd.
What's she charged with?
i want to see her.
Listen,i've already told
you more than i should have.
When agent moss
returns,he'll tell you
Everything you need to know.
In the meanwhile,i'm gonna have
To ask you to wait in
the conference room,okay?
Please. i'm sorry.
Please escort him to
the conference room.
Thank you.
Janis,larry's calling for you.
He says it's urgent.
What line? three.
Sign here,verifying
you understand
The terms of your suspension,
And again here...
Agent walker?
Go ahead, i'm listening.
Larry,it's janis.
Ryan burnett is dead.
How?
Bauer was interrogating
him when it happened,
And we're responsible.
You're saying that
bauer killed burnett?
I don't know.
He escaped before
i could get to him.
He called me,said he was being
set up and he wouldn't come in.
I lost him,janis.
I lost him,and it's
on me to find him.
Just tell me what you need.
I already sent out a
priority,all-agency apb.
I need you to
follow up on that.
I'm coming back to
the office right now.
I'll coordinate the search
operation from there.
Okay.
Open an all-agency channel
With flags for immediate
action on jack bauer.
I'll make sure the
local police departments
Are linked in.
On it. thank you.
Janis,what did larry say?
Jack get anything
out of burnett?
You're suspended.
I cannot discuss this with you.
Janis,this was my case.
Tell me if jack got
anything out of burnett.
Burnett is dead.
Well,tell me what happened.
Bauer was there,and
now he's missing.
Janis,the channel's open.
Thank you.
That's all i know,honestly.
So,please,let me get
back to work,okay?
Please attach jack bauer's
profile to the apb.
Got you.
Walker.
Renee,it's jack.
Don't hang up the phone,please.
Whatever they told you,i
did not kill burnett.
Renee?
Yeah.
Bill was right.
There are still very
powerful people
Involved in this conspiracy
that were not named
In dubaku's drive.
They're trying to
cover their tracks.
They killed burnett,and
they're framing me for it.
Even if i wanted
to help you,jack,
Larry has every law enforcement
agency within 100 miles
Looking for you,and i
have been suspended.
All i want you to
do is make an i.d.
I got a frame grab from the
hospital's surveillance.
I sent you a photo
Of the man who
did kill burnett.
It's in your inbox.
Renee,this man is
The only connection i
have to whoever else
Is involved in this thing.
Please,i need your help.
Look,i know you don't agree
with some of thing i did to the
But... i'm telling
you the truth.
Renee?
You know what?
Forget it. i'm-i'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
I'll call you back
at this number.
Metro police,
This is the fbi reporting.
We have a suspect,jack
bauer,that's escaped custody.
All available
units,please respond.
Yes,quinn.
Bauer got away from the fbi.
How?
Well,bauer is
An extremely
impressive operative.
You don't have to tell me that.
But the fbi has launched a
major effort to apprehend him.
He won't be able to
avoid them for long.
Well,we'll see,won't we?
Monitor the situation,keep
me apprised.
Yes,sir.
If bauer connects us to juma,
It could seriously
impede this operation.
Yes,it could.
Is the shipment on time?
Yes. due into port
in the next hour.
Then I don't foresee a problem.
Once the weapons are deployed,
Then it doesn't matter what mr.
bauer or anyone else knows.
Something wrong?
No,sir.
Mr. seaton,I get no pleasure
From the knowledge that
people will die at our hands.
One single soul,the loss of
one soul is tragic to me,
Let alone the numbers
we're talking about!
But do not forget
that every war
Worth fighting involves
collateral damage.
And what we're doing
Is fundamentally and
absolutely necessary!
And I know you understand that!
Of course.
Wake up our colleagues
And have them
assembled in one hour.
And tell them to pack their
pajamas and their toothbrushes.
It's gonna be a long night.
Yeah?
- I have an I.D. - Who is it?
John quinn.
Black ops combat vet.
Served tours all
over the world.
Now he works for starkwood.
The defense consultant?
Uh,yeah,they started
out as consultants,
But over the past few
years,while you were
Out of the country,the
pentagon outsourced
Billions of dollars
in contracts to them.
What kind of contracts?
Manpower.
Starkwood's basically
a private army.
They recruit ex-soldiers
and swat team members
From around the world,
Then they hire them back to
the military security teams.
We're talking thousands of
men deployed here and abroad.
Starkwood work with juma?
Well,if they did,it
wasn't on the books.
But,you know,if anyone
knows,it's senator mayer.
Why mayer?
After he dismantled ctu,
He launched several
other investigations.
One of them has been
looking at starkwood.
What were they accused of?
The hearings are classified,but
Supposedly,mayer has enough
to put them out of business.
Okay,i'm gonna need
to talk to him.
See if you can access
the CIRG logs.
They should have
a location on him.
Okay. i'll send you mayer's
location as soon as i have it.
Thanks.
Agent walker still here?
She was just in her office.
But there's somebody
waiting to see you
In the conference room.
they need to...
Just have a few more
forms to fill out,
Then I'm taking off.
You hear what happened
at the hospital?
After everything that
jack's done today,
Do you really believe
that he murdered Burnett?
I don't know.
I... I don't care.
He's a federal fugitive
and needs to be found.
But you think it's
possible that he did this?
I'm not sure I do.
It's been a long day.
Go home,get some sleep.
- I'll call you in the morning.
- Okay.
Excuse me,Larry.
Morris o'brian is waiting
in the conference room.
He wants to know why
his wife is in holding.
Renee talked to bauer.
How do you know?
Access her phone log
for the last 15 minutes
And get into her workstation,
find out what she's been doing
All right.
If we want to catch
bauer,she's our best shot.
Okay.
We've received confirmation
that president taylor
will be making a statement
to the country shortly.
She is expected to address
the attack on the white house
That ended an hour ago
in a startling rescue.
Now,based on the
few details we have,
We do know the rescue
resulted in the death
Of general juma and
all of his forces.
Angela,how much lead time
does the media need,
Once I'm finished
with my revisions?
The major outlets will
put us on immediately.
I'll be done shortly.
Thank you,angela.
I have a thought
About the speech,if
you'd like to hear it.
Of course.
Right now your main
thrust is reassurance.
The attacks are behind us,
Everything's going to
be back to normal.
But I think you're missing
an opportunity here.
To do what?
Claim victory.
To say that juma's
death means standing up
To tyranny works,and
that your decision
To send troops into
sangala was the right one.
I'm not sure that this is
The appropriate time to
sound triumphant,livy.
A lot of lives were lost today.
And by addressing those
deaths,you give them meaning.
Those people are heroes
Who died in a war that
was worth fighting.
Let's work it in.
Come in.
Madam president,i have
some troubling news.
May i speak with you alone?
You my speak freely
in front of olivia.
Just after the attack
on the white house,
Jack bauer came forward
With a disturbing claim.
He said there were people
Still at large who were
involved in the conspiracy--
Persons unknown
who had helped juma
Plan and execute the attacks.
Did bauer have any
evidence of this?
Nothing concrete.
But he promoted the
notion that ryan burnett
Was our best chance of
identifying these people,
And bauer asked to be
allowed to question him.
This was supposed to be
a controlled situation.
A ploy to intimidate burnett
into giving up intel.
So,I granted bauer's request.
It was a terrible mistake.
What happened,ethan?
Burnett is dead.
My god...
The evidence suggests
That he was killed by bauer.
I don't believe it!
His claim of another party
being involved in the attacks
Appear to have been
a fabrication.
A fabrication.
It may have something to do
with bill buchanan's death;
No one knows.
But madam president,
I take full responsibility.
I was trying to insulate you.
To provide you with deniability
In case anything went wrong.
Or was it because you thought
the president would say no?
Olivia.
Where is bauer now?
At large.
The fbi is devoting its full
resources to the manhunt.
Let me know the
minute they find him.
Yes,ma'am.
Madam president...
I'm sorry.
Looks like everything.
She's on the move.
Where's bauer?
I don't know.
Don't you lie to me.
We traced two calls
from your cell
To a phone that was
reported stolen.
And we know you accessed a
classified government database
And sent someone's name
and address to bauer.
Renee,that makes you an
accessory after the fact.
Now tell me where he is.
I can't.
Damn it!
I still don't believe
that he did this.
Then explain to me why he's
not turning himself in,
And letting us help him find
this mysterious third party.
Because he was framed
and he doesn't trust
Our ability to work through it.
And,you know,after what
we've put him through,
How can you blame him?
You're actually willing To
sacrifice everything to protect him.
Once jack finds the
evidence,he will call us.
You know,janis is
decrpyting what you sent.
It's not going to
take her a long time.
We are going to find him.
Renee,tell me whose
information you sent.
I'll let the A.G.
know that you're cooperating.
I'm sorry,larry.
Put her in holding.
Mirandize her.
Good night,sir.
See you in the morning.
Hello?
Keep your hands where
i can see them,senator.
Bauer.
Take a seat.
I know what you did
to ryan burnett.
I'm not going to let you
butcher me like you did him.
You want me dead,bauer,
You'll have to kill
me where i stand.
If i wanted to
kill you,senator,
You'd be dead already.
Now take a seat!
You're a real enigma,bauer.
An hour after you save the
president from terrorists,
You murder a federal
witness in cold blood.
I didn't kill burnett.
This man did.
Do you know who he is?
No.
His name is john quinn.
He works for starkwood.
What in the world does
starkwood have to do with this?
I don't know yet.
But i do know they sent
someone to kill burnett
And frame me to cover
up their involvement
In everything that's
happened today,
Including the attack
on the white house.
That's a hell of
a theory,bauer.
But you'll have to spin
a better story than that
If you expect it to
get you off the hook.
Senator,i did not come
here to clear my name.
I'm trying to understand
The connection between
juma and starkwood.
There isn't one.
I've spent the better
part of six months
Investigating starkwood.
If there was a connection
to juma or sangala,
I would know it.
I want to see
every file you have
Concerning that investigation.
Look...
Starkwood has let their
security teams run amok
All over the world,with
no oversight.
They've bribed their way
into large contracts,
They've tried to
influence foreign policy
To their own benefit--
all good reasons
Why this country should
not be outsourcing
Its military operations
to private corporations.
And i am going to
shut them down.
But there is nothing
to remotely suggest
They'd be involved in terrorist
attacks on their own country
For any amount of money.
Maybe they have different
reasons for helping juma.
Like what?
I don't know.
Sir,i believe this country
is still under attack,
And there has to be a reason.
And i'm supposed to believe this, Coming
from a man who's holding me hostage?
I need access to those files.
And if the connection
Between juma and
starkwood isn't there,
Will you turn yourself in,then?
Just open the files,sir.
Ladies and gentlemen,
The president will be making
a brief statement tonight.
Good luck,mom.
I'm sure you'll understand,
Based on the events of today,
There will be no opportunity
for follow-up questions.
Ladies and gentlemen,
The president of
the united states.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
My fellow americans,john adams,
The first president to take up
residence in the white house,
Once prayed for
heaven to bestow
Its blessings on this place.
Tonight,those blessings
have seen us through
A brutal attack by
a desperate tyrant.
We have lost friends
and loved ones here,
But we have prevailed.
I have commanded law
enforcement agencies,
Emergency services
and first responders
To keep their
deployment level...
Mr. kanin,ken dellao,cnb.
I'm wondering if you can
confirm some information
I received a short time ago?
Ken,this is clearly
not the time...
Yeah,i'm,i'm going to be Reporting
in this evening's broadcast
That a rogue ex-federal
agent named jack bauer
Is the prime suspect in
the murder of ryan burnett.
...cannot forget
today's events.
The lives we lost...
Where did you get this?
So,it's true,then?
I'm not confirming anything.
I'll also be reporting That you
authorized bauer's release from custody
And arranged for his
access to the victim.
...daughters and
sons,brothers and sisters,
But they have not
taken our spirit.
Make no mistake,today's attacks
Were intended to
crush our resolve.
Mr. kanin.
I said no comment.
But america is not
so easily broken.
Our military action in
sangala has been a success.
At this hour,our forces
have taken control
of sangala city.
We have won.
I see you're back to
your old tactics.
What?
You leaked the story
of burnett's murder
And my involvement
to the press.
Ethan,i don't know what
you're talking about.
Olivia,don't bother denying it.
I can count on one hand
the number of people
Who knew i'd authorized
bauer's release.
So another one of
your errors in
judgment bites you have
And you think you can
lay the blame on me.
Do you realize
what you've done?
In trying to hurt me,
You'll have caused tremendous
damage to your mother.
The president has
gone on record
That torture is unacceptable
under any circumstances.
When this gets out,it will
look like bauer was sent
Exactly for that.
It'll be a political disaster.
You've gone too far this time.
I'm not listening
to you anymore.
I'm not going to let
you get away with this.
Get your hands off me.
As americans,
We should stand together proud
Of what we have achieved.
Thanks to the efforts
and the sacrifices
Of so many,this
place,our national home,
Stands tall tonight.
And all our citizens can sleep
soundly with the knowledge
That the blessings of freedom
continue to shine upon us all.
No,there's been no sign of
bauer in the northeast sector,
So expand your cordon
to the 25-mile mark.
And be prepared
to back up metro.
I'm directing them to begin
random traffic stops,citywide.
Thank you.
I isolated the data
renee uploaded to bauer,
But i can't get past
the file header.
What does that mean?
She encrypted the name
and address she used,
And i can't seem to crack it.
You can't?
she used her personal computer.
This is very
serious encryption.
I mean,there are some high-level
people who can do it. like who?
Chloe o'brian--
but from what you've
told me,she's still
loyal to Bauer.
Is her husband still here?
Yeah. He's waiting to see you.
According to her file,he's
a level-six analyst,too.
Yeah. He's waiting to see me.
I have no idea how much
longer i'm going to be here.
Just do me a favor and
give prescott his babu
Before you put him down.
Yeah,i'm going to have
to call you back. yeah.
Mr. o'brian,i'm larry moss.
Yeah,i'd like to see my wife.
All right.
What the bloody hell
are you holding her for?
Obstruction,evidence tampering.
I think you should be
more concerned about
What you can do to
get her out. sorry?
Help us find jack bauer.
Last i heard from chloe,jack
was working for the bureau.
That's you,if i'm not mistaken.
He was.
Until he snapped and
murdered a federal witness.
Really?
I find that hard to believe.
All that's relevant
here is that your wife
Is going to be prosecuted
for colluding with bauer,
Unless you help us find him.
Mr. o'brian,
A short time ago,
One of our agents was in
touch with jack bauer.
She sent a name and address
That we assume is
his next destination.
Unfortunately,it's encrypted
with blowfish 148.
No one here knows
how to crack that.
Therefore,we need your help.
Please.
Jack bauer and my wife
have a very long history.
I consider him to be a friend.
And he'll have
his day in court.
But the case against your wife
Is rock solid.
I can't.
We're talking about her serving
a minimum sentence of 15 years.
Your son will be 19 by the
time she gets out of prison.
I want guarantees
of full immunity,
No jail time,expulsion of
all charges from her record.
You have my word.
You are a witness
to this agreement.
Yes.
Show me the file.
Original information--
16- or 32-bit word
length? thirty-two.
Native or modified data points?
Native.
The designer of this algorithm
Built a backdoor into his code.
Decryption's a piece of cake if
you know the override codes.
And you do?
Yeah.
Will this take long?
Course not.
Mr. o'brian,can you
tell me specifically
When you'll have
the file decrypted?
Yes.
Now.
Your agent sent jack to
951 deerbrook
avenue,georgetown,
Residence of senator
blaine mayer.
Assemble the field teams.
Tell them we have a
probable location on bauer.
And get metro pd on the way.
No luck reaching
mayer on his cell
or at the house.
The phone company said
The line was
shorted out on-site.
Yeah,that's bauer.
Why is he doing this?
Because mayer spent
the last six months
Trying to send bauer to prison
for the rest of his life.
All right,metro pd is closing
in on mayer's residence.
I've authorized them to move in
As soon as they're in
position and at strength.
I told them,and i'm telling you,it
is impossible to overestimate bauer.
He has more training
and more experience
Than anybody in this room,and
that includes myself.
Okay,let's move.
Agent moss will be
running on-point tactical
with fbi teams on five.
All units must register and
log their com through me,
And i will distribute recognition
codes and credentials.
Chloe... i can't believe you.
You're helping them catch jack.
I did it for you.
This is the last thing
i would have wanted.
How could you do this?
let's see,for a start,
I thought it might be
nice to spare prescott
The inconvenience of having
a convict for a mother.
Jack saved your life.
i don't deny that i owe him.
But my child and my
marriage comes first,
And it should for you,too.
Chloe,love,you've helped
jack enough.
You have.
And you can't go deciding to
make this sacrifice on your own.
But he didn't do what
they're saying he did.
Then he can prove that when
they take him into custody.
If they give him the chance.
At the hearing this morning,you
said you had no regrets
About what you've done.
But what i saw was a
man full of regret.
Of course i
have regrets,senator.
I regret losing my family.
My wife was murdered
because i was responsible
For protecting david palmer
during an assassination attempt.
My daughter can't
even look at me.
Every day,i regret
looking into the eyes
Of men,women and children,
Knowing that,any moment,
Their lives might be
deemed expendable
In an effort to protect
the greater good.
I regret every decision or
mistake i might have made
That resulted in the loss
of a single innocent life.
But you know what
i regret the most?
Is that this world even
needs people like me.
So you think i'm
naive to believe
We need to hold ourselves to
a higher standard of combat?
Doesn't even matter
what i think,senator.
You just need to
understand where i work,
Things get a lot messier than
where you work on the hill.
What you've lost,mr.
bauer,is tragic.
What you've been
compelled to do
In the name of saving
innocent life is tragic.
Sometimes we need to incur
the most horrible losses
In order to uphold the ideals
That this country
was founded on.
How can we presume
to lead the world
Unless we set an example?
You make it sound so simple.
Well,maybe it's
simpler than you think.
Maybe all the things
that you've seen
And all the things that you've
done have cloud of your vision.
Look at this.
Tell me about this
car accident.
That has nothing
to do with juma.
Who was the victim?
A source inside of starkwood.
A whistle-blower.
Unfortunately,he was
also a drunk.
He was killed when
he wrecked his car
On the way home
from atlantic city.
Blood alcohol off the charts.
Senator,this was no accident.
Your informant was
murdered by the same man
Who took ryan burnett
out this evening.
What does this mean,bauer?
They were scared of
what he had to say.
What does your informant
have on starkwood?
He made a lot of
wild accusations,
But not a single one
of them panned out.
Maybe you didn't
dig deep enough.
Senator,i need to know
exactly what he told you.
He alleged that starkwood
Was blackmailing
pentagon officials.
That they were involved
in assassination plots.
Even that they were seeking
to acquire their own wmds.
Specifically what?
Well,i don't
remember,but i'm sure
That his interview
transcript should be there.
Okay,i got it.
Oh,my god.
That's it.
What?
Your informant claims
that starkwood
Was trying to
acquire a bioweapon.
That's your connection to juma.
I don't understand.
When juma was in
power,it was rumored
That he was running an
illegal weapons program.
He was developing a bioweapon,
But nobody could prove it.
But the people that
i knew in sangala
Believed he was testing these
weapons on his own population.
He used a remote village,
Released some kind of pathogen.
Everyone there was
struck with dementia,
Paralysis and eventually died.
Why wasn't this pursued?
'cause juma destroyed
all the evidence.
He firebombed the
village before anyone
Could get there,and
un officials
Had a hard time believing
that juma had the technology
Or expertise to
develop such a weapon.
But starkwood... they had both.
The technology
and the expertise.
And what did juma have
to offer starkwood?
A safe haven to
develop the weapon
And an endless supply of
victims to test it on.
Even if all this was
true,why in the world
Would starkwood
want a bioweapon?
Senator,you've been trying
to dismantle starkwood
For the last six months.
Maybe they planned
on fighting back.
But regardless,if they
have a weapon like this,
You better believe
they intend to use it.
Senator mayer!
This is metro pd!
Don't you move.
Hold on. hold on!
You're obviously
on to something.
They can help you
Find the evidence you
need to prove your case.
Right now everyone thinks
i killed ryan burnett.
- No one's gonna listen to me.
- i can protect you.
I can order them to help us.
Starkwood infiltrated
the white house.
As soon as they find out
you're going after them
For a bioweapon,they'll
bury the evidence.
Then we'll keep
the circle small.
I can make this happen.
It's time for you to start
trusting the institutions
That you've sacrificed
so much to protect.
Trust isn't my greatest asset.
Son,you have to
start somewhere.
Senator!
This is metro pd!
You really think
you can do this?
I know i can.
Let 'em in.
Coming!
No!
You wanted to see me?
Yes,livy.
Ethan just come to me with
something very disturbing.
I assume it's about the press
leak regarding jack bauer.
Ethan seems to think you
had something to do with it.
I didn't.
I already told him that.
Well,given the past experience
Between the two of
you,he's not convinced.
And what do you think?
I think i need to hear
what you have to say.
There's nothing she can
say,madam president.
She was one of the few people
Who knew all the details.
More people knew
than you think.
I just got off
the phone with the
white house secretary producer
At cnb.
He won't give me
the source's name,
But he's willing to confirm
That the leak came from
someone inside the federal
Marshal's office.
He'll guarantee it didn't
come from the white house,
Or from me.
This is verifiable?
Producer's name is
charlie isakson.
Here's his number.
You can call him
yourself if you'd like.
I offered isakson some
Exclusive time with you
if he killed the story,
And he agreed.
So as long as we get
bauer in custody,
We should be able to keep
the fallout contained.
Ethan,under the circumstances,
I think it seems clear
That you were mistaken.
I'm satisfied.
Are you?
Yes,madam president.
I'm sorry,olivia,
If i misjudged
The situation...
And you.
I want to know
If the fbi's any closer
to finding bauer.
Yes,ma'am.
That's all.
I'm sorry
- I put you on the spot like that.
- i understand.
Ethan didn't give
you much of a choice.
I just hope
They find bauer before
this gets any worse.
You're dying.
Just tell me where
The weapons are coming in.
When are they getting here?
They're already here.
Janis,it's larry.
We got here too late.
Bauer murdered senator mayer.
Escalate the search
for him to region-wide.
I want reinforcements
from every branch
Within 50 miles
brought into this.
Copy that.
At this point...
Orders are to shoot on sight.
Yeah.
Tony,it's jack.
Jack,i've been monitoring
the fbi bandwidth.
What the hell's going on?
Listen,man,i need your help.
where are you?
3rd street and b.
Okay,listen to me,i need you
To meet me at the
port of alexandria.
I need you to bring a weapons
and a surveillance package.
- Get there as soon as possible.
- jack,wait.
I can't. i'll get back to
you as soon as i'm en route.