Subtitles: Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu
You know him, don't you?
Mr. Prady, we are in the middle
of a national security crisis.
I have to go back to my desk.
Okay, perhaps if I talk
to your supervisor,
he could let you
take a few minutes off.
It's over.
The parole officer
looking for Kevin is here.
He's after the raw feed.
I'm gonna give it to him.
- Why don't you wait?
- Do you hear me?
He knows everything,
he'll go to Hastings.
Do what he says
and you won't get hurt.
Who is he?
Another traitor?
The only traitor...
is your father.
We haven't disabled
the detectors yet.
- Where are the rods?
- They're still outside the city.
- How will you bring them to me?
- It's been taken care of.
Let's go!
Stop them!
You better take this, it's Kayla Hassan!
She's in a car, she's escaped.
They tried to kill me,
but Tarin got me out.
They shot him.
He told me to call CTU!
Ms. Hassan, my name is Jack Bauer.
We need to know
where you were being held.
We got the location.
Targets are heading north
on Orchard.
They're getting into an SUV.
We ID'd one of the targets
as Tarin Faroush.
Kayla said he sacrificed himself,
but he's still alive.
The car that Tarin got into,
where is it now?
Taking the first exit
of the Williamsburg Bridge.
- You've gotta put Hastings on now.
- I'm on.
You cannot let Kayla Hassan in.
They faked her escape.
They wanted to get her to CTU.
- She's in the tunnel.
- Stop the car!
Put your hands up!
It's an EMP!
What's happening?
Contact NSA.
Terrorists just took out CTU.
Central comm node is totally fried.
- Reroute to peripherals.
- I already tried.
Try again.
I can't have
the status on the drones.
- Everything's down.
- So?
- That they're going to crash?
- Not yet.
The NAV systems
should default to autopilot.
They'll circle
until they run out of gas.
But we've lost all aerial surveillance
and radiological detection.
Basically.
All right.
Agent Skaggs
is heading outside on foot.
Have him contact FAA
with the drones default flight paths.
They need to be taken down
before they crash on the city.
Yes, sir.
You okay?
Am I okay?
An EMP just took us out of play
and we're dropping the ball
on a radiological threat
against New York.
So, no, Chloe,
I am not okay.
And I won't be
until we find those rods.
Sir, Kayla Hassan
is finished in Medical.
I need her taken back to the UN
so she can be evacuated.
- I'll do it.
- No, I'll do it.
I need you to assemble division heads.
We have a briefing in 10 minutes.
Tell them to come
with full damage reports.
Their systems are down.
They can't generate reports.
Then tell them to use a pen
and a legal pad.
- Phil Holden.
- It's Jack Bauer.
So you're back in play.
I don't have a lot of time,
Listen to me carefully.
There's an IRK cell trying to smuggle
weapons-grade uranium into the city.
I just read the assessment.
It says you've got
a CTU team tracking them.
Yes, but we lost them.
CTU just got hit
by some electromagnetic pulse device,
wiped out all our visual incom.
I want you
to try and locate our hostiles.
We don't have any birds
over the metro area.
All aerial surveillance
was being routed through CTU.
And the traffic cams?
I can try.
The hostiles last location?
The West Broadway/
Roebling Street exit.
They're in a gray SUV.
I'll call you if we get a hit.
I also need you to shut down
all bridge and tunnel traffic.
- Done.
- Thanks.
- Where are you going?
- NSA's shutting all the traffic.
There's only one way
for them to get in.
Across the East River.
That's right.
- CTU is down.
- You have confirmation?
I have a real-time uplink
to the power grid.
It recorded a pulse surge
and now nothing.
CTU is blind, deaf, and dumb.
- Have you secured this area?
- Yes.
- You've done well.
- Thank you.
Load the rods.
I realize
this was very difficult for you.
But Hassan's daughter
was a necessary sacrifice.
Using her was the only way for us
to get the rods into the city.
Agents Beck and Henderson
will escort you back to the UN.
Tell me what's going on.
Agent Beck will brief you.
Once you're there, we'll need you.
Your father gave us a file
of IRK covert agents
operating in this country.
We need you to identify
the men working with Tarin.
I'm not doing anything
until you tell me what's happening.
The car you drove here was rigged
with an EMP device.
It's a pulse weapon
designed to disarm electronics.
It's crashed all our systems.
I don't understand.
Tarin put me in that car.
He used you.
He staged your escape,
put you in that car,
and sent you back here.
But he was shot.
I saw him.
He is alive.
We spotted him a few minutes ago.
It's a lot to take in,
but you need to go with these agents
back to the UN
and start looking through those files.
You've seen these terrorists.
If you can help us,
we stand a chance of finding them
before they carry out their attack.
Ahman has prepared the bomb.
It'll be short work
once we get the rods
across the river.
A vehicle is coming.
- Where is it?
- It's coming from the east.
Black SUV, no markings.
- How many men have you got?
- Three.
Wait until the SUV's in the range,
then take them out.
Let's go!
- Hold on.
- What is it?
Thought I caught something.
Heat source down by the water.
- Now it's gone.
- See if NYPD can get some units here.
I'll contact NSA, see if they've got
surveillance of the area.
That's weird.
I got four bars,
but the call's not going through.
Me neither.
We're being jammed.
They're here. Damn it!
Get down now!
Come on!
The engine's down.
Pass your weapons up front!
Take the sniper to your north.
Maintain coverage until we're clear.
Get ready to unload all the weapons
from the back, you ready?
How did they know
where to look for us?
They must have followed us.
Use your infrared!
Call out the snipers as you see them!
Ten o'clock, high and low!
I'm counting four men.
I recognize one from the hospital.
He was the one that talked Marcos
out of detonating the vest.
It's Jack Bauer.
Ex-CTU.
He was one of their best agents.
Nine o'clock low!
We can still cross with the rods.
As long as we're certain Bauer
and his men cannot warn anyone.
It's not a risk.
We started jamming their comm
as soon as they were in sight.
Now they can't leave.
Not with the snipers in position.
Good.
Make sure none of them
get out alive.
I'll call you
when we're across the river.
Let's move.
Reloading!
I've got two men,
leaving the dock in a boat.
Tarin's in it.
They're carrying a box
the right size and shape for the rods.
Copy that!
Went out of my range. We got to notify
NYPD before they cross the river.
I tried cell and radio frequencies.
They're all jammed.
There's a call box
mounted on the building. Ten o'clock.
It's gotta be a hard line.
We can call from there.
How do we get there?
The shooters will pick us off
one by one as soon as we step out
from behind the vehicle.
Our vehicle's armored.
We can use the panels for coverage.
Start now!
Casualty reports are also coming in.
Three fatalities from the bomb blast
in the motor pool tunnel.
- What else?
- Minor injuries for the most part.
Agent McCallan was burned
in a small electrical fire.
- How is he?
- He'll be okay.
But with our infirmary down we had
to transport him to the local hospital.
- Says here we have flooding.
- The pumps are down,
and certain sections of the basement
have about six inches of water.
Can you stop it
or are we all going to drown?
The repair crew's working on it.
Give me an update in 20 minutes.
- Excuse me, sir?
- What is it?
The NSA is here.
NSA?
Brian Hastings, director of CTU.
Frank Haynam, senior engineer
at the New York field office.
- You've been hit by an EMP?
- That's right.
I hope you're here to help
because we can use it.
We are indeed.
Brought my best men with me.
We'd start by restoring your aerial
surveillance and communications.
- Where's your server room?
- Downstairs.
I'll let my team know you're here.
You boys can put your heads together.
I prefer to work with my own people.
There's no one more familiar
with this facility than my crew.
Not exactly true.
I was part of the group
that helped design this place.
Can't say I'm thrilled
with what you've done with it.
How did you find out we were hit?
Jack Bauer called our regional HQ.
Told us your situation.
Bauer was pursuing the men
behind this attack
when we lost contact.
Do you know where he is?
NSA's been trying to call him back.
He's not answering.
They're not sure why.
Right this way.
We should be reporting damages.
What are you doing?
There may be a way to tap in,
get some of our systems running.
How?
I haven't figured it out yet,
and I won't if you keep talking.
All right, people, listen up.
This is Frank Haynam,
senior engineer
of the NSA's New York field office.
Now, he and his team
are going to help us restore
aerial surveillance
and communications.
So we can get back
to tracking the nuclear rods.
They also brought along
a fresh batch of cell phones.
Give them your full cooperation.
Whatever they need, make it happen.
Now, we have been knocked down,
but I promise you,
we are going to get back up.
Let's get to work.
Agent Blochard,
can you get them
down to the server room?
Has NSA heard from Jack?
They spoke with him 20 minutes ago,
but there hasn't been any contact since.
- Why not?
- They don't know.
He could be in some kind of trouble.
Send men out looking for him.
Even if I had agents available,
I wouldn't know where to send them.
He was heading toward the East River.
That's 4 square miles of Real Estate...
too much for me to commit resources
that we don't have.
He was pursuing the terrorists.
He's our best chance.
We'll focus on our efforts here.
When everything's back,
- we'll find them.
- It might be too late.
If anyone can take care of themselves,
it's Jack.
Now, go to the server room,
make sure Haynam has all he needs.
Worse than I thought.
90% of these components are fried.
We're going to have to swap them out
and install new server boards.
Mr. Haynam.
Chloe O'Brian. Mr. Hastings wanted me
to make sure you have all you need.
We're fine, Ms. O'Brian. Thank you.
You'll use the CLR processor?
We'll isolate it from the main servers
and create a brand-new subnet.
Creating a brand-new subnet
from scratch? That'll take forever.
Thanks for offering your help.
We'll take it from here.
I think there's another way.
I've been looking at the schematics.
- Tap directly into the trunk line.
- I'm not that insane.
We need to make sure
those nuclear rods
don't get into the city.
- My suggestion will be a lot faster.
- Or make things a whole lot worse.
How?
Reopen that without system buffers,
you could cause an overload,
wind up electrocuting yourself,
not to mention starting a fire.
I'm aware of the risks.
I think I can create a workaround.
You couldn't keep an EMP
from taking out your operation.
Forgive me if I don't bow
to your expertise.
If you'd stop with the insults
and just listen to me.
I'm not here to brainstorm.
But to clean up your mess.
You need to leave.
Now.
I said now, Ms. O'Brian.
I won't ask you again.
Start prepping the CLR
for a diagnostic.
Is there any other way to get into
the trunk line besides the server room?
That's the only way in. Why?
I think I have a faster way
to get us back online,
but Haynam says it's too dangerous.
I think he's a raging egomaniac.
Seems to be a prerequisite
for engineers these days.
You talk to Hastings?
He'll just shoot me down.
Maybe not.
And maybe the moon will fall
from the sky.
Just let it go. These NSA guys
seem to know what they're doing.
- And if they don't, what about Jack?
- What's Jack got to do with this?
Never mind.
- Hello?
- Renee, it's Chloe. Where are you?
At Jack's apartment.
What's going on?
Everything. CTU was hit by an EMP.
All of our systems are down.
It's a real mess.
- How did that happen?
- I can't go into it right now,
but we think the terrorists were trying
to take out our radiological detectors.
- Where's Jack?
- He might be in some kind of trouble.
Slow down, Chloe.
What do you mean?
Jack was tracking the terrorists
when the EMP hit.
He called NSA
and they lost contact, too.
- Does Hastings know about this?
- He's the one who told me.
What's he doing about it?
Nothing.
He won't send anyone out
to look for them.
He says he can't spare the men
and that Jack can take care of himself.
Where was Jack
before you lost contact?
He took the first exit
off the Williamsburg Bridge.
I'm going to try to find him.
Get CTU back online ASAP.
Get Jack's position,
- and direct me to him.
- That might take a while.
NSA brought in a repair team
and they're going about it all wrong.
I have a faster way
to get us back online.
Tell them.
I tried. They won't listen.
Then make them listen.
Do what you have to do.
Okay. I will.
Call me when you're back up.
The EMP took out all of our systems.
And since we don't know
how long it's going to be,
we'll to have to evacuate
all nonessential personnel.
Follow Agent Combs
through our access tunnel.
I need to speak with Mr. Prady.
Thank you.
Please.
I'm really sorry
it took me so long to get back to you.
I've been busy.
They briefed me on what happened.
It's a terrible thing.
And I have some bad news
because of it.
The video that you wanted
has been erased by the EMP.
Erased?
Everything in the building
has been fried.
That's a damn shame.
So what you're telling me
is whoever helped Kevin Wade
rob that evidence locker...
they just caught a huge break.
I'm afraid so.
Are you sure that it was all erased,
Ms. Walsh?
- Don't you have a backup system?
- Yes, yes, we do, but it's on-site.
All the servers
have been wiped clean.
I know how much Kevin means to you.
I really wish I could do more.
So you're sure
there's nothing else you can tell me?
Anything that would
help me find Kevin?
I have told you everything I know.
I'm sure you have.
I really have to go.
Good luck finding Kevin.
I hope that he's okay.
Me, too.
If anything changes
with those files,
I'll be in Little Rock. Call me.
Of course.
I hope you get your lights back on.
I think I found a way to deal
with the safety concerns about my idea.
Here's the workaround.
I thought I made myself clear.
We'll nowhere near that trunk line.
I'm going to ask you one last time.
We really need to do this my way.
We have agents closed to finding
the nuclear rods, they need our help.
And I'll ask you one last time.
Get out of here.
Get out or I'll call security!
You get out.
Now.
All of you, get out now.
Take a second to think.
Do you really want to do this?
Mr. Haynam,
I don't want to hurt you.
You're probably an okay guy
when you're not at work.
And you're wearing a wedding ring.
I swear to God,
if you don't leave right now,
I will shoot you.
Get out!
Go!
Go get Hastings
and tell him to bring security.
They're starting to flank us!
We're almost there!
- They're almost on us. We gotta leave.
- Just give me one more second.
Okay, I'm ready.
We'll use these plates to form a way
so we can make it over to the call box.
Remember, we need to move
slow and steady.
We must stick together.
- Understand?
- Yes, sir.
Bear the shooting,
this armor is gonna protect us.
Trust that.
Cole, you're with Agent King.
Owen, you're with me.
Let's go!
- The armor's not gonna hold up.
- Yes, it is.
Maintain formation.
- Can you get a shot?
- Not from this angle.
- It's not holding up.
- Yes, it is. Slow down!
We're almost there. Move!
Forget him for now.
- We can't just leave him there.
- We don't leave our men behind.
You try and bring him in, you're dead.
They're trying to draw us out.
Best thing we can do is make it
to the hard line and call for help.
We're almost there.
You cover the north, Owen the east.
I can get there.
Cover him!
I'm sorry.
I couldn't leave him behind.
You did great.
Is he all right?
Did he make it?
Did he make it?!
He made it.
Come on. Stay with me.
Jack, they're repositioning.
Stay on them.
Are you all right?
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm okay.
I'm so sorry.
You were right about Tarin.
I should have listened to you.
You are safe.
That's what's important.
CTU is preparing
a subterranean evacuation route.
If there is a radiological attack,
you'll be shielded underground.
- When do we leave?
- As soon as possible.
President Taylor's waiting for you
with the other delegates.
The files Mr. Hastings request
are inside.
Thank you.
Go with them.
She's strong.
She'll be all right.
We almost lost her.
And I... almost lost you.
All for a peace agreement
that could fall apart at any moment.
And it will only get more difficult.
My enemies will be waiting for me
once we return home.
Despite everything that's happened,
there's one thing I've never doubted.
That what you are doing here
is an absolute good.
You have to be strong, too.
We need to get in there fast
before she can do any more damage.
I understand the situation,
Mr. Haynam.
- How long?
- I need to drill into the mechanism.
Just a couple minutes.
This woman is out of her mind.
Where do you find these people?
She pulled a weapon on me.
- She was ready to use it.
- I seriously doubt that.
She was trying to scare you.
Well, she did a very good job.
- You wanted to see me, sir?
- O'Brian's going off the deep end.
She thinks she knows
how to get the CTU up and running.
But she's locked herself to do it.
We'll be in there in a few seconds.
What's she trying to do?
She's trying to tap directly
into the trunk line,
which is a catastrophe
waiting to happen,
Stop what you're doing!
Let's see the gun.
Don't shoot or anything.
What I did is crazy.
and I'm in a lot of trouble.
You're damned right.
I did it because it could work.
I just need ten more minutes.
- Get her out of here now.
- Let me give the orders.
- She pulled a gun on me!
- I know what she did. Now shut up
and let me handle it.
What were you thinking?
Jack's looking for the rods,
he need our help.
I can get satellite and comm back up
if I finish tapping into the trunk line.
I told Mr. Haynam,
but he wouldn't listen.
So I pulled a gun on him.
I didn't want to.
I don't even like guns.
Dana, what's your take on this?
Mr. Haynam is right.
That's dangerous
and there's no guarantee
that it'll work.
Cole could be in trouble.
Aren't you worried about him?
I am. That's why I can't go along
with your plan. It's reckless.
I'm sorry.
You've never been my fan.
Why start now?
It's not as dangerous
as they're saying.
I've taken precautions.
This can work.
I just need ten minutes.
I can't get the systems online
by then,
fine, arrest me.
You brought me on for this job,
because I didn't think like anyone else.
Ever since I got here,
I've been punished for that.
I've been right
more than once today.
I think I've proven myself
and I deserve that ten minutes.
10 minutes.
You can't be serious.
- You need any help?
- No, just let me work.
Let's give the lady some space.
That's all, gentlemen.
You are making a huge mistake.
Maybe, but I'm willing
to take that chance.
O'Brian proved herself today.
I want to see what she comes up with.
I'd appreciate it
if you and your men would stand by.
- What is it?
- A man wants to speak with you...
He says he's a probation officer.
- Probation officer?
- From Arkansas.
- What does he want?
- He didn't say.
Put him in Holding 2.
Tell him I'll be there in 15 minutes.
Stay here in case O'Brian
needs anything. I'll be in my office.
Mr. Hastings?
We're here, Chloe.
What's your status?
I'm into the trunk line.
I'll activate the bypass circuit.
What can we expect?
If I don't electrocute myself,
some primary systems
should start booting up.
All right, whenever you're ready.
We've got power to comm.
And one of the sat links
is back online.
Good enough.
Look for Bauer.
Chloe, it's working.
- You all right?
- I need more minutes.
I'll be right there.
Mr. Hastings, one more thing.
If you do locate Jack,
you need to call Renee Walker.
She went out looking for him.
She should be in the vicinity.
Will do.
Why don't you go see
if Miss O'Brian needs a hand?
And be civil this time.
Come on, Owen.
Stay with me.
He's gone.
I lost two of the snipers. If we'll make
a move, we got to do it soon.
We can't lay down cover fire
for something we can't see.
Give them something to shoot at.
I'll make a break to the north,
draw their fire, run for the call box.
That's a suicide play.
You'll never make it.
But you will.
- I can't let you do that.
- I'm in command here.
That's what gonna happen.
Do you understand?
- I need you to do me a favor.
- What is it?
You make sure
that Hastings keeps his promise.
That he doesn't bring Renee back in.
I give you my word.
You won't have long
before they fire on you.
Good luck, Jack.
You make it to that call box.
Go.
Clear!
It's okay.
It's me, Renee.
They got the fuel rods in a boat.
They're heading across the river
into the city.
I can't breathe.
Nothing went through.
Relax.
You may have a collapsed lung...
I got through to CTU.
They got back online.
NYPD's sending choppers.
We get a good shot at finding them.
Mr. Hastings,
I just got a call from Agent Ortiz.
The nuclear rods are on a Zodiac
with two terrorists aboard.
They were heading northwest
across the river toward the city.
- Where are the choppers?
- A second.
- They arrived.
- Redirect them.
Start diverting all available NYPD units
to that shoreline.
We need to lay down a cordon.
- Thanks. You were...
- I'm not good with praise.
What do you think you're doing?
My job.
I've answered all your questions.
Why won't you just leave?
I can't do that.
I know you were involved
with that robbery, Ms. Walsh.
What?
I think you know exactly where Kevin is.
I think you're protecting him.
- You are out of your mind.
- And you're a liar.
I'm not leaving here
until I know the truth.
This'll go a lot smoother for you
if you just...
come clean right now.
It's not too late, Ms. Walsh.
But I promise you, if you don't,
I'm gonna nail your ass to the wall.
Contact CTU.
See if they picked 'em up
going across the river.
It's me.
CTU's back online.
I know.
There are helicopters.
They're getting close.
- You should have warned us earlier.
- I didn't have time.
I was too busy preserving my cover.
I don't know how much longer
I'll be able to stay under.
- I thought you took care of it.
- So did I.
It came back.
We can't stay.
The police must already
be cordoning off the area.
- We'll need your help getting clear.
- I will get you out of there.
Don't worry.
Stand by.
I'll call you in a few minutes.