Previously on 24
Have you secured the canister?
I'm afraid not, ma'am.
Our suspect escaped
beyond the perimeter.
I was told that the
area was locked down.
- What happened? - He had help
From Tony Almeida.
Almeida?
He was working for us.
It only appeared that way.
Apparently he was
pursuing his own agenda,
Trying to get his
hands on the canister.
We're all regrouping
to develop leads.
I may have one.
As hodges was taken into custody,
He yelled at me about some larger group
That would continue
on after his arrest.
If that's the case, Madam President,
We need to talk to him.
I need you to call
the attorney general
And draft a witness protection
agreement for Jonas Hodges.
There's no other
way he'll talk.
This man murdered your son, not to
mention Hundreds of innocent civilians.
Is there anything else
that I can do for you?
Other than kill
Jonas Hodges, no.
I didn't mean that.
You know, you're right.
We shouldn't be talking
about this over the phone.
How soon can you be
at the White House?
- How's 15 minutes sound?
- Good.
The plan was to launch simultaneous
attacks early next year in many cities,
So the public would finally see that
the government can't protect them.
They'd demand drastic measures,
and we'd step in.
We were going to supply the enemies
that want to destroy this country.
Muhammed this, Achmed that.
Mr. Hodges, I need the names of the
people that you are working with.
- I don't have them.
- I want the names.
I don't know any!
Another attack today is all we need To
push this thing right over the edge.
This is no time to pull back.
I say we take that canister
- And finish the job off today.
- I'll contact the group.
The attack will be attributed to
this man-- Jibraan Al-zarian.
We're talking about launching a
new operation In the next few hours
And with only one canister.
The plan for this operation
was already in place.
We'd just be accelerating
the timetable.
Jonas Hodges was a loose cannon,
And the group is well rid of him,
But, in his lunacy,
he did us a favor.
I say we take it.
Hamid!
Keep your mouth shut
and no one gets hurt.
- You understand?! - Yes!
The following takes place between 4 a.m.
and 5 a.m.
How much more time do you need?
The material's almost
finished downloading.
Financial records are in place.
I'm gonna need about another 15
minutes to alter the time stamps.
Good.
I'm gonna take this off.
You yell for help,
you and your brother die.
Understand?
Who are you people?
You're putting Jihadi
propaganda on my computer.
These weapons-- you're...
You're trying to make me
look like a terrorist.
Why are you doing this?
Listen to me, jibraan.
There's only one thing
you need to know.
If you don't do
exactly as I say,
You're going to watch your younger
brother die right in front of your eyes.
And then... I'm gonna kill you.
However... if you cooperate...
...there's a good chance the two
of you will live through this.
What do you want me to do?
First off...
You're going to read this
statement in front of a camera,
And you're going to read
it like you mean it.
No, this is insane.
I can't read this.
I'm not going to do this.
Okay, see, that sounds to me like
you think you have a choice.
Please, this is not right.
You can't do this to us.
Okay, fine.
Okay, okay, please,
please don't hurt him.
I'll do whatever you say.
Okay?
I'll give you five
minutes to look that over.
I just finished the first
sweep with the CTU servers.
There's been no chatter,
no activity at all.
You updated the watch list?
Yes, everyone on that list Is already
under surveillance by law enforcement.
If one of them was gonna do something,
We would know about it.
Damn, well, we're going to
have to widen our parameter.
To include what?
I want you to check out every
muslim in the Washington D.C. area.
Target anyone who's working in
a sensitive government position
Or in a place that
might get hit.
Then I want you to
start pulling the files
On every political activist
working in the muslim community.
Also, I want you
to contact INS.
I want a list of every recent
immigrant from an islamic country.
Excuse me,
has anybody heard of racial profiling?
Janis, not now.
No, she's right.
You're right,
this is racial profiling,
And I don't like it any more than you
do, But Hodges told me specifically
That he was going to
utilize muslim extremists
In an effort to offload
the blame for this attack.
I need to know who he's working with,
And we're running out of time.
I don't know a better
way of doing this.
So if you do,
please tell me now.
No.
Okay, thank you.
Chloe, I need you to
run down the list of...
I-I'm sorry,
I forgot what I was saying.
INS records, jack?
Yeah, run those down first
and then work backwards.
Excuse me.
This is the second
time he's done this.
He keeps forgetting things,
he looks like hell.
He's doing pretty
well, considering.
Considering?
Considering what?
He didn't tell you?
Tell me what?
If there's something wrong with jack,
Tell me now.
He's sick, Chloe.
He was infected with
the prion variant.
How?
He was trying to recover the bioweapon
canisters And one of them ruptured.
He was exposed.
Oh, my god.
I'm sorry, Chloe,
he probably didn't want you to worry.
Chloe...
Why didn't you tell
me you were sick?
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter?
I'm your friend.
We need to stay focused
on finding Tony.
Jack, you should be
in the hospital.
There's no treatment for this.
There's no cure.
So you're telling
me you're dying?
Yes.
How long?
A day, maybe two.
I've been taking this anti-seizure
medicine to keep me on my feet.
It's been working so far.
Oh, my god.
I'm so sorry.
Chloe, it's all right.
I've accepted it...
and I need you to
accept it, too.
Whatever time I've got left,
I want it to matter.
We need to find Tony,
put an end to this.
Chloe.
I can't do this without you.
Please, I need you
to go back to work.
Okay.
We strike this blow for
our brothers and sisters
Who have died at the hands
of this corrupt nation.
The hour is here, And we are
ready for the war that is to come.
Our fighters will not rest Until
America lies crippled and dying,
Her streets running with blood,
And her people begging for mercy,
But there will be none...
Only our vengeance.
We have a problem.
What is it?
Police.
Why don't you close down the
computer and get out of sight.
Take everything down
and watch the brother.
You need to come with me.
What is happening?
There are two police
officers outside.
I want you to find
out what they want
And convince them that
everything's okay in here.
Jibraan... don't
try to warn them.
Right.
Open the door, please.
Yes?
"Jibrain" Al-zarian?
Jibraan al-zarian.
Uh, we got a call from
one of your neighbors.
They said they heard some yelling
coming from your apartment?
Saw some people they didn't
recognize enter the premises,
Thought there might
be some trouble.
No, everything is fine.
Those were friends of mine.
And what about the yelling?
We got into an argument.
They were drinking
a little too much.
Uh, it was nothing.
Where are your
friends now, sir?
You know, they got too loud,
so I asked them to leave.
They won't be back.
I'm very sorry for the noise.
Uh... it won't happen again.
I-I promise.
Okay. Just keep it
down from now on.
- I will. - Have a good night.
You, too.
All right, we're clear.
You did good, Jibraan.
We have to finish reading this
statement before we take off.
Where are we going?
Don't worry about that.
You just keep doing as we say,
And you and your brother
Are gonna make it through this,
all right?
Set him up.
And there will be none,
only our vengeance.
And this is only the beginning.
We will strike again and again in the
name Of all that is great and righteous.
I think I've got something.
Agent walker? What is it?
One of the filters flagged
this a few minutes ago.
I just finished vetting it.
These are multiple deposits
over a period of six months.
From an overseas Muslim
relief organization
Called the Islamic
League For World Peace.
A total of two million dollars To
the Washington Continental Bank.
Every penny of it was
withdrawn within 30 minutes.
What name's on the account?
Jibraan Al-Zarian.
He's 27 years old, moved here From
Pakistan on student visa four years ago.
This is his personal
web account.
These are some of the sites
he's been looking at recently.
We got an address on him?
No. This address is false.
It doesn't exist.
That's it, his visa expired.
He's here illegally,
And he probably doesn't
want to be found.
He does have a personal reference -
On his INS form. - Who?
Muhtadi Gohar.
He lives at the G street
mosque in Georgetown.
He's the imam there.
He might be able to
help us find Al-Zarian.
We need to talk to him.
Put out an APB
On Al-Zarian,
run it through the interagency database.
See what else you can find.
Fax everything over to the car.
Great work.
Jack, wait.
Are you sure you're
up for this?
I have to see this through.
Please.
I can help.
Okay. Let's go.
Come in.
Ma'am, Mr.
Collier here to see you.
Thank you, Agent Pierce.
That'll be all.
I appreciate you
coming, Martin.
It's been a long time.
You look good.
Thanks.
So, olivia,
I know why you asked me here,
But I have to tell you, having me dig
up dirt On Noah Daniels is one thing.
This is a whole
different animal.
I'm aware of that, Martin.
I want this to happen.
I want this person taken care of.
It's Jonas Hodges.
- Starkwood? - Yes.
What in god's name do
you have against him?
I don't know how much of this will get
out, But Hodges was behind everything
That happened today,
from the planes going down
To the attack on
the White House.
- What? - It's true.
He's also responsible for
the death of my brother.
I thought your brother
killed himself.
He was murdered,
And Hodges was responsible.
Okay. But why?
It's complicated, Martin,
And I don't have time to go into it.
All you need to know is
Hodges worked a deal.
Witness protection.
My mother approved it,
and he's going free...
Unless someone intervenes.
- Okay, can I give you a little advice?
- What?
This is big game. Walk away.
I can't do that.
Once this happens, Once it goes through,
you can never go back.
You will live with it for
the rest of your life.
I don't need a lecture on
conscience from you, Of all people.
I have thought this through.
What I can't live with Is that
monster getting away with this.
He has to pay for what he did.
So, uh, where's Hodges now?
In FBI custody,
downtown Bureau.
Deal has been signed.
He's being released into witness
protection Within the hour.
Here's his itinerary.
When he walks out that door,
we lose him.
He disappears forever.
This has got to happen fast.
Martin.
All right.
I'll make a call.
I'll get you contact information,
a price,
And instructions on how
to transfer the funds.
Thank you.
You'll hear from me soon.
Mr. Hodges, This is U.S.
Marshal Sullivan.
I'm placing you in his custody.
He'll take you to
witness protection.
Thank you for your hospitality,
young lady.
This dossier outlines your new identity,
Your new place of residence,
All the information you're going
to need to make this transition.
Robert Tippett?
That's my new name?
Yes, sir.
Sounds like a dog breed.
Our first stop is the Witt-Sec
facility in Colorado.
We'll put the finishing touches on your
new biography, Fabricate your new ID,
Get you into counseling.
Counseling?
It helps entrants deal with
their new circumstances.
Son, you know who I am.
Do I impress you as someone who needs
therapy To cope with new circumstances?
The service is available if you want it,
sir, Courtesy of the American taxpayer.
You think I'm getting off easy,
don't you?
I don't think anything.
I can smell attitude, son,
And you're giving it off pretty thick.
I've lost everything--
My company, my family,
And most importantly, my name.
You know how much blood and sweat went
into making that name mean something?
We leave for Andrews Air
Force base in 30 minutes.
I suggest you get ready.
Jack?
I'm fine.
What are you doing? We don't even
know that they've done anything yet.
They could be innocent.
Innocent? You heard Hodges.
They're gonna use sleeper cells
to carry out these attacks.
Al-zarian might not have
been knowingly complicit
About everything that happened today,
But innocent? No.
Yes?
This is agent Walker with FBI.
Mr. Gohar?
Yes.
We're sorry to bother you at such
a late hour, But we need your help.
My help?
To stop a potential
terrorist attack.
Mr. Gohar?
I know you.
My name is jack bauer.
Of course.
I watched your
testimony on television.
Sir. Can we talk to you inside?
Please.
What do you want?
We're looking for a
man who worships here.
We believe he may be Helping
to plan another attack
That may be happening soon,
in D.C.
I knew the blame would
eventually fall on us.
His name is Jibraan Al-Zarian.
Do you know him?
And why do you think
he's a terrorist?
He fits a specific profile.
You mean, he is a muslim.
He's a pakistani national.
His visa lapsed a year ago.
And he has no legal address.
He listed you as a personal
reference on his INS form.
Where someone worships is private
information, protected by law.
Right now, finding al-zarian
Is the only way we're going to
prevent an attack against civilians.
So, I ask you again,
sir, do you know him?
Look at the photo!
Yes, I know him.
But he is not a terrorist!
What makes you so sure?
Jibraan has come to me many
times for spiritual advice.
I know the man.
He is not violent and
he is not an extremist.
We have evidence that
indicates otherwise.
I would like to
see this evidence.
Listen to me.
We did not come here to
debate this with you.
Where does he live?
I don't know where he lives.
- Where does he work? -
I don't know that, either.
And I don't believe you!
But you expect me
to believe you?
I watched your hearing at the senate,
I know what you have done.
So, tell me why should I
believe anything you say to me?
First because you
don't have a choice.
Second, because I am
telling you the truth!
The truth is that you come
into a house of worship
With information
you should not have,
An outrageous accusation,
no legal warrant, and threaten me.
I have not threatened you.
Not yet.
But we both know
where this is going.
If you're so sure
he's innocent,
- Why are you afraid to tell
us where he is? - Jack...
Where is he?!
I told you, I don't know.
But even if i did,
I would say nothing.
I would not help you
arrest an innocent man.
This is agent Walker.
It's Janis.
A DCPD officer recognized Jibraan
Al-zarian from a domestic
disturbance call
he took 15 minutes ago.
The address is 2700 eastbrook,
Apartment 3.
All right, good.
Coordinate with DCPD.
Set up an envelope and put the
building under surveillance
We'll be there in 10 minutes.
We have an address
on Al-zarian.
- Let's go, Jack.
- Turn around.
- Why? - I said turn around.
- Put your hands up, now!
- Jack?
What are you doing, Jack?
I'm not letting him call
Al-zarian Before we get there.
- He's coming with us.
- You have no right!
- I have done nothing wrong!
- Shut up!
...there will be none,
only our vengeance.
And this is only the beginning.
We will strike again and again In the
name of all that is great and righteous.
All right, fine.
The staging team's
ready and waiting on us.
This'll be uploaded
in two minutes.
Good.
Jibraan...
We're getting
ready to move out.
I'm gonna need you to
talk to your brother.
Tell him what we discussed.
Go ahead and wake him up.
Please, I can't do this.
Yes, you can.
And you will.
How do I know you won't
kill Hamid anyway?
Because we need him to tell the police
That his brother's a terrorist.
Believe me,
You're saving his life by doing this.
Now, come on, let's go.
Hamid, Hamid, calm down.
Don't be scared.
Jibraan, what is this?
Sorry we had to do it this way.
But you're not going to
be hurt anymore, okay?
We? Who is we?
What's happening?
I'll explain everything
to you, okay?
Who's he?
Um, he's a friend.
Your friend?
I know all your friends.
I've never seen him before.
That's because I have
kept him from you.
What are you talking about?
I have to tell you something.
I'm not the person
you think I am.
What?
I hate what this country
has done to our people.
And I'm working with these men.
They will help me strike back against
the evil that has been done to us.
Strike back?
I can't say any more than that.
I don't believe it.
This country brought us in, gave us
a home, That's what you always said.
Yeah, that was a lie.
I have been protecting you from
this rage I've always felt inside.
But now it is time for
you to know the truth.
It was the Americans who
killed our parents, Hamid.
I'm going to make them pay.
What have you done
to my brother?
You've poisoned his mind!
This isn't my brother!
They have not done
anything to me, okay.
It is very important you
accept what I'm saying to you.
Why are you telling me this?
When they ask you why I did what I did,
I want you to tell them.
Okay, no one will
blame you for anything.
You have done nothing wrong.
I know this is very difficult
for you to understand.
But over time, you will see.
I love you, Hamid.
You said today was a
bad day to be a muslim.
Well, it's an even worse
day to be your brother.
All right, let's go.
Staging area's ready.
You stay here and finish up.
Understood.
Jibraan, don't do this.
Everything set?
Yeah, was the
brother convinced?
I'm not sure.
But even if he wasn't,
Once the attack happens, he will be.
Let's go.
Hello?
Yes, yes, martin collier said
you'd be expecting my call.
He gave me the
target's itinerary.
I'm set to go.
Good. good,
so the terms are acceptable.
They are.
I just need you to
transfer the funds.
What's the account number?
International banking code
is Victor-six-bravo-one-bravo-one.
After the funds have been transferred,
I'll proceed.
There'll be no need for us
to have any further contact.
All right, but what are you--
Yes?
Excuse me, Ms. Taylor.
I thought you should know your
father has asked to see you.
My father's here?
In light of the potential
bioweapon attack,
The president ordered him moved to
the white house for his safety.
Thank you, Aaron.
I just have something
to take care of.
Tell them I'll be right there.
Yes, ma'am.
You've reached Martin Collier.
Please leave a message.
Martin, it's Olivia Taylor.
I spoke to the contact,
But I couldn't go through with it.
I decided to take your
advice and walk away.
Please call me as
soon as you can.
This is Bauer.
It's Chloe, I found something weird
about these hits on Jibraan Al-zarian.
Go ahead.
You know how I said that the two million
dollars Was deposited into his account
Over a period of six months?
Well, that wasn't right.
They were backdated.
What do you mean?
One of the trace algorithms
caught a discrepancy,
All that money was really just
deposited 30 minutes ago.
What about the extremist
websites he was visiting?
Same thing with
the time stamps.
The hits were backdated
30 minutes ago.
Are you absolutely positive?
It looks that way.
Jibraan could be innocent.
Okay, thanks.
What's going on, Jack?
Chloe found evidence that
Jibraan is being set up.
He's been framed.
Why would Almeida
frame an innocent man?
Because they wouldn't want to risk the
attack Not being carried out properly.
How could I be so stupid?
An innocent man is so
much easier to control.
All they needed was a muslim, They could
create whatever background they wanted.
Give me your hands.
I am surprised.
Why? You were right.
Not about Jibraan.
My experience with
the authorities,
The police is that they will go to any
lengths Not to admit they were wrong.
Even at the expense of
an Innocent man's life.
At least you didn't do that.
Please know that I forgive you.
I'm not asking for
your forgiveness.
Then i hope you can at
least forgive yourself.
I gave up on that
a long time ago.
It's never to late to turn towards god,
Mr. Bauer.
- That's enough?
- Yeah, thanks.
Thank you.
You don't need to
stay with me, Ally.
But they know where to
find me if they need me.
I thought it was important for
you to hear what's going on.
And for you to understand
why I did what I did.
You're the
president, sweetheart.
You don't owe me
an explanation.
There's my girl.
Hi, dad.
Livy, you can
squeeze a bit harder.
I won't break.
Oh, I might!
I'm sorry I couldn't
come to the hospital.
Don't be silly.
You're a godsend being
here helping your mom.
Just knowing you two
were speaking again,
Let alone working together,
that's enough.
Henry, I'm not sure that our
d¨¦ente Is holding at the moment.
Olivia, your mother told me About
the deal she made with Jonas Hodges.
And I know you, understandably,
Have serious concerns about that.
Well, I've had some
time to think.
To put myself in
mom's position.
To be objective And pragmatic--
The way a good
leader should be.
Has to be.
I know that decision
was horrible for you.
But I do understand.
I'm sorry I made the
choice even harder.
Jonas Hodges will face
judgment one day.
If not in this life,
in the next.
Mr. Tippet.
Oh. sorry.
It's going to take me a little
while to get used to that.
Always does.
I'll need to
confiscate the wallet.
We can't let you hold on to anything
That ties you to your former life.
And the picture.
You like your job,
Mr. Sullivan?
It has its challenges.
You strike me as someone
who wouldn't be totally satisfied
ferrying prisoners around.
I don't plan on doing
this my entire life.
Good to hear that.
Maybe you and I can do some
work together some day.
Sir?
I don't intend to be Mr.
Tippet forever.
Sign here
acknowledging transfer.
FBI's identified
The man they believe is going to
carry out e bioweapon's attack.
Jack Bauer and agent Walker are on their
way To a possible location for him.
Have they found out anything that
would give us an idea of the target--
- Or a timetable? - No.
Nothing actionable. Not yet.
Um, Madam president.
This is woods.
Are you sure?
How did this happen?
Call me as soon
as you know more.
What is it, Tim?
Jonas Hodges was just killed.
- What? How?
- Car bomb.
As he was leaving FBI.
What else do they know?
- Are there any suspects?
- Not yet.
Um, excuse me.
My guess is this
was an inside job.
Inside job?
Whoever ordered the hit
Knew exactly when and where
hodges was being transported.
Damn it!
Tim, get on top of this.
I want to know exactly
how this happened.
Yes, ma'am.
Ms. Taylor,
Is everything all right?
Oh, it's fine.
I'll be right back.
Yeah?
Hodges is dead!
Okay, calm down.
We shouldn't be
talking on the phone.
You don't understand,
There's been a terrible mistake.
I spoke to the man whose
number you gave me.
But I didn't go
through with it.
I couldn't.
Didn't you get my message?
Olivia, I said calm down.
I can't!
Hodges is dead and
I'm responsible.
We cannot have this
conversation over the phone.
Do you understand? Do you realize What
could happen to me if this gets out?!
Olivia, you need to
stop talking now.
Do you hear me?
Take a deep breath,
listen to me.
All right, we'll hang up, okay?
All right.
Okay, I'm listening.
Okay.
Can you get to Pershing Park?
No, not right now.
I'm in a meeting
with my mother.
Fine. I'll wait.
Get there as fast as you can.
We'll talk about
this face-to-face.
Okay?
All right.
Thank you, Aaron.
What do you have, agent?
Armed hostile in the back room,
holding a hostage.
What about Almeida?
He's not in there.
See for yourself. Reed, -
Give us another look. - Yes, sir.
Move in closer on the hostage.
Is that who you're looking for?
No.
That's Jibraan's
brother, Hamid.
They're using him as leverage,
to make Jibraan Do what they want.
How can you be sure?
'cause that's what
I would've done.
Agent, it is imperative that
we take this hostile alive.
Right now,
he's our only shot at finding out
Where this attack is
going taking place.
Understood. I've
already informed my men.
I want to run point on this.
Is that all right?
Thanks.
You're going to stay here
With the backup teams.
Are you sure that's
such a good idea?
What?
Agent Bauer--
he doesn't seem to be too well.
- Maybe you should be in charge.
- I am.
Jack was infected
with the bioweapon.
The same one that they are
going to use in this attack.
Then he should be
in the hospital.
There is no treatment.
He probably has less
than a day to live.
So if he is strong enough, trust me,
He's the best person for this job.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize.
Agent Walker, we're ready.
Please, Mr.
Bauer, Do what you can to save Hamid.
We've checked the windows.
We have a clear approach.
- Let's go. -
Agents, stay with Mr. Gohar.
On my count.
Three... two... one.
Hamid, stop!
Put it down.
We're FBI. We need him alive.
- Put it down. -
He made my brother into a terrorist.
Your brother is not a terrorist.
He's innocent.
We know that.
He's being set up.
- He's being forced to do this.
Please. - What?
The only one who can tell us
Where your brother is
that man right there.
Now put it down.
Stand up now,
put your hands behind your head.
Do it!
Agent Walker, move in now.
Move! On the bed
Damn it, he's bleeding out.
We need a medic, now!
We need a med team on site.
Sit right there.
Are you in their system?
I've tapped into the main
security trunk line,
But I'm still looping in breakers to
make sure The tap doesn't get flagged.
All right, well,
we're on a timetable here.
How much longer is
it going to take?
Ten, maybe 15 minutes.
Hand me that case.
What are you going
to have me do?
You'll find out soon enough.
Is the subway on schedule?
Yeah, it's on schedule.
¸ü¶àÃÀ¾ç¸üÐÂ ÇëµÇÂ½
www.YYeTs.net