Subtitles: Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu
The people
that you think are responsible
for killing Hassan
were not working alone.
They were being managed
by people working
inside the Russian government.
How do you know this?
I'm being set up.
I need to get this evidence to you.
Arlo got a cell phone intercept
report off NSA's Echelon.
Keywords: "Jack Bauer."
We confirmed the voiceprint.
Reed's connection to Hassan means
she'd be highly motivated to help him.
Take it to the press.
His next move.
This is a major opportunity
to make everything go away,
Bauer and the evidence.
I need to find Jack...
Or else they're gonna kill him.
If we can get to him,
we can expose the cover-up.
- Jack is working with someone.
- Who?
I never saw 'em, but Jack showed up
with weapons and comms.
Pavel, do you see Bauer?
- If you have a shot, take it.
- I've got him.
Put it down.
Everything's all clear up on top.
Come with me.
Do exactly what I say.
- Move!
- He knew it was a trap.
The evidence is on this memory card.
Take it.
When you see it, you'll know it's real.
The hit on Hassan is all arranged.
Bazhaev is taking care of everything.
I already know
that you killed Renee Walker.
What I want to know
is the name of the Russian pig
inside your government
that gave the order.
Where's the SIM card?
You dumb bastard, you swallowed it.
This is for my friend.
You've reached the mobile number
of President Charles Logan.
As a principal player in this
unprecedented and historic
peace initiative,
Secretary of State Kanin's
untimely decision
to withdrew for health reasons
was a difficult one.
However,
the president wishes it to be known
that in Secretary Kanin's absence
and per his own recommendation,
she has sought and gained the counsel
of former President Charles Logan.
Now, the president
is acutely aware that this decision
bears some controversy.
But President Logan's experience
with foreign policy
and his skills in negotiation
have already proven to be
a great asset in these final hours
before the signing
of the peace agreement
with the Islamic Republic.
- Once Mrs. Hassan...
- Excuse me, Mr. President.
... and the IRK delegation...
Your car to the heliport
is ready and waiting downstairs.
Has President Suvarov's
plane arrived yet?
It should be soon touching down at JFK,
and then he'll be choppered in
to the 93rd Street Heliport
Thank you.
I'll be down in a moment.
Once Mrs. Hassan
and the IRK delegation
have hashed out a few remaining
points of protocol
with President Taylor,
the signing will commence
as scheduled.
Tell me you have a lead on Bauer.
I'm sorry, sir.
We tracked him to an adjacent building,
but he managed to get out of the cordon,
along with the reporter
Meredith Reed.
Also, he's killed Pavel.
I've taken jurisdictional control
over the scene from NYPD.
We should be able to keep
this contained, but it...
it's not gonna matter if Bauer's
already passed along the evidence
he got from Dana Walsh to the press.
- The story's going to come out.
- No, not necessarily.
We still might be able
to manage this.
I know you've told me that you're
committed to seeing this through,
but you can still extricate yourself.
There's no evidence against you yet.
- You can delay the press announcement.
- It's too late for that.
The White House Press Secretary just
announced my role in the peace process.
There is no turning back.
There's something else
you should know.
Bauer didn't just kill Pavel.
He butchered him.
He beat him savagely,
and then he eviscerated him.
I don't think Bauer's just looking
to expose the Russians' involvement
in the plot against Hassan.
This guy's out for blood.
Then you better find him
and stop him, hadn't you?
Keep me posted.
I'm not going any further till you
tell me what happened back there.
- You killed that man, didn't you?
- Your life is in danger.
You want to get through this alive,
you're gonna do exactly what I say.
Do you understand?
I can't get a locate on the number
you called from this phone.
It's restricted.
I'm gonna have to route a back trace.
- Can you do it here?
- I need the equipment at my place.
Get back to me as soon
as you got a location. Let's go.
Who is it you're looking for?
Someone who can give me
the names of everyone else involved.
- And what are you gonna do then?
- It doesn't concern you.
How can I trust you
if you don't tell me what you're doing?
Because I'm not trying to kill you.
The video file that I gave you
is the only proof of the Russians' guilt
in President Hassan's assassination.
But the conspiracy doesn't end
with the Russians.
There are people in the government
trying to cover this up,
including President Taylor.
Why would the president want this?
Because she's trying to keep
the peace accord alive with the IRK.
And she knows if Dalia Hassan finds out
that the Russians killed her husband,
she'll never sign the agreement.
What do you want from me?
I need you to break the story
in case I don't make it.
I think President Hassan
deserves that.
Let me see your cell phone.
Wait.
What are you doing?
They've seen you with me.
The authorities are going to monitor
your usual forms of communication.
You can't go home
or back to your office.
Is there anyone that you work with
that you trust?
My editor, Gary Klausner.
You need to get him the evidence.
I can get you as far as a pay phone.
After that, you're on your own.
I'm glad we were able
to come to terms.
So am I.
Thank you,
for your patience with me.
I am still new to this.
You are a natural leader, Dalia,
and you have a superb
advisor in Minister Jamot.
I appreciate the endorsement,
Madam President.
Pardon me...
for interrupting.
We were just finishing up.
I'm honored to finally meet you.
I was a great admirer
of your husband.
I'm so sorry for you loss.
Thank you.
President Taylor tells me
you were instrumental
in convincing the Russian to stay
at the negotiating table.
I'm honored to play even a small part
in such an historic event.
May I have a few moments with you?
I'll see you at the signing.
You still haven't found out how Logan
convinced the Russians to stay?
I've investigated it,
but I learned nothing.
Our intelligence service
can look into it.
Thank you.
I trust President Taylor.
We have to assume that if she involved
Logan, it was for a good reason.
The operation to capture Bauer
was unsuccessful.
He got away, along with the evidence
that he took from Dana Walsh.
You said you had
the situation under control.
Clearly, I was overly optimistic.
And in my optimism,
I neglected to tell you that Bauer
made contact with a journalist.
- Meredith Reed.
- My God...
You need to call her publisher
right away.
Deny any foreknowledge
of whatever evidence she has,
and demand
that they do not run the story.
You're suggesting
muzzling the press?
Have you forgotten
that freedom of the press
- is constitutionally protected?
- You are the president, for God's sake.
Invoke national security.
You tell them
this story will start a war.
- Innocent lives will be lost.
- New lies to cover the old ones.
The time has passed
for hand wringing.
If you don't use
the power of your office
to shut this story down,
your peace agreement
won't be the only casualty.
You don't need me
to tell you the damage
that your criminal prosecution
will do
to this country.
This country survived
your presidency.
But it won't survive yours.
Me...
I inherited my presidency.
I was never
nearly as popular as you are.
And most of my alleged misdeeds
never made the press.
But if you...
were to bare your sins
to the people
who put you in office...
You are a beacon of righteousness,
not only for Americans,
but for the rest of the world
You... are the president
who had her own daughter arrested
rather than see justice go unserved.
You're a poison.
I never should have
let you to do this.
With due respect, Madam President,
I gave recommendations,
I made...
whatever arrangements
needed to be made.
But every decision was yours.
Let's not pretend otherwise.
I've studied you
for a number of years, Allison.
I pride myself on being
a good judge of character.
You're a smart woman.
You've always known
what needed to be done
and were willing to do it.
Which is why I know you will call
Meredith Reed's publisher
and make sure he kills the story.
I would suggest you do it now.
You have a signing ceremony
to prepare for.
And...
I need to go meet President Suvarov.
- You need to see this.
- What is it?
I just tapped into a live feed
from Pillar's team.
This guy was found sliced open
in an abandoned building
across from the department store.
He's got Russian papers, but I can't
make 'em out, the rez is too low.
Looks like someone left a sniper rifle
at the scene.
What's the caliber?
Bring it up.
They tagged it as a 308 Springfield.
That's the gun that killed Renee.
That's got to be the shooter.
Jack did this, and you still think
you're gonna be able
- to talk him down?
- I gotta try.
Pillar are just gonna kill him,
I can't let that happen.
Got a match from the department store
security feed: 82%.
- That's the guy helping Jack?
- James Ricker.
Ex-Green Beret, Special Ops.
He served with Jack in the Gulf
before Jack was enlisted by CTU.
Just one problem.
He's dead.
It says he died in a chemical plant
explosion in Basra 7 years ago.
Then he must have a twin who was there
when Jack reversed the ambush.
You better go back to your station.
Pillar's watchdog is getting suspicious.
Cross-reference Ricker's photo
with State DMV database.
He must be living under an alias.
We find him, we find Jack.
- You get the location?
- You didn't tell me that was
- Logan's phone that I was tracing.
- Does it matter?
Yeah, it kind of does.
I think you know it, too,
or else you would've been
straight with me.
Taking out a bunch of Russian spooks
is one thing,
moving on an ex-president,
that's quite another.
That's a seriously line
you're crossing there.
I know what I'm doing. Are you gonna
give me the location or not?
Logan's in a vehicle.
He's moving west from the U.N.
I'm syncing up with the Secret Service
deployment grid.
- I'll upload his route to your tablet.
- Hold on.
Okay, I've got it.
I sure hope
you know what you're doing,
because this path you're on,
there ain't no coming back from it.
I wasn't planning on coming back.
You're right, you've already done
more than I had a right to ask for.
I want you to erase
all your connections to me.
Thanks for everything.
Goodbye.
That's all you need?
Should I call the doctor?
It's just a headache. I'm fine.
You wanted to see me?
Please sit down.
You remember the reporter
CTU arrested last night?
It has been brought to my attention
that she intends to publish
an unfounded story
regarding Omar Hassan's murder.
What is she gonna be writing?
I need you to contact the FBI,
have them search
the Sunday Magazine offices,
locate Reed,
and seize whatever evidence
she purports to have.
I don't understand.
Her allegations are false,
but the allegations alone
could derail the peace process.
Even so, you have to be aware,
they'll accuse you of censore.
Tim, I did not ask for your counsel.
I know exactly
what I'm ordering you to do,
so please just do it.
Hey, drop-off and receiving?
Straight ahead. Right there.
Just make sure Duggan knows
he's covering the Logan profile.
Tell him we'll work out
the byline later.
- Editor's desk. This is Klausner.
- Gary, it's me.
Look, are you alone?
Can you speak freely?
What's going on?
I don't have a lot of time,
I have a lead on a story.
- I'm listening.
- I have a digital video recording
indicating that the IRK
terrorists who killed Hassan
were being funded and run
by Russian operatives.
You sure it's legit?
Where did you get it?
From Jack Bauer.
The man's a fugitive.
It's really not safe for me to talk.
I'll explain more when I see you.
Can you meet me?
Sure, of course.
All right, that diner
with the coffee you hate.
I can be there in 15 minutes.
And, Gary, don't tell anyone.
All right?
I got it.
Be safe.
You, too.
There's no need to panic.
Do you know what he did to Pavel?
He was beaten savagely,
gutted like a pig.
His men shot dead.
I'm sorry to hear that,
but we both knew that...
Bauer would be
a difficult problem to solve.
You know what he's doing, don't you?
He's eliminating everyone involved,
working his way up...
how long before he gets to me?
- That's not going to happen.
- How can you be so sure?
Because you told me yourself
your man would never talk,
and if that's true, then...
nobody outside of your inner circle
can point the finger at you.
I promise you...
Bauer's never going to know.
And on the upside,
his recent activities
have given us a bit of an advantage.
What advantage?
CTU orders concerning him
have been upgraded
to "shoot on sight".
First you have to find him.
They're going to find him,
don't worry.
He can't stay
under the radar forever.
I'll keep you posted.
Come in! We're under assault!
We are trapped
in the 4th Street underpass.
Unit LEZ-1, requesting
immediate backup.
Both entrances are blocked.
We are boxed in.
That's Jack Bauer.
That's got to be.
Did you hear what I said?
That's Jack Bauer!
Don't just sit there!
He's coming for me!
Stay in the vehicle. We're armored
and the glass is bulletproof.
The assailant is masked.
It may be Jack Bauer.
- Close the door! Secure the vehicle!
- Close the door!
Stay down, Mr. President.
Kill him!
Get up,
or I will kill you right here.
Move!
I got your flash.
What'd you find out about Ricker?
You were right.
DMV records show Ricker
living in Suffolk County
under the name Simon Strocker.
I tried to confirm,
found out he moved from there,
but he left a forwarding address
with the postal service.
It's right here in Soho.
Devon, what's going on?
Pillar's people are requesting
backup for the team in the field.
- Why?
- You didn't hear?
Jack Bauer just kidnapped
Charles Logan.
How the hell did he pull that off?
Charles Logan?
I need to hear what's going on
in that room. Follow me.
- How far out are you?
- We're approaching the tunnel now.
How the hell did
Secret Service let this happen?
Bauer hit the town car
with tear gas.
The agents were too incapacitated
to pursue.
PD's got the tunnel locked down.
I'm working on getting you schematics.
Hurry up.
CTU! Make a hole!
Where did Bauer
take President Logan?
I don't know.
You must have seen something.
Tell me you saw something.
- Sorry, sir.
- Nothing?
No one saw anything.
They went through a service gate.
- I need those schematics.
- Sending them to you now.
Go.
Kirsch, take the corridor.
Brown, you're down there.
Ames, you're with me. Remember,
unless it poses a threat
to President Logan, you shoot Bauer
on sight, and you shoot to kill.
Let's go.
Through here.
Look at me.
I said look at me!
You're going to tell me
everything I want.
Jack, you're making a mistake.
Don't you pretend
you're not a part of this.
I found the man
who killed Renee Walker:
the Russian operative Pavel Tokarev.
I got his cell phone.
- The last call he got was from you.
- You got to let me explain.
What?
That you sent for him to kill me?
- You sent him to kill me, right?
- Yes! Damn it, yes!
Why did you kill Renee Walker?
I had nothing to do with that.
I was brought in after that happened.
- Who brought you in?
- The president needed my help
to bring the Russians back to the table.
I called my sources in Moscow.
They told me that people
in their government
were behind Hassan's assassination.
I told the Russian delegation
I had evidence of that fact
and all the names.
It was to keep them at the conference.
What evidence?
It doesn't exist.
I was playing poker.
It was a bluff. It worked.
It kept Taylor's peace agreement
on the table, but...
You were determined
to screw things up.
I admit, I was part of the cover-up, but
I'm not part of the Russian conspiracy.
I had nothing to do
with the terrorist attack
or your friend's death.
I'm not the bad guy here.
Okay, but you know who is.
You know the name
of the Russian person
giving the orders. I want it.
Give me the name!
You got five seconds
before I put a bullet through your head.
- Five... Four... three...
- I'll tell you. Mikhail Novakovich.
He's the head of the delegation.
He's been trying to kill
the peace treaty from the start.
- You're lying.
- No! No! I'm not lying to you!
You got my call from Pavel's phone.
You check the previous calls.
There's a dozen more from Novakovich.
I'm telling you.
- He's the one you want.
- Shut up!
Say another word,
and I'll drop you right here.
- Get on your knees.
- Oh, no. Please.
Don't kill me.
If I was gonna kill you,
you'd already be dead.
Bauer was just here... find him!
Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
I need a med unit
at the 49th junction.
On its way.
Is it Bauer?
No. It's the president.
He's unconscious.
Bauer escaped. I'm gonna need you
to redirect the pursuit.
- I'll stay with the president.
- Understood.
They still might catch up to him.
They haven't yet.
Do you have Ricker's file?
Yeah, including his current address.
I'm sending it to you now.
What are your plans?
We can't send any tactical units
without Pillar finding out about it.
- I'm not using any of them.
- Then who are you going to get?
All of our agents are fully deployed
in the field. There's nobody to send.
There's one.
I saw the flash from division.
They approved your request
to release Agent Ortiz
into your custody?
- I'm in a hurry, so...
- What do you think you're doing?
He's a non-cooperative witness
who is facing federal charges.
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm still in charge of UN Security,
and you've taken away all my resources.
Not that it's any of your business,
but Agent Ortiz designed
the entire UN operation.
The signing is in less than two hours.
His assistance in the field is vital.
I'm going to have to clear this
with Pillar.
Do what you want, but you have bigger
problems, like not finding Jack Bauer.
Are you Meredith?
There's a Gary Klausner
on the phone for you.
It's up by the cashier.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Where are you?
The FBI is here.
Showed up before I could leave.
They're looking for you,
including me.
- You didn't tell them anything?
- Of course not.
But they've got an executive order
from the president.
They say you're in possession
of materials
- that pose a national security risk.
- It's a cover-up.
The White House is trying
to suppress the story.
You can't let them.
Until we clear this up,
you have to protect that evidence.
I told them
I'm not in contact with you,
but they're tracing this call.
Get the hell out of there.
And go where?
Mr. Klausner.
No communication
outside of our presence.
I'm canceling an appointment.
- They're going to bury the truth.
- Not if I can help it.
I'll try to put a call in
to Ed Sampson at the Justice Department,
but, until then, lay low.
Now go.
Let's go.
- Where are we going?
- I have to go to the UN,
and division has given you
a temporary furlough.
Since you had earlier
command of UN security,
I need your help coordinating protocols
for the signing ceremony.
Pillar's okay with this?
I'm still provisional
Director of Operations.
I don't need his consent.
Would you rather
wait here
for your federal prosecution?
Let's go.
I'll take him from here.
You want to tell me
what's really going on?
You were right about Jack.
He is working with somebody.
James Ricker,
ex-CIA Op.
He lives at a place on Mercer Street
under the alias Simon Strocker.
- Maybe he's still with the CIA.
- No, he was listed as deceased.
More than likely,
he's gone into business for himself,
dealing arms or intel.
In any case, he's not going to be happy.
Wait a second.
Why are you telling me this?
I need you to talk to him.
Get him to tell us where Jack is.
Are you good with that, or not?
I want to expose this cover-up
as much as you. I'm in.
Good. Log sheets
will show you
accompanying me to the UN.
I've secured you a separate vehicle.
Is there any more intel on Jack?
Has he resurfaced again?
Yeah, you could say that.
I just received word.
President Suvarov's plane
has touched down.
Tell Ivan to bring the car.
I want to be at the UN
when the president arrives.
Where's Novakovich?
- I'm not going to ask you again.
- 11th.
- 11th floor, suite 1170.
- How do I get up there?
Secure elevator inside of garage.
- Where's your keycard?
- I don't have.
- Where is your keycard?
- I don't have one, I swear.
His personal guards have them
at elevator.
- How many?
- Two.
And upstairs?
One outside the suite, two inside.
Another by elevator.
Where else?
- Where else?
- That's all I know.
Do you really need an arsenal?
Better to have it than to not.
Besides, Ricker's a trained killer.
He's gone to a lot of trouble
to stay off the grid.
Okay.
I also have to consider the possibility
that Jack's with him.
Listen, Chloe,
I can't be worried about Jack,
not after what you told me he did.
Obviously, Logan's
part of the conspiracy.
He terrorized a tunnel
full of peoples
with automatic weapon fire.
He shot Secret Service agents.
He shot to wound.
He's careless,
and he only cares about revenge.
Does that sound like
the man you know?
The man you're trying to save?
This is about exposing
the Russians' cover-up.
Not about Jack.
Are you sure about that?
Because if Jack's there,
and he makes any move
other than complete surrender...
I'm putting him down.
You still okay?
I don't have a choice.
Whatever happens,
call me at the U.N.
You got it.
You'll approach the rostrum
prior to the signing ceremony,
and take a seat here
in position three,
next to your mother.
I'm honored.
But is that appropriate?
I may be her daughter,
but I don't have any
official role in government.
Excuse me.
Ms. Hassan, there's a call
on your father's secure line...
a woman wants to speak
with your mother.
She's in a meeting.
That's what I said,
but this woman is quite insistent.
- Who is she?
- She won't say.
We're done, Ms. Hassan.
I'll see you in the staging area.
Thank you.
Line two.
Hello. Who is this?
Is this Kayla?
- Who are you?
- Sorry...
I am Meredith Reed.
I need to speak to your mother.
I know who you are.
Why are you calling here?
I know I'm the last person that either
of you wants to talk to right now...
You're right.
I'm hanging up now.
No, please, your mother needs to hear
what I have to say
before she signs the agreement.
What is it that is so important?
I'm sorry, I need to speak
to your mother directly.
Haven't you caused
my mother enough pain?
Leave us alone!
It's about the people
who really murdered your father.
What are you talking about?
We know who was responsible.
What you don't know is,
those people were working
under the orders of Russian agents.
What?
Hello?
When your mother gets back,
have her call me at this number.
Can you take this down?
Go ahead.
It's 212-555-0121.
- I'll explain everything to her then.
- Wait!
Meredith Reed?
FBI. Get your hands
where we can see 'em.
What is this?
You have no right to take that.
I haven't done anything wrong.
What is this?
- You're under arrest.
- I've done nothing wrong.
I've done nothing wrong!
- Yes?
- Mr. Woods, ma'am.
I've just received word
from the FBI.
Reed is in custody,
and they've secured
a data card they found on her.
No one sees what's on it but me.
Understood.
- We'll take it from here.
- I'm riding with him to the hospital.
Give him some space.
Nova...
Novakovich.
Bauer knows.
Warn Novakovich
Bauer's coming after him.
- We gotta get going.
- Not yet.
Just do what you can for him here.
Understood.
Mr. Novakovich?
Hello?
It's Berkov.
We've been attacked.
It was Bauer.
- Where's Novakovich?
- He's dead.
Everyone is dead.
Berkov, did Novakovich
say anything to Bauer?
I need an ambulance.
Just answer my question.
What did Novakovich say to Bauer?
Nothing.
Bauer just came in shooting.
But he was bleeding.
I think he was wounded
by one of the guards.
Sit tight,
an ambulance is on the way.
Go.
Novakovich is dead.
Bauer killed him,
killed all of his men...
I don't know
if Novakovich said anything to Bauer.
- Yes?
- Yuri?
Charles Logan.
I thought you were going to be
at the heliport for my arrival.
Yes, well...
I ran into some trouble.
I'm afraid I have bad news.
It appears that Mikhail Novakovich
was just murdered by Jack Bauer.
What?
Jack Bauer learned
that Novakovich was responsible
for ordering and...
coordinating
Omar Hassan's assassination,
as well as the rest
of Samir's activities.
Where would he get that idea?
From me.
The lunatic was gonna kill me, Yuri.
What can I say?
Think of it as...
sacrificing a rook for a king.
Then Bauer has no idea
that Novakovich was operating
under my orders?
None.
According to a witness,
Mikhail didn't have a chance
to give you up, even he wanted to.
As far as Bauer is concerned...
the trail ended with Novakovich.
And he's being hunted by every
law enforcement agency in the city.
And I've heard that...
he's been wounded.
There is nothing more dangerous
than a wounded animal.
If you're so worried about Bauer,
you never should have given the order
to kill Renee Walker.
That's what stirred up
the hornet's nest.
If I had known that you were going
to find out about our activities
and use that information
to blackmail me
into signing
Taylor's peace agreement,
I wouldn't have bothered
with the woman.
Water under the bridge, Yuri.
I needed an opportunity
to put myself back in the game.
I'm sorry that it has come
at your expense.
You wouldn't begrudge an old friend
his second chance in the sun.
All right, then, I will...
I will meet you
at the United Nations...
as soon as I can.