Previously on 24
Mr. knowles, my name is jack bauer.
Jonas hodges is in possession of a military-grade bioweapon.
I was contaminated when trying to intercept the canisters.
I promise you, sir, the weapon is on your base.
Do you have any idea where they might be?
I think I might.
I have an order from the president of the united states.
To search this building.
Are there weapons of mass destruction?
Are there weapons of any kind?
You've got five minutes
To get these helicopters flying out of here
With all of you on board.
Larry, I want you and your men
To pull out on hodges' timetable.
Tony, you're gonna need to find a way to stay behind.
We're gonna get your vectors over to a man
That we contacted inside starkwood.
His name is douglas knowles.
He believes he knows where the weapons are.
Stay here. I'll be right back.
Jack!
We need a medic!
The bioagent is more virulent than we thought.
All we're doing here is just masking the symptoms.
I understand.
There's something you may want to consider.
What's that?
A possible treatment using stem cells
From a genetically compatible donor.
I saw your file, and it says you have a daughter.
I don't want my daughter involved in this.
It should be her choice.
Well, it's not.
I'm the one who's dying.
I'm in.
But they got knowles.
A little loyalty.
Wasn't that the least I deserved?
You can't take on the federal government.
I have a visual on the weapon.
Okay, those are the canisters.
I'll notify admiral smith the target is located and confirmed.
You remember starkwood was deployed to pakistan,
That we requisitioned a missile system at that time.
Well, three of those missiles
Are now loaded with a pathogen
And aimed at cities on our eastern seaboard.
You will keep this conversation to yourself
And turn the planes around.
And if you do not comply, madam president,
I will have no choice
But to launch those missiles.
Abort the air strike, admiral smith.
Ma'am, with all respect...
Damn it, admiral.
Abort the air strike immediately!
The following takes place between 1 a.m. and 2 a.m.
Tony, it's jack.
Do you copy?
Jack, what the hell is going on?
Where are those f-18s?
Tim woods just called from the white house.
The president canceled the air strike.
What?
Why?
She doesn't believe our intel
Is strong enough to justify military action.
Is she out of her mind?
Jack, I saw those canisters with my own eyes.
So did you. they're in that bunker.
- She's not gonna get any better intel than that. - I know.
It doesn't make any sense, but right now,
We've got a presidential order to pull you out
Of the starkwood compound, along with the perimeter teams.
Tony, larry's been told the president's decision.
He's preparing to move his teams out, but he's got
To get you out of there first.
He'll be sending you coordinates for an exfiltration point
Along the southwest perimeter.
Tony?
Hold on a second.
Tony, what's going on?
Jack, I might know
Why the president called off that air strike.
What do you mean?
I think starkwood's got surface-to-surface missiles.
That's how they're gonna deploy the bioweapon.
How do you know this?
A fuel truck just pulled up next to the bunker
Where they're storing the weapons.
They're pumping rp-7 into an underground depot.
What's rp-7?
It's a propellant only used in surface-to-surface missiles.
Tony, are you sure?
I'm looking right at it, jack.
Do you have any c-4 on you?
Yeah, I've got three charges and a remote detonator.
Do you think you can gain access to the underground fuel depot?
Yeah, I think we've got a play,
But I've got to move soon...
Before that fuel truck pulls away.
Okay, I want you to maintain your position.
I'm gonna call the president.
Come with me.
What is it, tim?
Madam president, the joint chiefs
Are beginning to question your decision
To call off the air strike against starkwood.
They think the intelligence we received from tony almeida
Was sufficient and that we may be missing
An opportunity to destroy the bioweapons.
Gave my orders, tim.
No air strike.
No military action of any kind against starkwood.
Now, I asked you to handle the joint chiefs;
Handle them.
I'll do my best, ma'am,
But if I may...
What is our next move?
Jonas hodges is coming to the white house.
He wants to speak with me alone.
- For what possible reason? - I don't know.
Madam president, shouldn't your advisors
Be at that meeting?
Tim, stop asking me questions.
If you want to help,
Make sure as few people as possible know
That jonas hodges is coming here.
And bring him in through the southeast service entrance.
Yes?
Madam president, jack bauer
And renee walker are calling from fbi.
You did speak to fbi?
Yes, ma'am, five minutes ago.
I gave them your reason for calling off
The air strike, but I must warn you,
They were skeptical as well.
Be ready for hodges.
Mr. bauer,
Agent walker, this is the president.
Madam president, we need to talk.
No, mr. bauer, we don't.
You need to listen.
I appreciate everything that you have done
In gathering this intel,
But I still need more
Before I can authorize an air strike.
I'm sorry.
Madam president, with all due respect,
I don't believe you're being truthful with us.
Excuse me?
I think you called off the air strike
Because jonas hodges is in possession
Of surface-to-surface missiles armed with the bioweapon,
And he's threatening to use them
In case you try to take action against him.
Madam president, tony almeida witnessed a truck
Pumping rp-7 rocket fuel into an underground depot
Situated right next to the bunker
Where the bioweapons are being stored.
The only purpose for rp-7 rocket fuel
Is to launch missiles.
Madam president, please just tell us the truth.
Jack, hodges has 13 python missiles
Armed with the bioweapons.
Three are currently aimed at american cities.
He demanded that I recall the planes,
Or he would launch.
What does hodges want?
I don't know...
But he's requested a face-to-face meeting.
He'll be at the white house in a few minutes.
Madam president, the only reason he wants
A face-to-face meeting is to lay out his demands,
And whatever they are, you cannot negotiate with him.
I'm not planning on negotiating with him, jack.
Once he places his cards on the table,
I am sure that I can... I can make him realize
The futility of what he is trying to do.
Jonas hodges is a traitor and a terrorist,
And after everything that's happened today,
Are you really naive enough
To believe that you can simply talk to him
And change his mind?
I'm not new at this, jack,
And right now, I don't have another option.
Madam president, you do.
Tony almeida is still inside starkwood.
I ordered him exfiltrated immediately.
What's he still doing there?
I asked him to stand by until I could talk to you.
He believes he can gain access to the fuel depot
And lay a series of explosive charges
And take the missiles out.
Now, I believe this can work, but we need to act quickly.
What about the bioweapons?
Rp-7 rocket fuel burns at 5,000 degrees.
There will be nothing left.
Once the weapons are destroyed, larry moss and his teams
Can move in on starkwood and lock it down.
Hodges gave standing orders to his men
To launch the missiles at the first detection
Of government interference.
If Almeida is detected,
Thousands of americans will die, Jack.
Madam president, I know that there's a risk,
But I would not be asking you to do this
If I didn't think it would work.
Please, I am begging you.
Trust me.
How long did the doctors give you to live?
Uh, they're not sure,
But the pathogen has started to take effect.
Then there's not much I can threaten you with, is there?
I expect you'll do what you think is right.
What the hell does that mean?
She wants us to go in.
But she didn't authorize it.
She can't.
She needs this to be a covert operation.
If something were to go wrong
And those missiles were to be launched,
The president needs to be able to swear
Under oath that we were working on our own
She wants us to go in.
Notify Larry. we need to move fast.
I told you I'd get you to the white house.
I just didn't think it would be
Under these conditions.
It was brilliant, you know.
What was that, sir?
What you did to make Almeida think
That you were betraying me.
Quite brilliant.
Thank you, sir.
You put yourself in harm's way, greg,
And I'll never forget that.
I can't believe... I'm feeling nervous.
You're gonna do fine, sir.
Thank you, Tim.
You're welcome.
So, it sounds to me like the president
Didn't actually authorize this.
Technically, no.
It was more of an... an indirect order,
But believe me, Larry, she wants this to happen.
She's gonna meet with Hodges,
And we're gonna blow those fuel tanks.
Larry, do you have a problem with this?
As a matter of fact, no.
None whatsoever.
These Starkwood bastards drew on my men.
I'm looking forward to getting back in there.
All right, have your teams hold their position
And be ready to move.
Believe me, you'll know when it happens.
All right.
Tony,
- It's Jack. do you copy? - Yeah, I'm here.
You were right about the missiles.
The president confirmed it.
We're gonna have to carry this out
As a covert operation.
Larry and his men are standing by to lock down Starkwood
As soon as the missiles have been destroyed.
- Good. - Tony...
I need to know that you can do this
Without being detected.
Hodges's given his men standing orders
To launch those missiles if there's a breach of any kind.
Yeah. I can do it.
Okay. good luck.
Yeah.
We're done here.
I'm going to go run a perimeter check.
You said you just finished one.
I know.
But I don't think we can be too careful right now.
- yeah. - It's me.
Auxiliary tanks are fueled and ready.
Confirmed.
I'll be down in a few minutes.
Copy that.
Freeze!
Let me see your hands.
Almeida.
Put your gun on the ground.
Slowly.
Kick it.
Drag him under the truck.
Now! let's go!
Hands up.
What do you think you're doing?
You're going to take me down to the fuel tanks.
Let's go.
Open it up.
Go ahead.
President will see you now.
Very good. Thank you.
Mr. Hodges.
Madam president.
This is Greg Seaton,
My associate.
He's a remarkable man.
Doesn't look remarkable,
But believe me, he's a genius.
Yes, I know Mr. Seaton.
Thank you, gentlemen.
It never gets old, does it?
Stepping into the... the Oval Office.
Almost
Smells of history.
Can we sit?
Please.
You know, this is the first Time
I've been in this room since you were elected?
I'm aware of that, yes.
Under your predecessor,
I used to drop by every couple of months.
I'd brief President Daniels
On what was really going on in the world.
And you've been excluded now.
Is that what this is about?
No, ma'am.
It's about allowing Starkwood
To fulfill the purpose for which was founded
Protecting this country.
You have been attacking this country.
You and General Juma
Have killed hundreds of innocent people,
Including my son.
Madam president,
I'm deeply sorry for your loss,
And my heart breaks
For all the lives that were taken today,
But I'm shocked
That you would think that I had anything
- To do with it. - we have evidence
That you've been working with juma.
Your intelligence agencies have failed you.
If I had known what juma was up to,
I would have done everything in my power to stop him.
So let's push aside all these baseless accusations
And maybe we can do some business here.
I'm listening.
Madam president,
I know you're a student of history,
And so you're well aware
That our nation's independence was won
With the aid of private armies,
And we can't survive without them.
Look how easy it was to get bioweapons into this country.
Our defenses are fragile.
They're on the verge of collapse.
But it's not too late to do something about it.
So what are you suggesting?
In short,
I want a seat at the table.
Starkwood needs to be involved in the shaping
Of military policy, domestic and global.
It sounds more like
You want a seat at the head of the table.
Madam president, I'm not here to supplant your authority.
What I'm proposing is a partnership.
Think of Starkwood
As the fifth branch of the military.
Greg?
This contains the protocols
That will serve as the basis of our agreement.
I suggest that we review them together.
Jonas, I agreed to this meeting
Because I wanted to hear what you had to say.
But what you're proposing is blackmail.
Well, that's putting it in the worst possible light.
You are threatening to kill thousands of people.
I'm not proud of this chapter.
I'm the first to admit it.
And it's time to turn the page.
This country has seen enough bloodshed today.
For the sake of the american people, madam president,
I implore you to work with me,
And let's move past this.
Pick up the document, madam president.
Let's go.
Come on. get up now, or I'll leave you down here.
And you don't want that, believe me. get up!
Let's go!
Come on!
What is it?
Code 363.
That's a government breach.
We're supposed to launch.
Are you sure it's not a false alarm?
No way to tell.
We've got standing orders, though.
Let's start the launch sequence.
Too late.
Launch sequence complete.
Target is locked.
Enter the firing codes.
Sir, we need to confirm this.
That's not the correct protocol.
We're about to kill 10,000 people.
We should get someone on the phone.
Enter the codes.
Now!
No, sir.
That's it. that's us. let's go.
We're a go!
It's done.
Tony?
Tony, do you copy?
An explosion of that magnitude would have shorted out his com.
We're gonna have to wait for larry and his men to move in.
It says here that you want
Active status in the pentagon's strategic planning group.
That's correct.
That would give you access to level 6 classified material.
Not even the vice president has that clearance.
These points are nonnegotiable.
I'm not here to debate them.
Let's review the next section,
Which concerns senate oversight of starkwood field operations.
I'm sorry to interrupt, madam president, but I need
To speak with you.
Can it wait?
No, ma'am, it can't.
Will you excuse me for a moment?
Of course.
Satcom has just detected
A massive explosion on the starkwood compound.
The bioweapons facility has been destroyed.
- Are you sure? - Yes, ma'am.
Judging by the size of the explosion,
Nothing could have survived.
But I don't know how this happened.
This wasn't us.
Call FBI and have them lock down starkwood.
- They're already moving in. - Good.
And when this is over, I want to speak to jack bauer.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm not sure I'm reaching her.
I think you handled it perfectly, sir.
We'll see.
What the hell is this?
Put this document into evidence, and take these men
Into custody.
What are you thinking? Have you lost your mind?
Jonas, we've taken out your missiles.
It's over.
That's impossible.
It's the truth.
And you're under arrest.
You are a terrorist and a murderer,
And I'm gonna do everything in my power to make sure
That you pay dearly for your crimes.
My only crime is that I'm trying to protect
My country!
You think this ends with me?
I'm just a small cog in a very big machine.
Hold on.
You can't even begin to imagine what you're up against.
What are you talking about?
You'll find out.
Get him out of here.
Evase by wise protein were put in new trace
bioweapen were near the blast sight.
It was incinerated in the explosion.
Good.
- Any word on tony? - Not yet.
Larry's searching the compound now.
We should hear something soon.
Mr. Bauer,
You have a phone call; it's the president.
I'll take it in the conference room. thank you.
I'll be right back.
Madam president.
Mr. bauer, jonas hodges is under arrest.
That's good news.
That's very good.
Jack, you and your team provided me with an option.
And for that, I am deeply grateful.
And so are the american people.
Madam president, it was tony almeida
Who risked his life to destroy those missiles.
And as you know, he's facing arrest
For things he did leading up to today,
And I was hoping that maybe
You could...
Yes, mr. bauer?
Jack?
Um, I'm sorry, I...
Completely forgot what I was saying.
You were talking about Mr. Almeida.
And my answer is yes,
I-I will take his actions into account.
Thank you.
What's happening?
I-I-I'm not exactly sure.
Jack, I am so sorry you're going through this.
I wish that there were something I could do.
M-madam president, I appreciate this phone call.
But I'm sorry. I-I have to go.
Of course.
Thank you.
Jonas hodges has been arrested.
Let me know
As soon as you got tony.
I need to go see dr. macer.
Yes, madam president?
Call ben landry at cdc.
Tell him that I want real-time updates
On jack bauer's condition.
Yes, ma'am.
We've secured all entry points and command posts
And are sweeping the compound on a grid-by-grid basis.
Are you meeting any resistance?
No.
They're surrendering peacefully and cooperating.
Most of the men on this base,
I don't think they had any idea what was going on.
What about almeida?
Uh, he's here.
We found him.
- Is he okay? - Some cuts and bruises,
But otherwise, he's in pretty good shape.
Good. good.
Jack will be glad to hear that.
Listen, renee...
We've known each other a long time, you know.
Um, so much stuff has happened today.
Yeah.
We have a lot to talk about.
I know.
Excuse me, agent walker. she's in the waiting area.
Okay, thank you.
Larry, I've got to go.
- Kim bauer's here. - Jack's daughter?
Yes. I-I asked her to come.
There's this experimental treatment
For jack's disease, but he needs compatible stem cells.
It's a long shot, but it's the only hope he's got.
Okay.
Let me know how it goes, all right?
I will. I'm going off com.
All right.
Did they say something about kim bauer?
Yeah, she's at FBI
Helping with a treatment for jack,
Some, uh, some kind of stem cell therapy.
So they think he's gonna be all right?
Didn't sound promising.
Listen, tony, this isn't easy for me,
But, uh... I'm under orders
To take you into federal custody.
Yeah, I know.
You did a brave thing here.
Probably saved thousands of lives.
For the record,
I don't think this is how you should be repaid.
I appreciate that, but, uh...
I'm ready to pay for what I've done.
Get the cuffs off him, will you?
Chopper's on the way.
I'll be taking you back to fbi, all right?
Memory loss is consistent with the disease,Mr. bauer.
I just wouldn't have expected it to manifest this quickly.
It's not just memory loss.
It feels like...
I don't know exactly how to explain it.
I feel like, uh,
Like I'm losing some part of myself.
The disease profile includes
Personality changes, sometis even hallucinations.
But this is a weaponized pathogen
We don't know much about.
Military's still combing through the remains
Of the bioweapons lab in sangala,
So we expect to learn something very soon.
You were able to give me something that controlled the shaking.
Is there anything that you can give me
That would help me with this?
No.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Thank you. excuse me.
Jack, is it all right?
Yeah, um,
I'm gonna need to go on record about everything that happened today.
And we need to do it soon.
I'm not sure how much longer I'm gonna be
Able to provide you with the details.
Okay.
First, there's something that you need to know.
What?
It's about kim.
She's here, jack.
I told her that you were sick
And that she might be able to help
With the treatment.
You did...
You did what?
Come here.
Who the hell do you think you are?
You think this is easy?
You think you understand what I'm going through?
Because you don't.
I am dying.
And I was okay with it.
I could handle it.
And now you've put in front of me the one thing,
The one thing that is gonna make this unbearable.
- Jack, listen... - No, you listen to me.
I specifically told you do not drag my daughter into this.
No one dragged her into anything.
She's been trying to see you all day.
What?
She was at the senate hearing this morning.
She flew out from L.A. to be there,
But we pulled you out before she could see you.
She's been leaving messages at our office all day.
They just didn't get to me till now.
If you want, I can tell her that you're not here.
I can tell her that you can't see her.
Can't do that.
Where is she?
Down the hall.
Show me.
Daddy.
How are you feeling?
I'm-i'm okay.
You're not in any pain?
No.
Come sit down.
Did agent Walker tell you that I was trying to find you?
Yeah.
I've tried everything to track you down.
State department, private investigators.
Every time I got a phone number or an address,
You were already gone.
I'm sorry.
I thought I was doing the best thing for you
By staying away.
Daddy, I've missed you so much.
I've missed you,too.
You need to know how sorry I am
For everything that you've had to live through because of me.
No, don't do that.
Don't put that on yourself.
I'm the one that should apologize.
I pushed you away.
And instead of taking responsibility
For all the mistakes I've made in my life, I blamed you.
And it was stupid
And immature.
And now, all the time that we've lost...
Agent Walker told me that there's a chance--
A small chance-- that I could help you,
And you don't want me to.
The treatment is experimental.
And I don't think it's going to work.
And you don't want to because you're afraid to ask me.
No.
There's a risk to you.
A small risk...
Worth taking.
Not to me.
Kim... I'm dying.
And whatever small chance there is to stop that from happening--
It is not worth the pain for me to let you
Sit there and watch me die.
Daddy, I don't want to lose you.
Come here.
I don't.
Sweetheart, it's going to be all right.
It's gonna be all right. I promise you.
What is it?
What?
Sweetheart, I'm sorry...
But you need to go.
Please, baby, please, I'm begging you.
I love you so much.
Honey, I love you, too. please, baby.
Thank you. Go.
Perimeter 2 to Dispatch. Auxiliary gate 6 is clear.
Copy that, P-2. hold your position.
Freeze!
Show me your hands.
Get 'em up!
P-2 to Dispatch.
I have an agent down and a suspect in custody.
Code red.
Copy that, P-2.
All available agents respond to auxiliary gate 6.
- Drop the bag. - Code red.
Hands on the hood.
Danger,hazardous materiel
P-2 to Dispatch.
Put me through to agent Moss. it's urgent.
Agent Moss.
Agent Moss, this is Davis at auxiliary gate 6.
I have a Starkwood op in custody.
He killed one of our agents.
He was carrying a canister of the bioweapon,
Trying to smuggle it out
Using one of our vehicles.
What?! are you sure?
I'm looking at it right now.
Agent davis?
Davis?!
Walker.
Renee, we got a breach in the cordon at gate 6.
One of the starkwood ops--
He's got a canister of the bioweapon.
What?
It was id'd by agent davis,
Who I believe has just been shot.
The suspect may be fleeing in an FBI vehicle,
So I need you to close down all access roads,
And alert perimeter units and metro police.
Janis, get me DC metro.
I'm gonna pursue it from the air.
Let's go! let us up!
Renee,
Alert homeland, let them know what's going on.
Are we thinking this is another attack, larry?
I don't know, but there's enough prion variant
In one of those canisters to take out a small city.
Agent miller, are there any major roadways
In our perimeter that Starkwood operatives could have used?
Yes, sir.
We're coming up on highway 42.
Should I turn us that way?
Yeah, let's head that way until we hear something from agent Walker.
Roger that.
Yes, sir. we'll keep homeland apprised
With real-time updates.
Did you access the GPS locator system?
Yeah, I'm scanning transponders
for the stolen FBI vehicle.
How long will that take?
As long as it takes for the satellite to reposition.
When you spoke to Larry, you mentioned an attack?
The Starkwood operative,
We're trying to find a stolen canister of the bioweapon.
I thought Tony Almeida destroyed all the weapons.
Apparently not.
How did this operative get past our perimeter?
Shot and killed two of our agents.
This is it.
The suspect is getting off highway 42 at moketree avenue.
He's heading toward the industrial corridor.
Put me on the interagency channel.
- Go ahead. - All units, this is
Agent walker with FBI.
Suspect has exited highway 42 at smoketree.
He's heading north into the industrial corridor.
Units in the vicinity, please respond.
Renee, it's me.
We're over smoketree right now.
We're redirecting, and we'll tighten our pursuit.
Got it. I'll reroute swat team alpha to the scene.
Swat team alpha, we need to set up a roadblock
At the fairfax county line.
Dc metro's covering the district line in case he tries
- To double back.- Copy that. County line.
Sir.
I have a visual.
Yeah. got him.
Send us lower.
Yeah, he's pulling off the road. get us down there now.
Renee, it's larry. suspect is on foot.
We can't wait for backup.
We're moving in right now.
All right. swat team's a few minutes out.
- Careful, larry. - Yeah.
Remember, suspect has a canister,
So pic your shots.
If possible, let's take him alive.
Yes, sir.
We got to get out of here.
Almeida, cover. let's go.
Come on!
Sir, relax.
Relax.
- I'm okay. - Relax.
- Swallow. - Tony.
Tony!
What...?
I'm sorry, larry.
Oh... god...
Let me see it.
How the hell do we get out of here?
I want you to take this, find a place to hide.
- Wait for my call. - What about you?
I'm gonna wait on the FBI,
Figure out a way to get you out of here.
Go!
www.YYeTs.net