Subtitles: Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu
Who are you looking for?
Someone who can give me
the names of everyone else involved.
Break the story
in case I don't make it.
If Dalia Hassan finds out
that the Russians had a hand
in her husband's dead,
she'll never sign.
I've to speak to Dalia.
It's about the people
who murdered your father.
We know who is responsible.
What you don't know is,
those people were working under
the orders of Russian agents.
Bauer made contact
with Meredith Reed.
You need
to call her publisher and demand
that they do not run the story.
You're suggesting
muzzling the press?
If you don't use
the power of your office
to shut this story down,
your peace agreement
won't be the only casualty.
I need you to contact the FBI.
Have them locate Reed
and seize whatever evidence
she purports to have.
Meredith Reed? FBI.
- You're under arrest.
- Let's go.
You were right about Jack.
He is working with somebody.
It's James Ricker, ex-CIA op.
He lives on Mercer Street.
He's not gonna be happy
we tracked him down.
I need you to talk to him.
Get him to tell us where Jack is.
Are you good,
or have you still not taken sides?
I want to expose this cover-up
as much as you. I'm in.
That's Jack Bauer!
Get up
or I will kill you right here.
You know the name of the person
in the Russian government who's leading.
I want that name.
Give me the name!
I'll tell you.
Mikhail Novakovich!
Where's Novakovich?
He's dead.
Bauer came in shooting.
Mikhail Novakovich was just murdered
by Jack Bauer.
What?
As far as, Bauer is concerned,
the trail ended with Novakovich.
Then Bauer has no idea
- that he was operating under my orders?
- None.
If you're so worried about Bauer,
you never should
have given the order
to kill Renee Walker.
I just picked up a preliminary flash.
Jack murdered Novakovich at his hotel,
and six of his security guards.
According to a witness,
Jack killed all seven men on his own.
Then fell right back off the radar.
Eden can't find any trace of him.
Does Chloe know about this?
I just talked to her,
she should be at the UN any minute.
I know that we need
this evidence that Jack has,
but this crime scene
is a slaughterhouse.
Does Chloe really still
think she can pull this off?
If anyone can talk Jack down,
it's Chloe.
And if she can't?
We're both prepared to do
whatever it takes.
Even when Novakovich's
whole security staff couldn't?
What do you want me to do?
The truth about today
needs to get out,
and that's not going to happen
unless we get to Jack.
I'm coming up on Ricker's apartment.
I'm going in.
Ricker went to a lot of trouble
to disappear.
He's not going to like
that you found him.
I'm not expecting him to.
You're looking at the UN Plaza gardens
and the podium from which
all three co-sponsors of the peace
treaty will address the public
following a private signing ceremony
inside the UN Council Chamber
Russian President Yuri Suvarov,
the third co-sponsor of the treaty,
is en route to the UN
where he will join President Taylor
and acting IRK President
Dalia Hassan...
This is Agent Ortiz, CTU!
Open that door.
Before you pull that trigger,
you ought to know this.
I don't place a call in 15 minutes,
every intelligence agency
in the country gets alerted about you.
Weapon charges alone
will get you locked up for the duration,
Or you can help us find Jack Bauer,
and we'll keep our mouths shut.
You think you're protecting him?
The order on Jack Bauer
is shoot to kill.
He knew
what he was getting himself into.
Jack's not thinking straight.
Look, I read your file.
I know Jack saved your life
in Damascus.
This is your opportunity
to pay back that debt.
You know how this
is gonna end, right?
Do you?
If Jack dies today,
it's on you.
Wait a minute.
Thanks, Adam.
Agent Burke. I have the revised
security assessment for you.
I noticed that Ortiz's name
was back on the duty roster.
That's right.
He was arrested
for helping Jack Bauer.
I got him a temporary clearance
so he could help us.
He was the one who designed
the UN protocols in the first place.
I know.
Do you really think
we can trust him?
I wouldn't have gotten him
a release if I didn't.
Excuse me.
- What happened?
- Not good.
I think Jack's targeting Suvarov.
Is that what Ricker said?
Yeah. Jack planted a bug
on Charles Logan,
overheard a conversation
between them.
Suvarov's the one who gave the order
for Renee to be killed.
Does Ricker have a recording
of that conversation?
No. He wiped his system clean
as soon as he saw me coming.
But the surveillance rig he gave Jack
makes a backup, so Jack has a copy.
Good.
We're gonna need it.
- Why?
- Meredith Reed has been arrested.
They confiscated a data card
from her.
- Dana's evidence.
- Exactly.
The recording that Jack has
is the only proof we have now.
I don't know that getting proof
is our first priority anymore.
We have to put an alert out on Jack.
If we do that,
Pillar will get to him first.
He'll kill Jack,
and he'll destroy the recording.
We can't stand by and let Jack
assassinate the president of Russia.
No, but we can buy ourselves time.
Can change Suvarov's
motorcade route,
sequester him in the UN. Make it
impossible for Jack to get to him.
Except Suvarov's gonna
be standing at that podium soon,
and once he's exposed like that,
we can't protect him.
That's not happening
for over an hour.
If we haven't found Jack by then,
we put out the alert.
It's still taking a big risk, Chloe.
I know.
Get Suvarov's route changed.
But I'm in charge of his security
as soon as he gets to the UN.
- How far out are you?
- I'll be there in ten.
Sir, the flash
about Novakovich is going out.
You wanted to speak with the president
before that happened.
Thank you, Jason.
Do we know anything about Bauer?
No. Nothing.
If you don't mind me asking, sir.
What are you going to tell Taylor?
I think it's time she...
she knows everything.
All the delegates are present
except Suvarov, who's still in transit.
He'll be given the details
once he arrives.
Excuse me.
I'm about to go into the meeting.
What's going on?
I wanted you to hear this news
from me first.
What news?
I tried to insulate you
as long as I could,
preserve your plausible
deniability, but...
Tell me what you're talking about.
Jack Bauer isn't just trying
to gather evidence
about the conspiracy.
He's seeking retribution.
Go on.
Bauer just murdered
Mikhail Novakovich,
along with a good number
of his staff.
So Novakovich was responsible
for the assassination
of President Hassan?
Novakovich was the ranking member
of the Russian Delegation.
President Suvarov is going
to demand an explanation.
Actually, he's not.
Are you telling me
that Hassan's murder goes
all the way up to Suvarov?
But the good news is
that Bauer doesn't know that.
How can you be sure?
Because according to a witness,
Bauer killed Novakovich
before he could talk.
And aside from me, Novakavich
is the only person who ever knew
that Suvarov was calling the shots.
Madam President, Bauer's finished
what he started, Suvarov will be happy
to sweep this under the rug.
And the peace agreement
can go forward as planned.
This is...
Really, we couldn't have
asked for a better outcome.
Except that I am asking
Dalia Hassan to shake hands
with her husband's murderer.
Call Suvarov.
Tell him that I am aware
of his involvement in this,
and that I will see him
at the signing.
My apologies.
Thank you for waiting.
- How did the call go?
- I told the president
about Suvarov's involvement, and...
she understood... not that
she has an alternative.
That's good news.
Your new Secret Service detail's here
to escort you to the UN.
It's been a long road, but...
we're almost there.
Anything new on Bauer?
A security camera picked him up
leaving Novakovich's hotel.
Confirmed what Berkov told us.
Bauer was definitely wounded
during the attack.
How badly?
He's gonna need treatment.
Getting alerts out
to medical facilities now.
Let Port Authority and INS know Bauer
might be trying to escape.
We'll find him...
It's only a question of time.
Maybe a little quicker
than you thought.
Slowly, take your weapon out
and pass it back to me.
Slowly.
Start the car and drive.
You saw what I did to Pavel.
I didn't have a time.
You, I've got all the time
in the world.
So you either do what I say,
or I will take you apart
piece by piece.
Now, drive!
- Where are we going?
- The UN.
Why?
You already got what you wanted.
- You killed everyone involved.
- Save your breath.
I know about President Suvarov.
Your delegations will be joining
you at the reception
after the post-signing ceremony.
And finally,
on behalf of the UN staff,
I would like to say
that we are all honored
to be part
of this historic occasion.
Thank you for your time.
Your daughter's been waiting
outside to speak to you.
She says it's important.
Let her know I'll be right there.
I have something for you.
It's from Omar.
He wanted to give it to you
to sign the agreement...
I'm grateful
that I can do so on his behalf.
It reads:
"All religions,
"all this singing,
"one song,
"peace be with you."
It is a verse
Omar would quote from Rumi
when he was talking about what
you and he were trying to achieve.
Thank you for seeing this through
and for helping us all
do justice to his memory.
I am honored.
I'm very honored.
Kayla, what is it?
Meredith Reed called
the residence looking for you.
I am not interested
in that woman's condolences.
That is not why she called.
She says she has information
about the people who are
behind Father's murder.
But we know who was behind
your father's death...
extremists in our country.
She claims
that they had outside help.
That the Russians were involved.
Why would she say such a thing?
Does she have evidence,
or is this a rumor?
I don't know, but it can't have been
easy for her to call you.
I don't think
it's because of a rumor.
- What else did she say?
- She wouldn't say anything more
until she talked to you.
She left her number.
Let's call her from the residence.
President Suvarov's
motorcade is delayed
five minutes, put out an all-agency.
How do you want it coded?
Eyes only.
Lanza, make sure Burke reports here
with a set of tactical gear
for Agent Ortiz.
Arlo's at CTU,
running the surveillance video
through facial recognition.
Still no sign of Jack.
I've been thinking.
Let's say this file are from Jack.
What are we supposed to do?
If the president's willing
to lock down Meredith Reed...
She can't shut down every media,
which is where
we're gonna send this file.
We're also gonna send it
to every government employee.
Legislative, military, judiciary...
a lot of people.
How?
By using CTU servers,
we can distribute it simultaneously.
President Taylor
won't be able to stop the truth.
Good to see you.
Do you have the revised protocol
for President Suvarov's arrival?
We're bringing the motorcade
into the FDR Drive ramp.
Make sure that Agent Ortiz
has the revised protocols.
He's back in charge.
Let's take a look.
We're going to the Hart Building.
I want you to park underground.
This guard's life is in your hands.
One move that I don't like,
I'm gonna kill you both.
There's no one inside
since two hours ago.
Yeah, I'm just running
a last-minute security check.
Of course, sir.
Anything else?
No. Thank you.
Drive.
Pull in over here.
Slowly, with your right hand,
take the keys out of the ignition
and pass them back.
Get out of the car.
Now!
Close the door.
Put your hands on the roof.
Don't you move.
Suvarov's not gonna be out
on the podium for another hour.
You're not gonna make it that long.
Slowly,
back up towards me.
Stop.
Turn around.
You're gonna suture me up.
You try and make a move on me,
the slightest twitch,
I will put a bullet in your brain.
You got it?
I don't understand something.
You've spent your entire career
outside the system,
you've always had a good reason.
But this...
it's just blood lost.
You're destroying an agreement
that took years.
An agreement made by
murderers and liars.
Murderers?
You're the one killing people
in cold blood.
Everybody I took out had
a hand in today's attack.
But who makes you judge and jury?
President Taylor,
when she agreed to the cover-up.
I would have accepted justice
by law...
but that was taken away from me
by people like you.
So you're right,
I am judge and jury.
Now, step back.
Turn around.
Start to move back towards the car.
I came in after Hassan,
Walker were killed.
I'm not responsible for that.
- Get on your knees!
- I'm telling you the truth.
I've got a family.
Shut up.
Bauer, please, I have a little girl.
I have a daughter. She's six.
Please.
Don't do this.
Still no answer.
Are you sure
this is Meredith Reed's number?
- It's the right number.
- Then why isn't she answering?
I just talked to Gary Klausner,
Ms. Reed's editor.
He doesn't know where she is
and has no way to reach her.
He seemed very anxious
to get off the phone.
You leave?
I'm supposed
to be sitting across the table
from Yuri Suvav
in less than an hour.
If his government was involved,
President Taylor needs to know.
Following the death of Omar Hassan,
President Suvarov
was reportedly pessimistic
about the viability
of the peace treaty.
But rumors of a Russian withdrawal
were soon dismissed
by the White House.
Suvarov is expected
to arrive at the UN.
Yes?
It's Dalia Hassan.
I'll call her back.
She's outside, ma'am.
She says it's urgent.
Okay.
Madam President, forgive me.
I have just heard something
that is very disturbing.
What did you hear?
That the Russian government,
or people within the Russian government,
were involved
in the murder of my husband.
Where did you hear this?
My daughter received a phone call
from the journalist, Meredith Reed.
Have you spoken with h?
I've tried everything,
but I've been unable to reach her.
I came here to ask for your help
finding Miss Reed.
I need to know
if there is any truth in what she said.
We heard a rumor about the Russians
being involved as well.
And you didn't tell me?
Because we looked into it and found
that there was nothing backing it up.
It was a frivolous accusation.
Whatever else she may be,
Meredith Reed is not a frivolous woman.
She came to me,
someone she knew
would have every reason to doubt her.
I know that you want answers...
but we are signing the agreement
in less than an hour.
I feel
like you're not listening to me.
Before I sign a treaty with...
people who may have murdered
my husband,
I need help finding this woman.
I will do the best I can
in the time that we have left.
I don't think
I'm making myself clear.
Until I determine if it's true,
I will not sign this treaty.
Please, be reasonable.
This is my position,
Madam President.
I will not change my mind.
Then you...
You leave me no choice.
I had Meredith Reed arrested.
Why?
Because her allegations
would be too damaging.
That doesn't make any sense.
You wouldn't arrest someone for making
false allegations.
Unless they aren't false.
You knew!
You knew the Russians
were behind my husband's death,
and you said nothing?
I am so sorry.
It was an impossible situation.
I was trying to protect you.
Protect me?
You betrayed me!
We are about to complete
the most important diplomatic action
in generations.
Your husband sacrificed his life
to preserve the treaty...
How dare you invoke my husband!
He never would have stood for this!
This treaty happened
because he trusted you.
And even though every fiber in my being
wanted to go home
and grieve,
I carried on because I trusted you.
But not anymore.
I will not make peace
with the people who murdered my husband.
Or with you.
There will be no agreement.
I will be entering a formal complaint
with the United Nations,
demanding that you release Ms. Reed,
and disclose whatever evidence
you've kept from me
and from the rest of the world!
In one hour,
you will stand beside me
in the council chamber,
and you will sign the treaty
your husband and I agreed to.
I won't!
You will!
If you don't,
my administration...
will disclose hard,
indisputable evidence
that agents
inside your intelligence service
attempted to detonate
a nuclear device
on our soil, which will give me
all the justification I need
to retaliate against the IRK
with the full force
of the American military.
It will be decades,
before your country recovers.
But it doesn't need to come to that.
All you have to do
is sign the agreement.
First they murder my husband,
and this woman who has lied to me
is threatening my country!
I don't see a way out of this,
Madam President.
We can tell the world
what these Russian bastards did,
and how President Taylor
protected them.
We can take our case
directly to The Hague.
There is no case.
No proof
to support any of these accusations.
More important,
there are aylor's threats to consider.
We cannot dismiss them.
Our military can protect us
from incursion.
And if necessary,
we can reactivate our nuclear program!
Giving your husband's enemies exactly
what they wanted in the first place.
In addition to providing her
with even more of an excuse
to launch a preemptive military strike
against us.
I don't care what President Taylor said,
she wouldn't dare.
Can you really take that chance?
Yuri Suvarov's delegation
will be arriving any moment.
President Taylor is expecting you there
to greet him.
- What's going on?
- I spoke with Arlo.
He got a facial recognition
hit on Jack.
Where?
Inside our perimeter.
He's here, Cole.
He's been careful to avoid
all the cameras, but Arlo found this.
The 22nd floor of the Hart Building
across the street from the UN.
The software
picked up his reflection.
How did he get into?
According to the logs,
the only one that entered the building
within the past 20 minutes was Pillar.
Jack must have taken him hostage.
The windows on the east side give him
a line of sight down onto the podium.
- I'm going to go find him.
- I'm going with you.
You can't.
You'll just cause a fight.
- I'm the only one Jack will listen to.
- What if he doesn't?
20 minutes.
If you don't hear from me,
we'll follow through.
Sound the alarm about Jack
and secure Suvarov.
20 minutes.
Keep your comm open.
I want to know what's going on.
I can't.
CTU is monitoring all frequencies.
It's too risky.
All right.
At least take this.
- Thanks.
- Be careful.
Where's O'Brian headed?
She's running
a last-minute perimeter sweep.
By herself?
Keep a uplink open
with Suvarov's security people.
Let me know
when it's up and running.
As long as I can remember,
every time I've had to talk to you,
it seems, for some reasons,
I've started out
by telling you how sorry I am.
I'm not going to do that to you now.
You'll hear a lot of stories
about what I've done today.
Some of them may even be true.
But no one, and I mean no one...
can tell you why I did what I did
except for me.
And a lot of good people died today.
Not just President Hasn.
Operatives from CTU,
members of law enforcement agencies.
Who I was very close to.
President Suvarov's motorcade
has just rounded the corner.
Was Mrs. Hassan notified
of his arrival?
I believe so.
Yes or no, Tim? Which is it?
Is she coming or not?
Why wouldn't she be?
That we are all here together...
is a tribute to your persistence.
I am sorry for your loss.
I admired your husband very much.
We're wanted upstairs
for the press conference.
Yes, of course.
I know
this is very difficult for you.
There is nothing left
for either of us to say...
Chloe O'Brian, Director of CTU.
Master key and building schematics
you requested.
Good afternoon, fellow delegates
and ladies and gentlemen of the press.
The last 24 hours
have been the most...
difficult in this long
and challenging road
that we've all traveled together
to reach this moment.
The eyes of the world
are looking to the leaders
standing here with me now,
ready to usher
in a new era of...
transparency, honesty,
and trust.
They have each risen to this challenge
for the sake of world peace.
And the treaty
that they have created together
represents the culmination
of their courageous efforts.
Agent Burke?
I need you to assemble a ten-man squad
and deploy them to Sector C-7.
The Hart Building?
We've men on post.
Not enough if there's a threat
along that corridor.
Keep your men outside
until you hear otherwise.
What are you doing here?
Don't kill Suvarov.
There's another way.
Who knows where I am?
- Please listen.
- Who else knows?
If I don't get you out now,
Cole's gonna send in
every agent we have.
Jack, they're going to kill you.
There's a order to shoot you on sight.
I couldn't let that happen.
You should let them come after me.
You're my friend.
I didn't have a choice.
Neither do I.
Don't fight it.
Thank you.
Mr. Secretary General,
distinguished delegates,
honored guests,
today the world
takes a tremendous step...
You watching?
I have a five-five-six rifle
pointed straight at your head.
The bullet
travels 2,900 feet per second.
If you move, you're a dead man.
Which means you need to do what I say.
Do you understand?
I told you everything I know.
And you thought I believed you?
And aside from me,
Novakovich was the only one
who knew that Suvarov
was calling the shots.
What do you want?
Call President Suvarov
and have him meet you
where you are as soon as
the conference is over.
What do I tell him?
Try the truth for a change.
Tell him you've credible intelligence
about a threat to his life.