Jack!
We need a medic!
The bioagent is more
virulent than we thought.
All we're doing here is just
masking the symptoms. I understand.
There's something you
may want to consider.
What's that?
A possible treatment
using stems cells from
a genetically-compatible donor.
I saw your file.
It says you have a daughter.
I don't want my daughter
involved in this.
Daddy.
Agent Walker told me
that there's a chance,
a small chance that I could help you,
and you don't want me to.
I'm dying,
and whatever small chance there is
to stop that from happening,
it is not worth the pain
for me to let you sit
there and watch me die.
Jack, Hodges has 13 Python missiles
armed with the bioweapons.
He demanded that I recall the planes,
or he would launch.
Tony Almeida is still
inside Starkwood.
He believes he can gain
access to the fuel depot,
and lay a series of explosive charges,
and take the missiles out.
What do you think you're doing?
You're gonna take me
down to the fuel tanks.
You're too late.
Jonas, we've taken
out your missiles.
It's over,
and you're under arrest.
You can't even begin to
imagine what you're up against.
What are you talking about?
You'll find out.
Agent Moss,
this is Davis at Auxiliary Gate Six.
I have a Starkwood
op in custody.
He was carrying a canister
of the bioweapon.
Are you sure?
I'm looking at it right now.
One of the Starkwood ops--
he's got a canister of the bioweapon.
So I need you to close
down all access roads,
and alert perimeter
units and Metro Police.
Janis, get me D.C. Metro.
I'm gonna pursue from the air.
Let's go!
Come on!
I'm okay.
Tony! Tony!
Oh, God. Oh...
Yeah?
Patricia, Matt.
I just got off with
Secret Service.
You're cleared with White House
security at the south entrance.
How soon do you think
you'll get there?
Uh, within the half-hour.
Do you have any more information
why Hodges was arrested?
They didn't give me a lot.
Apparently, Jonas was in some kind of
policy meeting with the president,
and things got out of hand.
That's when he requested
his favorite attorney.
I'm flattered.
I'll call you after
I've spoken to him.
Hurry it up.
Janis, we just got an
ID on the suspect.
One of Starkwood's
security cameras
picked him up leaving the compound;
he was carrying a backpack.
Robert Galvez, two-year Starkwood
employee, former special forces.
Relay that information to Larry--
he needs to know who he's tracking.
I've been trying.
He's not answering his comm.
How far away is backup?
They're still a few minutes out,
but Agent Park's teams
have secured a
four-block perimeter.
The bioweapons canister is
secured within the cordon.
Get Galvez' picture
and description out
to Tactical and distribute
department wide.
And keep trying Larry.
To all units,
I'm uploading a photo of the suspect
to all units' PDAs.
His name is Robert Galvez.
Be advised he has advanced
military training,
so proceed with caution.
Roger that.
Almeida? Almeida,
are you there?
Are you in a secure location?
I'm holed up in a storage yard
near the projects on Jefferson.
But I just spotted a patrol.
I think I better keep moving.
No, don't.
The FBI's got the entire
perimeter locked down.
And they know who you are.
How? TONY: They have a picture.
Which means the search
teams can ID you on sight.
Just stay put until
I can get a read
on their search protocols,
and I'll guide you out.
I should have never have let
you talk me into helping you.
I promise you,
that canister you stole for me
is worth a lot of money to
the people I'm working for.
Hell of a lot of good that
money's gonna do me in prison.
Just shut up and do
what I tell you to do.
Guard the canister, stay put,
and wait for my call.
We've got agents down.
Get a med team out here now.
Almeida?
Almeida, can you hear me?
What happened?
Where's the suspect?
He ambushed us.
Did you see where he went?
I don't know.
Renee, I just got confirmation the
Tac Team has arrived at the scene.
Do we have a 20 on Larry?
Not yet.
Excuse me, Agent Walker.
I know you're busy. Kim.
I just came to say good-bye.
Good-bye? Where are you going?
Back to L.A.
Um, I don't understand.
You're not going through with the
treatment to help your father?
I mean,
it's his only chance for a cure.
I know that, and so does he.
But it's a slim one,
and he believes
it's not worth taking, so...
If he's going to die,
he wants it to be on his terms.
Yes, but can't you
change his mind?
I would think you'd know by now that
no one can change my father's mind
when it's made up.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I put
you in this position.
No, don't be.
I'm grateful to you,
Agent Walker.
My father and I got to say a
lot of things to each other.
I wish I could have said more, but I
don't want to cause him any more pain.
Renee?
Agent Park is on
the phone for you.
I need to take this.
I understand.
Good luck.
This is Walker.
Agent Moss is dead.
What?
Apparently, he was killed in
an ambush by the suspect.
The chopper pilot, too.
Tony Almeida's been shot,
but he's alive.
I've got medical personnel
working on him now.
Agent Walker?
Do we have any lead on Galvez?
No, but the area's
been cordoned off.
He couldn't have gotten far.
We're setting up an operations base here
on the scene to coordinate the manhunt.
How do you want to proceed?
Me?
You're the ranking
agent in charge now.
Maintain the perimeter.
Begin a south-north sweep.
I'll chopper out a team and meet
you there as soon as I can.
Agent Walker,
I have more than enough personnel.
You don't need to be involved
in the search. Yes, I do.
Keep me posted if
you hear anything.
Yes, ma'am.
Larry?
He was killed in a
shootout with the suspect.
Oh, God.
I need you to brief the White
House on what's happened.
Call Dr. Macer and have her deploy
a HazMat team to the perimeter line.
Assemble a team to
chopper out with me.
I'm so sorry.
Someone's going to need to
notify Larry's ex-wife.
Probably shouldn't be me.
It's okay.
I'll take care of it.
All right.
We've debriefed on hours 8:00 a.m.
to 3:00 p.m.
pertaining to the CIP recovery
and the capture of Ike Dubaku.
Now, Mr.
Bauer, maybe you'd like to take a break.
No. We need to finish
this while I still can.
Let's go.
Now, according to your
earlier statement,
it was about this
time you received
intel regarding the imminent
attack on the White House.
Tony Almeida provided me with the intel,
but we did not know
the White House was a
target at that time.
And who was Mr.
Almeida's source?
He was interrogating
a mercenary.
Did Almeida give you a name?
Um...
Yeah. Sorry.
Car... Cardiff.
He said his name was Vincent Cardiff.
Did you yourself
question the source?
No.
He didn't survive
Tony's interrogation,
but he was the one who provided us
with the intel on the upcoming attack.
But we did not know that the White House
was the intended target at that time.
We did not know the White House
was the intended target...
Mr. Bauer?
You sure you don't want
to take that break?
Um, I'm repeating myself again.
I'm sorry.
Here's the data file
you asked for, sir.
Tom, we need to move.
Agent Walker's got
our assignments.
Excuse me.
We're not going to lose
control of this situation.
I know that most of you are tired,
working double shifts,
but I need each and every
one of you focused and alert
if we are going to
locate the suspect
and secure the bioweapon
canister that he's carrying.
While I am out in the field,
you will pass all pertinent information
out of this office
through Janis.
Let's get to work.
Adams, you and your men are with me.
Renee? Renee?
I'll meet you at the helipad.
The bioweapon's
still out there?
We have it contained.
Wait a second.
Just tell me what
the hell is going on.
A Starkwood operative by
the name of Robert Galvez
got away with a canister
of the pathogen.
We have him trapped inside a perimeter
a mile or so from Starkwood's compound.
Is Larry in command
of the perimeter?
He was killed in a firefight.
What?
Tony was injured.
He's at the scene with
the advance team.
Larry's dead?
We have two agents down.
Yes. I have to go.
You're lucky.
An inch to the left,
the bullet might have
nicked your splenic artery.
You need to get yourself checked
out at the hospital, sir.
Yeah, I can't do
that right now.
Let me get you
something for the pain.
No, I,
I need to keep my head clear.
Sweep 9, this is Mobile Command,
what's your status?
Mobile Command, this is Sweep 9,
Southeast grid 211 clear.
Moving on. Copy that, Sweep 9.
Sweep 7, what's your position?
Clearing 214. Nothing so far.
No sign of him?
Don't worry.
We'll find him.
You should get some rest.
Thanks.
...this is Mobile Command,
status check, over.
Yeah? Yeah, they're sweeping north,
clearing grids.
You've got a clear path on Jefferson
all the way up to 12th and 13th Street.
That should be the last
sector they're searching.
Judging by their progress,
it'll give you about 30 minutes.
Should be plenty of time.
Time for what?
You still got that
C-4 I gave you?
Yeah. I got it. All right.
I want you to find a structure, a store,
warehouse, something big enough
where they have to
enter and search.
We need to draw as many of them into
the building as possible, then blow it.
You want me to blow up a
couple of dozen FBI agents?
You got a problem with that?
They're still gonna have
the perimeter locked down.
I don't see how doing this is gonna
get me out of here with the canister.
Yeah, I've got that worked out.
Jack, what the hell
are you doing?
I'm going with you.
You're ill.
If my condition interferes with
your operation, I will stand down.
I give you my word. Jack...
You want keep arguing about this,
waste more time? Fine.
I'm not getting out.
Good morning.
Ms. Eames.
You're Jonas Hodges' attorney.
That's right.
They told us to expect you.
I just need you to place your
thumb against the glass.
Okay. Sergeant Cadden will
escort you to the holding area.
Thank you.
How could this man have
gotten out of Starkwood
with a canister
of the bioweapon?
No one's sure.
But he's already
murdered four people.
Including Larry Moss.
The FBI has tracked him to a
nearby residential district.
They've sealed off the area and
are conducting a thorough search.
Mom, this man Galvez is
a Starkwood operative.
Clearly, Hodges is behind this.
Maybe.
What do you mean, maybe?
As Hodges was taken away,
he said it wasn't over.
He alluded to others,
called himself
a small cog in a very large
machine that I wouldn't
be able to stop.
He was ranting.
That doesn't mean he
wasn't telling the truth.
We need to find out what
Hodges knows about this.
I want him taken to the
FBI for interrogation.
He's a sociopath, Mom.
He's not going to talk.
He's going to want
to make some kind of deal in
exchange for his cooperation.
Mom, you're not
considering that...
Olivia...
You know what this man is,
what he did to Roger.
Just get him to FBI.
Mr. Hodges.
Your attorney's
here to see you.
Well, it's about damn time.
We're going to
need some privacy.
You're a little
taller than her.
But it's a good look for you.
Hello, Jonas.
I'm not going to
ask how you got in.
But I'm definitely interested in
how you're going to get me out.
Jonas, you're in a very
difficult position.
And your actions today have put everyone
else in a very difficult position.
Oh, I see.
I've upset the cart, have I?
Everyone's bent out of shape.
Well, where the hell were they when
the government came after my company?
When Senator Mayer and his
subpoena-waving goon squad
were trying to ruin me
and everything I've built?
You would have been
protected, Jonas.
You and Starkwood.
But you jeopardized the plan.
That bioweapon that you developed for
us was not intended for personal use.
The consensus is that
you've had some sort of...
psychotic break.
Well, the consensus is wrong.
Coming from you right now,
that's not much comfort.
I want to talk to them.
Get some form of
communication between us.
I want to talk to them.
I think it's a little
late for that, Jonas.
You've brought undue attention
by showing your hand.
Exposing yourself.
And I'm sure you could understand
their concern that you may,
in fact,
expose the others as well.
How can I do that?
I don't know who they are.
You know enough,
and they need to be certain.
I think we can agree that
there's no reason for your family
to pay for your mistakes.
Is that why you're here?
To threaten my family.
On the contrary.
I came to guarantee
your family's safety.
If you do the right thing.
This will induce cardiac arrest,
and leave no trace in your system.
A natural, dignified death.
Without you to prosecute,
the case against you and your
company will be difficult,
likely impossible,
preserving at least some small part of
Starkwood's legacy of patriotic service.
Which I know is very
important to you.
Party's over, counselor.
We're moving him to the Bureau.
My client has invoked his right
to silence and to counsel.
No one speaks to him unless in
my presence, is that understood?
In some countries they'd
have shot him by now.
Process him out.
Step out of the cell
and raise your arms.
Yes?
I met with him.
And?
I'm quite certain he
understands our terms.
They're transferring him to
the FBI for interrogation.
Will that be a problem?
Hopefully, it'll
just pressure him
to resolve the situation
sooner rather than later.
I'll be happy when
this is behind us.
Have you heard from Almeida?
He called in before
I met with Hodges.
Has he secured the canister?
Soon.
He's your guy.
Better not screw this up.
Tony's been the one bright spot
in an otherwise dreary day.
I have faith he'll
come through.
Yeah?
I found a place to set up.
It's an abandoned apartment building
just shy of the north perimeter line.
1297 Rincon, corner of 12th.
Yeah, I see it.
Sweep teams are just entering
three sectors to the south.
You've got less
than 20 minutes.
That doesn't give me much time.
No, it doesn't, so maybe you should
get off the phone and get to it.
I lost two partners in a row.
Early on.
I couldn't handle it.
I guess that's why over the last ten
years, I've pretty much worked alone.
It's all right for you to
be feeling what you feel.
And if you can't do this tonight,
that's all right, too.
Just don't try and pretend like
you're not feeling anything.
That's how you make a mistake.
Please, Jack, don't tell me what to
feel and don't tell me how to feel it.
Agent Walker.
He's over there.
Jack! Where is he?
This way. You okay?
Yeah, I got lucky.
The bullet went
straight through.
Didn't think I'd
see you out here.
I'm only here for observation.
You do not have to do this.
Show me.
I'm sorry about Larry.
How the hell did this happen?
It all went down pretty fast,
I mean...
We were ambushed before we
got out of the helicopter.
The chopper pilot
was hit first.
I was unarmed, so Larry laid
down cover so I could get clear.
I don't remember a lot,
but I definitely heard auto-fire.
As I was tagged, Larry came over to
help me out and that's when he was hit.
I blacked out after that.
But I'm pretty sure
Larry saved my life.
Larry was hit with
heavy ordnance.
Shotgun rounds, armor piercing.
You were obviously hit
with something smaller.
Jacketed. MED TECH:
I treated Mr. Almeida.
His wound was consistent
with a nine millimeter.
JACK: You sure it wasn't a .45?
Not likely--
the entry was too small. Why?
Because you have spent
.45 casings in evidence.
Galvez had access to the weapons
inside the FBI vehicle he stole.
He probably switched in
the middle of the fight.
That many weapons?
In the time frame that
you described the ambush?
It doesn't add up.
Okay, so what are you saying?
Someone was with him.
Like I said,
it all happened pretty fast, but...
I mean, I didn't think so.
I guess it makes sense.
One man didn't do this alone.
He had help.
I'll tell Park to
alert the field.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Good.
Hello?
Did I wake you?
Who could sleep after
what happened today?
How did it go with your father?
Sweetheart, what is it?
What happened?
He's dying, Stephen.
What?
He was exposed to something.
Like a biological agent.
It had something to do with the
attacks that took place earlier today.
Kim, honey, I'm so sorry.
Um, isn't there anything
that they can do?
No.
I'm coming back home.
Don't you want to stay? Don't you
wanna be with him as long as you can?
My presence,
with what he's going through right now,
will only make things worse.
Did you at least, um, did you
tell him about his granddaughter?
Kim?
I couldn't, Stephen.
I couldn't bring
myself to tell him
I wasn't the only person
he was leaving behind.
Telling him about Teri
would've only made it worse.
I'm gonna try and
get on the 7:10.
If I do, I'll be back in L.A.
by 9:00.
Okay.
You can always leave later,
if you change your mind.
t.
I love you both.
We love you, too.
Bye.
Mobile Command,
this is Sweep 9.
221 is clear.
Copy, 9. Proceed to 224.
Why has that area of the
grid not been cleared?
Sweep 3,
why have you not cleared 219?
Mobile Command, we're encountering some
resistance from neighborhood residents.
They're not happy about
their homes being searched
without a warrant at
2:30 in the morning.
I'm concerned about their safety,
not their happiness.
Whoever is helping Galvez
may be providing him shelter
in one of those houses.
If those civilians are
interfering in that sweep,
arrest them, but get that
area cleared.
Do you understand?
Copy.
Jack?
Excuse me...
It's an antiseizure medicine.
I should've used it earlier.
Jack, what are you
doing out here?
Why don't you go back to FBI
medical and let them treat you?
There is no treatment.
There's no cure.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
Yeah.
Why are you in the field?
Agent Walker just lost
her partner, Tony.
I thought I could help.
I owe her that much.
Agent Stoller to Mobile Command.
Code Yellow.
Go ahead, Agent Stoller,
this is Mobile Command.
Are you reporting
a Code Yellow?
Affirmative.
I have a confirmed visual
on the target suspect
with the canister.
Repeat, confirmed visual
of suspect and canister.
Agent Park, may I?
Agent Stoller,
this is Jack Bauer.
Is Galvez with someone?
Agent Stoller?
Negative. He's alone.
Copy that.
What's his 20?
Entering an abandoned apartment
building on the south side
of Rincon and 12th.
I am in pursuit.
Try to maintain a visual
and wait for backup.
Do not engage
until we get there.
Copy that.
PARK: All primary units
respond to 12th and Rincon.
Suspect sighted entering
a building with canister.
Code Yellow. Agent Park?
I want a secure net
around the building,
agents at all exits and I want
sharpshooters covering each
of the four exposures.
Yes, ma'am.
Jack.
I can't.
It's all right, I'll be fine.
I'll stay back,
I'll watch operations.
You be careful out there.
I still think Galvez
has a partner.
You watch your back.
"Hellfire." You served
with the 27th in Pakistan.
Two tours, sir.
Did you, by any chance,
encounter any Starkwood units?
There was a force protection
team attached by my C.O.
They fought with you.
Yes, sir.
Side by side.
Soldier...
How would you rate
their professionalism?
Their performance under fire.
Thank you, son.
Just made my day.
All right, let's go.
Our orders are to deliver the
prisoner to the rear entrance at FBI.
The White House wants
to keep this low-key.
Sarge!
This is Sergeant Cadden.
Prisoner's in severe cardiac
and respiratory distress.
We are rerouting to West
Arlington Hospital.
Need emergency medical
team standing by!
Go, go!
Assemble the teams. You got it.
Agent Stoller,
this is Agent Walker, do you copy?
I copy you, Agent Walker.
What is your position?
East stairwell between the
first and second floor.
Suspect with canister has
moved to the top floor.
Do you have any indication
that he's not alone?
Negative. Not at this time.
All right, stand by.
We're coming to you.
Agent Stoller puts the suspect
somewhere on the second floor.
However, there's no guarantee that
he's the only hostile in the building.
Therefore, we stick to SOP,
clearing room by room.
Agent Park and I will lead two teams,
East and West.
Check your weapons
and headsets.
We move in 60 seconds.
All right, you heard her,
you guys are with me...
Mobile Command, this is Walker.
Go ahead, Agent Walker.
We're about to
enter the building.
Have HazMat teams on alert,
in case the canister gets breached.
Copy that.
How you holding up?
Better, thanks.
Excuse me.
This is Bauer.
Mr. Bauer,
this is Agent Mizelli.
Sorry to bother you with this,
but I need to follow up on
something from our debrief.
Agent, this isn't a good time.
Some new information has come to light,
and I need
to clear up a discrepancy.
What discrepancy?
You told me Tony Almeida's
source on the White House attack
was a man identified to
you as Vincent Cardiff?
Yeah, that's right.
Is there a possibility you
misremembered the name?
No, I don't think so.
Are you sure?
You yourself have voiced some
concern about your own acuity.
Hold on.
What is this here?
Sir?
Agent Mizelli, I'm gonna have to
get back to you. Locator codes
for all units'
radio transponders.
Are they in real time?
Yes, sir.
Can you do a map overlay?
It'll take a minute.
Get it done.
What's going on, Jack?
I'm not sure yet.
Ready? Now.
Right there,
there's Stoller's transponder.
He's not even in the building.
Agent Walker, this is Jack.
Get your men out
of the building.
It's a trap. Jack, what?
Stoller's not even in there.
Get your men out now.
RENEE: Code Blue.
Repeat: Code Blue.
Agent Walker, Agent Park!
Get us a vehicle now!
All perimeter teams,
this is Park.
Agents are down.
Report to 12th and Rincon.
We need assistance.
Negative, negative,
disregard that order.
Maintain your positions.
I repeat,
maintain your positions.
Bauer, what the
hell are you doing?
They are trying to
pull you off the line.
You leave a hole in that perimeter,
we are going to lose the canister.
Tell your men to stand fast.
Medivac is on its way.
Get them in the air now!
Jack, I'm going in.
Agent Park.
How many men are unaccounted for?
Still assessing.
There were at least 30 of us in the
building when it went up.
- And Agent Walker?
- I don't know.
Renee, this is Jack.
Do you copy?
Damn it.
Almeida.
You got the canister?
Yeah.
Let me see.
Hurry up,
we need to get moving.
Let's go.
Renee!
Renee...
Renee! Jack.
Are you okay?
Yeah, but he's not breathing.
We need a medic!
They've got him.
I want to get you out of here.
Come on, let's go now.
How'd you know it was a trap?
Stoller's transponder was
outside of the building.
They were trying to thin our ranks,
create a diversion.
Has the cordon been breached?
No, I told the men to
maintain their positions.
The perimeter's secure.
It's almost like
they knew, Jack.
They would have needed time to wire
this building with explosives.
This was the last sector
we were due to search.
You think they knew your sweep patterns?
They must have.
Oh, my God.
Jack, what is it?
I'll meet you back
at your vehicle.
Hey, you want me to take him?
No, I got him.
They need your help inside.
Agent Mizelli.
This is Bauer.
You said you wanted to talk to me
about Tony's suspect
Vincent Cardiff.
Yes, yes,
thanks for getting back to me.
Listen, uh,
you told me that he expired
during the course of Tony
Almeida's interrogation.
Yeah, that's what Tony told me.
Well, it can't be him.
What are you talking about?
Vincent Cardiff was picked up
over an hour ago by Customs,
trying to cross the
border into Canada.
Are you sure?
Look, I'm positive,
I've got his arrest report right here.
Cardiff's alive.
Were there any signs
from his interrogation--
physical violence,
abuse, anything at all?
Nothing's indicated
on the report.
That's why I was asking if maybe you
had mistaken the name Almeida gave you.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Tony!
Yeah.
We need to talk.
Sure.
What's going on?
I told you earlier today, if you were
lying to me I'd kill you myself.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Cardiff, Vincent Cardiff-- you said he
was killed during his interrogation.
Yeah, so?
He's alive and well, in custody, and
he's showing no signs of physical abuse.
Explain that.
All right, look,
Jack, I'm sorry.
Cardiff knew that by spilling that
intel, he was going to get killed,
so I cut a deal with him.
I told him I'd
let the FBI think
he was dead,
so he could walk away and disappear.
I thought it was just
a meaningless lie.
You and I have been doing
this long enough to know
that there is no such
thing as a meaningless lie.
How are you involved in this?
You're not making
any sense, Jack.
That intel was good.
Without it you'd have never been in
the White House to save the president.
What is your involvement?!
You're not thinking straight.
How were you shot?
Does Galvez even
have a second man...
or was it just you?
Just stop and listen
to what you're saying.
It's insane. It's paranoia.
Now, why don't you
put the gun down?
Don't you move!
The toxin is starting to
affect your judgment.
That's what's happening.
You can see that, right?
Is this what you're
looking for?
I never wanted to
hurt you, Jack.
I told you to stay out of it.
But you wouldn't listen,
would you?
Can we get some help here?
This man's having a seizure.
Stand back, please.
Go get my bag and call Dr.
Mason, stat.
I don't see anything.
The wound must be posterior.
Sir, I need to turn
you on your side.
Put it down and
keep driving. Now!