Subtitles: Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu
You know I have the fuel rods.
But I have no desire
to harm innocent Americans.
And yet you're threatening them
with a bomb.
What I'm asking for is simple.
Turn over Hassan.
That will never happen.
You have exactly one hour
to change your mind.
We have an out here.
We should take it.
Give in to the demand
to turn over Hassan?
I will not sell him out
to the very terrorists
that we are determined to defeat.
- What are you suggesting?
- A covert action.
We deliver Hassan to the terrorists,
but make it look like
they took him hostage.
I'm begging you.
Don't do this.
Don't betray the President.
All right.
My God!
Call a medic.
We wait to acquire Hassan
before calling an ambulance.
Understand?
Take the weapon off now!
A dirty bomb
will be detonated in New York
unless we deliver Hassan.
- Does the President know about this?
- She's refusing to deal.
This is General Brucker's operation.
What are you doing?
This is on you now.
You have to deliver Hassan.
I don't take orders
from anybody but the President.
Now, move.
Are the Americans
handing over Hassan or not?
The only information is that he's being
transported to McGuire Air Force Base.
So, President Taylor doesn't intend
to give him up.
The President has not responded.
Start the countdown.
The NYPD
will handle HAZMAT and triage,
the National Guard
will control the streets,
and I've got
an army battalion standing by.
A dirty bomb is about to go off
in Manhattan, Commander.
I'd plan for mass panic.
Ethan Kanin is dying back there.
We need to get him medical help.
- We will.
- I mean now.
No, not until our team
completes its mission.
When we have the bomb,
then we'll get your friend help.
Madam President.
Carry on.
General, what's our status
on the ground?
The civilian first responders
are positioning for rapid deployment,
and we've got army support
available as necessary.
At this point, only command level knows
we're anticipating a radiological device
but people
are quick to connect the dots.
- Word will get out.
- Yeah. I'd like to get ahead of that.
I've drafted an address
for the networks.
I need you to look at it.
And Ethan has to read it too.
He wasn't in his office.
Do you know where he is?
I'll go find him.
Less than ten minutes.
Dear God, this bomb cannot go off.
I'm sorry, Madam President,
but we have to prepare for the worst.
What are
the latest casualty figures?
Median scenario shows
58,000 dead over three days
due to the bomb and ensuing panic.
But who knows?
Maybe we'll get lucky.
Let me know
the second President Hassan arrives.
This is not right.
My life for so many others.
- It's not right.
- The President doesn't see it that way.
She knows I would disagree.
That's why she kept me out of it.
You are more than just one life.
You are the best hope of ending a war
that has lasted for decades.
You must understand
Taylor's trying to protect that.
This is not acceptable.
Get in here.
Get down.
- What are you doing?
- He's slowing us down.
Don't worry. He'll be fine.
His injuries aren't lethal.
Can I talk to you?
What?
Hassan isn't happy about Taylor's
response to the ultimatum.
Doesn't matter.
- He's a head of state. Maybe it should.
- It's not our call.
If he wants to take it up with her,
he can do it when he sees...
Mom!
What?
- Throw your gun down.
- What are you doing?
Kick it to me.
Have you lost your mind?
You, outside!
Back up inside!
- Sir, you do not want to do...
- Just shut up and move it inside!
I'm giving you what you want.
Here, take the gun.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Dalia.
My life for tens of thousands?
- I couldn't live with that.
- Omar, don't.
- You can't give yourself up.
- I have to.
What if they're lying?
What if they blow up
the bomb anyway?
At least I've tried
to stop the attack,
and I've failed.
- But if I don't even try...
- Father, please.
You stay here with Kayla.
I'll send someone to pick you up.
I won't leave you.
- Do as I say.
- If you want me to stay here,
then lock me in that room
because I won't let you
walk to your death!
- I won't leave you!
- Dalia, I said do as I say!
Back in the room!
Now!
In the room!
We've got less than five minutes.
We got to move.
Mr. President, you can't trust him!
You can't trust him!
Come on.
These people owe you their lives, sir.
You're doing the right thing.
Excuse me.
- Do you have the package?
- Yes.
You're cutting it damn close.
You know that?
There were complications.
Jack Bauer found out
about our operation.
He's no longer a problem.
Casualties?
The entire unit.
Everyone but me.
You need to know that President Hassan
is cooperating with us.
He's here by choice.
What are you saying?
That he would have given himself up?
Yes, sir.
We got to move.
All right.
Stay on the line.
He'll be dead soon
if we don't do something.
Along with half of New York.
Bishop's on the line.
He's got Hassan.
Get ready to make the call.
Bishop, we're live.
You there?
We got two minutes.
Do it.
Rob Weiss,
President Taylor's chief of staff.
- Do you have Hassan?
- We're prepared to make the exchange.
- Prove it.
- Bishop, put him on.
He wants to talk to you.
This is President Hassan.
I'm prepared to give myself up,
if you stop the bomb.
So, President Taylor
changed her mind.
She wasn't willing
to meet your demands. I am.
- But I need assurances.
- Assurances?
- That the exchange will...
- It will happen exactly as you're told.
What you'll do
is exactly what I say.
Damn it.
We did what you asked.
Quit stalling.
We're running out of time.
He cut us off.
A minute and a half
till the bomb goes off.
Stop the bomb.
Hassan will be arriving.
You know what to do.
All right.
Bomb was supposed to go off yet.
There's no report of an explosion.
- What's happening on the ground?
- Sweep teams are looking. No luck.
According to the deadline,
we're on borrowed time.
The bomb is still out there,
still a threat.
We may have caught a break here.
Let's use it.
It's Jack, I need your help.
Reception is terrible.
I can barely hear you.
Can you hear me now?
President Hassan is giving himself up.
That's why the bomb didn't go off.
No one here knows that.
And no one else can
until I talk to the President.
- What's going on?
- I don't have time to explain.
Please, just contact Tim Woods.
He can get me a clean line.
But no one else can know
that I'm calling. Do you understand?
I'll call you back.
Who was that?
Search team.
Requesting updated grid assignments.
- Do you need some help?
- I'll ask if I do.
We're clear!
Keep them up here on the landing.
Nothing.
Get them back to President Taylor.
- What about you?
- I'm going to look for Hassan.
I just got off the phone with CTU.
We're going to find your husband.
But it's not safe here for you.
Continue on to the Air Force Base.
Agent Walker will help you get there.
She can be trusted completely.
Mr. Bauer, my father, he did
- what he thought was best.
- I know.
We're gonna get him back,
but right now we need to move. Let's go.
Jack, he gave himself up willingly.
- Maybe we should just let this happen.
- I already told you, it's not our call.
The President asked me to protect him.
That's what I'm gonna try and do.
So, please, just get them
to the Air Force Base.
Taxi!
- This is Bauer.
- I got a secure line.
Good. I need you
to do something else for me.
I'm on Seventh Avenue
between 53rd and 54th.
There's a security camera mid-block.
If you can get a feed, roll it back.
President Hassan was standing here
ten minutes ago.
I'll check.
Seven minutes past the deadline.
Do we have any idea
why the bomb didn't go off?
No. We're polling our civilian
counterparts, trying to determine that.
Maybe it's like you said.
We got lucky.
At the moment it looks that way.
What about President Hassan?
When will he arrive?
His transport was a Secret Service
operation. I'm not really in the loop.
- I'll look into it.
- No, I'd rather you find Ethan.
- I'll page him.
- No,
not page him, find him.
I need him here.
Please.
It's an urgent call from Homeland.
Excuse me.
President Taylor.
Madam President, Jack Bauer.
Please don't say my name
or react openly
to what I'm about to tell you.
President Hassan
is no longer in my custody.
He got away
and he's trying to hand himself over.
- That's why the bomb didn't detonate.
- I'm afraid I don't understand.
You're being betrayed
by General Brucker.
40 minutes ago we were attacked
by mercenaries under his command.
Go on.
We managed to fight off the attack,
but Hassan turned himself over
to one of them in an effort
to stop the bomb from going off.
As we speak,
they're preparing to hand him over.
I'm assuming that is still something
that is unacceptable to you.
That is correct.
General Brucker leads this operation.
He communicates with the terrorists.
I need to know
where the exchange is gonna take place.
- You need to confront him now.
- I understand.
As soon as you have anything,
contact CTU.
- I will.
- Thank you, ma'am.
Come with me, please.
- Chloe, you still there?
- I'm here.
What do you got?
Got the security camera feed
you were talking about.
Hassan got into a black SUV
at 6:08 with one other guy.
That's got to be the merc
he handed himself over to.
They were headed west
on 53rd Street.
I lost them
when they turned north on Tenth Avenue.
Redirect the satellites
to the Upper West Wide.
I'm on my way.
What now?
Who's this?
Listen carefully.
Hand the phone to the driver.
It's you, isn't it?
Hand it to him now.
He wants to talk to you.
Bishop.
This is what you need to do.
Listen to my instructions
and follow them.
Step out,
leaving the keys in the ignition.
Take the phone with you.
Do it now.
Walk toward the intersection.
When the light changes,
cross the street.
Stay inside the crosswalk.
Where's the bomb?
Do what I say.
The deal was Hassan for the bomb.
The light's changed.
Move.
Where is it?
Do what I say.
Shut up.
Listen.
Stop now.
Don't turn around
or you get nothing.
Stand there and wait.
Turn around. Walk toward the stand.
Look down.
Show me your hands.
Hands!
On the dash.
Where's the bomb?
Where is it?
Where is he?
- The General's in Mr. Kanin's office.
- With Ethan?
Not sure.
No one's seen him in nearly an hour.
There's something you need to know.
Your chief of staff
is with the General.
They appear
to be in on this together.
Are you saying
Rob Weiss betrayed me, too?
I'm afraid so.
Do it.
Don't move.
Hands where we can see them!
Up!
Call medical.
Against the wall,
hands behind your head.
You need to see this.
Is he still alive?
He's had a serious cardiac event.
Get him out of here!
You stay.
Where is President Hassan?
Damn you, Rob.
Where is he?
I don't know.
Don't lie to me!
Tell me where he is.
No, I cannot.
And if it makes any difference,
this was not an easy decision.
It makes no difference at all.
It wasn't your decision to make.
With all due respect,
you were not elected to sentence
tens of thousands of Americans to death.
Is that how you justify this?
You have sold out a peace
I committed this administration to.
I've protected New York
and given you plausible deniability
- in an impossible situation.
- I don't want deniability.
I want Hassan!
We are on the verge of a peace
that has eluded this planet
for 50 years,
and you are throwing it away!
Tell me where he is.
The charge is treason.
It carries the death penalty,
and so help me God,
I'll throw the switch myself.
Tell me where he is.
It's not too late.
Too late.
They have Hassan.
We have the bomb.
The bomb's at Amsterdam and 93rd.
We'll get NEST team there
as soon as possible.
Damn you, Rob.
Really, Madam President?
New York City is safe.
Take him away.
Your attention.
I've just spoken with the President
at McGuire.
Rogue operatives have handed Hassan over
to the terrorists.
In return, they've got the location
of the dirty bomb.
93rd and Amsterdam.
Jack Bauer and NEST are already on-site
and disarming the bomb.
Our focus
is to recover President Hassan.
I've got satellite feed at 93rd.
Looks like we're back in business.
Put it up on screen, Arlo.
We know that Hassan was handed over
at that location
approximately ten minutes ago.
NSA feed only gives us still images.
We might have missed him.
We didn't.
There's Bishop's SUV.
- They must be close, find them.
- Someone's approaching the SUV.
- Any idea who that is?
- I can try to clean up the image.
Lost it.
They were heading east.
We can use the traffic cam footage.
You and Dana, find that vehicle.
As soon as you reacquire it,
let Jack know.
Dana, where are you going?
Hastings wants us to do this.
- I'll reroute some of the servers.
- Not now.
- It'll give us more processing speed.
- We can work with what we have.
Those are the rods
we were looking for,
packed in enough C4
to irradiate half of Manhattan.
As soon as they're extracted,
I want you to contact CTU.
Thanks.
Transfer him
back to holding in medical.
- Contact Hastings as you're en route.
- So it's real.
A dirty bomb.
Then we succeeded.
We saved Manhattan.
You betrayed your President
and your country.
Get him out of here.
- This is Bauer.
- It's Chloe.
We found Hassan.
He's heading north
on Amsterdam in a black SUV.
- How far north?
- About... 30 blocks ahead of you.
The President wants us to do
everything we can to recover Hassan.
She wants you to lead the operation.
- How many men are with him?
- We think only one, the driver.
Chloe, find me
a suitable ambush point.
I want clean lines of fire
from rooftop and street level.
To protect Hassan, we must take the car
and the driver out at the same time.
Tac teams are standing by.
- Is Cole with them?
- We expect him here any minute.
Then he'll have to quarterback
this op from CTU.
I'll get you real-time updates
on Hassan's position.
Copy that.
Cole's back.
I'll go get him.
- I'm so glad you're back.
- Me, too.
I heard we recovered the bomb.
Only 'cause Hassan
gave himself up to the terrorists.
Jack's putting together
an intercept operation.
He wants you to run it from here.
You'd better bring me up to speed.
What happened
to that probation officer?
I convinced him
I didn't know anything. He left.
- That's good.
- Yeah, it's good.
We'll get through this.
We will.
We should go.
You don't have to do this, Tarin.
You can pull over right now,
stop the car.
Believe me, I want to do this.
If you hate me so much,
stand against me at home.
Join the opposition.
Fight me openly, honorably.
I don't need to fight you, Hassan.
You have already lost.
So tell me, what's the plan?
You'll put me on trial?
A dark room and a video camera,
I suppose.
A man hiding behind a mask...
will read a list of my crimes
and cut off my head with a sword.
The world will be impressed.
You've done worse in your prisons.
What I did...
I did to unite our country,
to make us stronger.
That's a lie.
You just wanted
to hand us over to the Americans.
I wanted us to rejoin the world.
I wanted us to have peace.
You wanted
the cover of Time magazine.
You think I don't know you, Omar.
I watched over you
day and night, remember,
watched over you while you betrayed
your own wife with a Western whore.
You care for nothing but yourself.
Yes, I've made mistakes,
but believing in peace
was not one of them.
Think whatever you like.
You won't be around to find out.
Just, just a moment.
They're going to treat you
on the base hospital.
But then I want you right back here.
That's an order.
Just a moment.
You have always been true to me.
I need you now.
Hurry back.
Take good care of him.
Mrs. Hassan and her daughter
have just arrived.
Thank you, Susan.
I am so relieved you're both safe.
Thank you, Madam President.
Do you know what is happening
with my husband?
We do.
He is in the hands of the terrorists,
but we're tracking him on satellite.
We're going in now
to monitor the rescue effort.
Do you want to join us?
Then go on in the situation room,
and I'll be there in a minute.
- Thank you.
I didn't expect
to see you again, Ms. Walker,
but lately,
I have learned how few people
I can really trust.
I am glad you're here.
Thank you, Madam President.
But I think
I'd be of more use at CTU.
Of course.
Susan will arrange a car for you.
Thank you, ma'am.
Thank you.
Jack Bauer and CTU
are running the operation.
We expect the intercept to occur
in a few minutes.
Ma'am, satellite feed's
coming in from CTU.
Jack, Hassan's vehicle
just crossed 130th.
I'm at 110th Street.
Do we have an ambush point yet?
Intersection of 161st and Amsterdam.
- Who we got for the take-down team?
- A special ops unit.
We'll trigger the traffic lights
to stop the vehicle at the intersection,
then heavy gun fire
into the engine block to disable it,
snipers to take out the driver.
- That leaves you to reacquire Hassan.
- And our perimeter?
Bridges and tunnels are closed.
So Riverside Drive is shut down, too.
He can only use Amsterdam.
- What about cross streets?
- All covered from 140th Street on.
If we don't spook him,
he'll drive straight in there.
Copy that. Leave us line open in case
there are any changes.
- You got it.
- What's our timing?
Given traffic flow, Tarin should hit
the intersection in eight minutes.
I can use traffic lights
to slow him down.
I'll let Taylor know.
I'm seeing some fluctuations
in the carrier signal on the subnet.
- What's that mean?
- Maybe a problem with the trunk line.
We can't afford
to loose satellite feed.
That's how we lost the rods
in the first place.
Chloe, how's your workaround?
It's working fine.
Do I get check it?
We need you here.
I can check it
if you can watch my screen.
Thanks, Dana.
What are you doing here?
I could ask you the same.
Cole asked me to check
on the trunk line.
Except the trunk line's over here.
I can do it from here also.
I set up this system, you know.
Right. Sorry.
Then maybe you can explain
why they keep going down.
We were hit
with a massive electromagnetic pulse.
It's a miracle we could get anything up
and running again as fast as we did.
So, what are you doing now?
I'm running a diagnostic
on the trunk line.
So why were you looking at
a map of Manhattan then?
I was checking
the progress of the operation.
How I do my work
is none of your business.
Given that I've been having
to cover for you the entire night,
I think it is my business.
Fine.
You want to check up on me,
go ahead.
- You're really going to do this.
- Yeah, I am.
So, where are the diagnostics?
In the systems folder,
where they always are.
No, I mean...
where on our screen?
Thought you said
you were working on this.
I wasn't using diagnostics.
I was monitoring the voltage fluctuation
in the trunk line directly.
Really.
How?
I thought you knew everything.
Arlo, where are you?
Hastings's looking for you.
I'll be right down.
Hastings wants me on the floor.
I'll leave you to do
whatever you're doing.
Don't push it, Arlo.
CTU is following you.
Where are they?
They're all over you.
- There's an ambush set for 161st.
- I'm nearly there.
Why am I only hearing this now?
I am already doing far more
than I've been paid to do.
You need to calm down.
We knew this might happen.
Can you find me an exit?
There's one between 158th and 159th.
Parking garage.
158th, 159th.
Is everyone ready for this?
I will let Samir know,
and then it is up to him.
It's only a matter of time
before this gets raced back to me.
I need to get the hell out
of here while I still can.
Hassan is crossing
over 148th Street.
I'm activating signals up to 160th.
- You took your time.
- I'm sorry. It got complicated.
- Is the trunk line going to hold?
- I think so.
Then we keep going.
- What's our timing, Chloe?
- Intercept: four minutes.
Jack, a visual on Hassan yet?
- Negative.
- He's five blocks ahead of you.
- Roger that. Tac teams in position?
- They're good to go.
Nobody move until Hassan's vehicle
is stopped in the intersection.
What are you looking for?
- We are being followed, aren't we?
- Shut up.
That phone call, it's a warning.
- CTU is onto you.
- I'm not afraid of CTU.
- Why are you looking behind you?
- I said shut up!
Tarin, it's not too late.
Give yourself up,
and I'll speak for you.
I won't warn you again.
You're on an island here.
There's no way out.
They'll find you.
Yes, they will.
Soon enough.
Damn it. They've made us.
He's breaking left. He's breaking left.
- Chloe, where are they going?
- Checking.
What's happening?
Why did he turn?
He's in a parking garage.
It extends across the block.
- How many exits?
- Only two.
He'll have to double back.
Where's the other exit?
- Broadway.
- I'll cover that.
Cole, pull your team
back from the ambush point.
- Cover the block.
- You got it.
All teams, pull back and reposition.
Set a perimeter around the parking
garage between 158th and 159th.
I've got him.
He's turning back.
Copy that.
All units converging on your position.
He's just moving deeper.
He's got no place else to go.
You got him.
- Where did they go?
- Inside the structure.
He's running for the roof.
Move!
Where the hell is he going?
Coming straight at me!
Damn it!
Chloe, any movement
from the target vehicle?
No one could survive that.
Chloe, Hassan is not in the vehicle.
- You know where to go.
- What if he comes to?
He won't.
Not before you deliver him. Go!
I said go!
It's me.
- Have you got Hassan?
- We set up our ambush.
We were about to take him down,
when the driver
deviated from his route.
He managed to transfer Hassan
before I could get to him.
Someone inside CTU
has got to be tipping them off.
- How is that possible?
- No idea,
but I've got
the driver's cell phone.
Soon as we can set up an uplink,
I'll be able to figure out who it is.
I'm on my way to CTU.
Do you want me to talk to Chloe?
Yeah, but no one else.
We need a secure area to run the uplink.
Get back to me as soon as you're ready.
Search the parking structure.
They switched cars. Move now.