Subtitles:
Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu (V 1.00)
It's him.
Damn it.
I couldn't get off a shot.
Stand by.
We'll get him on the way out.
Manuel!
Hey, Manny!
- Put Mauricio on the phone.
- Victor?
Just put Mauricio on!
He's dead.
- What?
- Someone shot him in the head.
What is happening?
I see him.
He's leaving the building.
I'm set.
It's not him.
He can't be far.
Coming at you! Gray Sedan!
Target is out of range.
Move out.
- 911. What's your emergency?
- Yes.
I want to report
a stolen vehicle.
License plate...
SNE15C5.
Sweetheart,
we already talked about this, remember?
You're supposed
to call me "Grandpa".
You don't look like a grandpa.
Couldn't agree with you more.
The cartoon I turned on is boring.
Okay. We'll find another one.
This is the boldest
diplomatic initiative
we've seen in a generation.
It could finally lay
a foundation for real peace
throughout the entire region.
Bob, the president's
certainly betting her legacy
on the success
of the negotiations...
Grandpa!
This isn't a cartoon!
This one! I like this one!
Sorry we're late. They're redirecting
everyone around the UN.
- It's all right. We're doing fine.
- How was the zoo?
To be honest with you, we spent our time
just going back and forth
between the black and polar bears.
I forgot to mention
that she's going through a bear phase.
She certainly knows what she wants.
She reminds me of you.
That's funny.
I always tell Stephen
how much she reminds me of you.
Anyway, we'll be there
in a few minutes.
Okay. Don't worry.
We'll meet you in the lobby.
Sounds like they had fun.
They always do.
What's wrong?
We talked to him about moving
to LA the night we got here.
He said he'd think about it.
And he hasn't mentioned one word
about it since. And we leave tonight.
Maybe he has to check
with his doctors.
No, they cleared him two weeks ago.
He's finished with treatment.
I don't know.
My father has been on his own
for so long.
Maybe he doesn't know
how to live any other way.
Why don't you ask him again?
My father is not the type of person
you ask twice.
If you want, I can do it.
Here at the United Nations,
a White House spokesman
just confirmed that Presidents
Taylor and Hassan will be holding
a joint press conference.
It is widely expected
that President Hassan will announce
the dismantling of his country's
nuclear weapons program.
President Hassan has stated
that he considers these negotiations
a historic success
and a new beginning for his country
and the entire Mideast region.
I believe that
that is a reasonable compromise.
Now, Mr. President, let's move on
to the issue of verification.
Now, the language
in your latest proposal is vague.
Let me be clear.
My country agrees to abandon
the pursuit of nuclear weapons
with full International
Atomic Energy Agency safeguards.
But our terms, Mr. President,
were that the inspectors themselves
would be American,
not IAEA.
With respect, Madam President,
your side pushed the point,
but we never conceded.
With respect,
your side has refused to negotiate
the point in good faith.
Without Americans...
Surely, we're not going to let
the nationality of a few hundred men...
... verification has no teeth.
Only the United States
can be trusted, Mr. Secretary?
This is the message that you sent
and you wonder
why we don't want to negotiate.
Farhad.
Madam President,
please excuse my brother's passion.
He only wants what is best
for our country.
I understand.
But we need to resolve this issue
before we can move forward.
And ideally,
before the press conference,
which gives us less than an hour.
What would your Congress say
if my Revolutionary Guard
was stationed on your soil?
It's the same
with my National Assembly.
Even if I agreed to this,
they would not ratify it.
After all, I'm not a king.
Nor I a queen.
Too bad for both of us.
I'd like to adjourn
and discuss this issue
with our respective teams.
Of course.
You are aware he was a salesman
before entering politics.
Household appliances.
You want to bet
he sold a lot of refrigerators?
Find a way to give him
what he wants.
You heard me.
Try to make the inspections work.
This man is a once
in a lifetime leader.
And he has already suspended his support
for terrorist organizations,
and privately, he's advocating
for a two-state solution.
How much further can we expect him
to stick his neck out?
Come here.
- Did you name him yet?
- Bear.
- "Bear."
- There she is.
I heard that you
and Grandpa were
hanging out with the bears.
Then we had ice cream,
but I didn't like mine, so Grandpa
gave me his.
- That's nice.
- Here, I got her.
- Thanks for watching her.
- Of course.
Listen, I've been thinking a lot
about what we talked about.
And I've made up my mind.
I want to move back to Los Angeles.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I got a friend
who's got a private security firm.
He'd give me some consulting work.
He's also got a place I can rent.
- Dad, I don't know what to say.
- Come here.
Say nothing.
Give me a ride to the airport tonight.
- Wait, you're coming with us tonight?
- If it's okay.
He's coming with us tonight.
I've got a few more things to pack.
I don't have very much.
- I can be at your hotel in an hour.
- Perfect.
We can get back and finish packing.
It'll be all right if I fly back
to Los Angeles with you?
- I'll walk you to the car.
- Let's go.
I got her.
We're going in the car.
Get your belt done up...
- I am so glad that you're doing this.
- Me, too.
- I love you.
- Love you.
I'll see you in an hour.
Bye, sweetheart.
Good afternoon, everyone.
All right, just a few things
before we get started here.
Presidents Taylor and Hassan
will each make a statement
after they've been introduced
by the Secretary-General.
The Q&A will follow,
but I want you to keep
your questions strictly on topic.
For obvious reasons, we're all operating
under heightened security measures,
so, unless you've been dying to know
what a chokehold feels like,
keep your credentials visible
at all times.
All right?
That's all for now.
Meredith Reed, press.
It's invalid.
What?
It can't be invalid.
Can you double check?
I did, ma'am.
Your credentials have been revoked.
- Revoked by whom?
- I don't have that information.
Okay, this has to be
some sort of mistake.
You do remember me.
Please step aside, ma'am.
I just talked
to Secretary of State Kanin.
He's agreed to IAEA inspectors.
- That's good news.
- There is a condition attached.
They're insisting that the head
of the verification team be an American.
I think we can live with that.
You know where I stand.
We've already surrendered too much
in the name of peace.
Surrender is a strong word, Farhad.
And what have we surrendered really,
apart from our nuclear ambition?
Isn't that enough?
Spinning 6,000 centrifuges
is good for political maneuvering,
but it's helping to bankrupt
our country.
The truth is,
we are not the ones
being so generous.
President Taylor is lifting
economic sanctions,
and offering an aid package
worth billions of dollars.
We got everything we wanted, Farhad.
As long as it's not a trick.
I'm sorry to bother you
with something so mundane,
but I'm stuck outside.
Stuck?
My press credentials
have been revoked.
- I don't know what happened.
- I'll take care of it.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Thank you.
Will you still have time
for the interview later?
After the press conference.
I'm looking forward to it.
So am I.
Reinstate Miss Reed's clearance.
- I was only...
- Just do it.
People are starting to talk
about you and this reporter.
And saying what?
Miss Reed is a journalist,
she's profiling me for her newspaper.
- But you have feelings for her.
- I'm friendly with her.
Think whatever you like.
This woman poses no threat to me
or the peace process.
Not here maybe,
but back in our country
you'll be torn apart.
The mullahs will say
you have been corrupted by the West.
What do you say?
Have I?
Have I been corrupted by the West?
You know I don't believe that.
But you are married.
Dalia hasn't been a wife to me
for a long time.
- That's no excuse to be reckless.
- I've done nothing reckless.
I've done nothing reckless.
Just reinstate
Miss Reed's clearance now.
I'll see to it.
Victor.
What are you doing here?
How the hell did you find me?
I was always resourceful.
That's what you liked about me.
Get in here.
Take a seat.
- What happened?
- I need help.
- You need an ambulance.
- Don't call.
That's what he's waiting for.
He's listening to the channels.
Who?
Just listen to me.
I have information.
The best I can do for you
is get you an ambulance.
I don't work
for the government anymore.
This you're going to want to hear.
Why?
Why? Because you're the guy
who always does the right thing.
There's a big hit going down.
- On who?
- President Hassan at the UN.
He's getting taken out.
- When?
- Today.
Before he can sign this thing
with Taylor.
You see?
I told you you'd be interested.
How do you know this?
I'm the one that got
the hitter into the country.
- I've been setting him up.
- And then he tried to take you out.
You're the only one at CTU
I ever did business with.
I need you to call them, vouch for me,
so I can cut a deal.
- Come on.
- Keep your seat.
I swear, this is real.
Someone is trying to make sure
that this peace agreement
does not happen.
I'm not doing anything
until you give me your weapon.
- Better not be screwing with me.
- I'm not. I swear, I'm not.
Who's the hitter? His name?
- Who's the hitter?
- I don't know his name.
- He's Russian or something.
- Not good enough. Who is the hitter?
I know how to find him and stop him.
But I'm not saying another word
until I make my deal.
You're lucky I'm retired.
This is Cole Ortiz. Move Singer's team
to the northeast quadrant,
and tell him, from now on,
I want updates every quarter hour.
Get back to me with confirmations.
Hastings wants you to expand
the patrol perimeter around the UN.
Great, but I barely have enough men
to cover the perimeter now.
- I'll see if I can get NYPD.
- Dana...
My sister said she left you a couple of
messages for the bridesmaids' dresses.
I told her there was probably a problem
with your voicemail.
I got her messages.
I just haven't had a chance.
- These double shifts...
- I revised the protocols at the UN.
You might like to take a look at it.
- Yeah, I do.
- I'll call your sister back, I promise.
Thanks.
Damn it, what is the problem?
Percussive maintenance?
That's what my network apps professor
called it when I hit my computer.
- Can I help?
- I just got the revised attendee list
for the press conference. I can't get
the facial recognition done in time.
You're running each person through
individually. Do them in a batch.
Not if the data
is in different formats.
That used to be true, but here.
Like I said, there's no reason
to be shy about asking for help.
Don't worry.
You'll catch up. You're doing great.
Excuse me.
O'Brien.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Did you tell Kim about LA?
Yeah, but not now.
I need to speak to the director.
Mr. Hastings is on the phone,
and he really doesn't like
to be interrupted.
Tell him it's regarding a plot
againt President Hassan.
See if that gets his attention.
Okay, hold on.
Now, give me an overlay on the UN,
view from the west.
Now, overlay the distribution
of security teams, please.
That looks good.
Give me a comp with incident reports
and satellite imaging.
Excuse me, Mr. Hastings.
Gary, hold on for a second.
Jack Bauer's on line three.
He says he needs to talk to you.
It's about a plot against Hassan.
You might want to take it the call.
Gary, I'll call you back.
Mr. Bauer, this is Brian Hastings.
I'm with an informant
that I used to run
who's claiming he's got intel
on an assassination attempt on Hassan.
- It'll take place today.
- We've received several threats
- in regard to the peace conference.
- I can only imagine.
My informant is Victor Aruz.
I used him in the Salazar op.
You should be able to pull his file.
He's been shot in the arm...
he claims by the assassin.
Look, I don't think
you should take this lightly.
And what does Mr. Aruz want
in return for his information?
CTU protection and immunity.
- That's a lot to ask, Mr. Bauer.
- Have you pulled his file yet?
I know him and my instinct is telling me
that you need to pay attention to this.
I need more than your instinct,
Mr. Bauer.
CTU isn't the organization you knew.
Okay, fine, but understand this:
If anything happens to President Hassan,
I'll call President Taylor and tell her
I tried to provide you with this intel,
and you ignored it.
- What is taking so long for the file?
- Still searching through the archives.
Mr. Hastings,
I need your answer now.
Are you bringing Aruz in or not?
- Let me talk to him.
- I'll put you on speaker.
Go ahead.
Mr. Aruz,
I'm gonna need some other details
to corroborate your story.
The hitter took out two of my guys.
Manuel Escobar and Mauricio Tellez.
- Check with the cops.
- We will.
- Mr. Bauer, where are you?
- 1145 West 18th.
I'll send a chopper to pick you up.
The closest helipad to you is...
the 12th precinct.
That's five blocks away.
Can you get him there, Mr. Bauer?
- I'll have a team there in 20 minutes.
- Don't use official channels.
We believe the assassin
is monitoring emergency bandwidth.
Got it.
Gather comm and tactical,
tell them we've got a situation.
Let's go.
There you are.
Now that doesn't suck.
Arlo.
Come on.
Hastings called an emergency briefing.
And if he ever catches you doing that,
you'll be out of a job.
Be worth it.
I think this might be love.
Now.
This is CTU transferring control
of drones A31 and 32
to HS aerial command.
Roger that.
Offload confirmed.
We've got a situation.
Cole, scramble a chopper for a pickup.
And the new patrol parameters?
- This is a priority.
- Who am I picking up?
Someone who claims to have intel
about a threat to President Hassan.
- How good is the intel?
- According to Jack Bauer, very.
- Jack Bauer?
- He's delivering the informant.
Who is Jack Bauer?
Location's downtown,
Chloe's sending you the coordinates.
Take a small team with you.
Torres' people are free.
I'll need a second team
to secure the landing.
One team will be enough. We'll use
a drone to protect the ground operation.
Arlo, scramble a drone
alongside the chopper.
Full spectrum coverage of the landing
zone as well as the air corridor.
Done.
We're clear. Come on.
Dispatch, this is Unit 2354.
Go ahead, 2354.
Got a plate match
on a stolen vehicle.
... 03 Pontiac.
Plate: Sierra, November, Echo,
one, five, Charlie, five.
Got bullet holes
in the windshield and body.
- That's him.
- Roger that. What's your location?
Vehicle's parked on 18th,
just west of Ninth Avenue.
We'll take care of it.
Will you?
Or am I going to have to step in?
Now would be the time to tell me.
Aruz is a dead man, sir.
You have my word.
Good.
Thank you.
Excuse me, Madam President.
President Hassan accepted
our counterproposals on inspections.
That is great news.
By the end of this next session,
we may have a signed agreement.
It's an extraordinary accomplishment,
Allison.
A problem?
I was thinking about Henry.
Achieving a comprehensive peace
agreement with the Islamic Republic
was something
that he and I talked about years ago.
I wish that he were here
to share the moment.
You surprised?
Considering his behavior
during the divorce,
yes, I am surprised.
He went out of his way to hurt you,
especially in the press.
He was angry, Ethan.
I sent our daughter to prison.
You refused to cover up a murder.
Olivia was responsible
for what happened... no one else.
Still,
if the the situation had been reversed,
I might've felt
the same way as Henry.
Sorry if I'm interrupting,
but I just talked to Hastings at CTU.
What's going on, Rob?
Someone's claiming to have information
about an assassination plot on Hassan.
- How real is the threat?
- Real enough to loop you in.
This informant came to them
through Jack Bauer.
I thought Jack was out of all of this.
How did he get involved?
This informant came to him.
We'll know more once he signs
a deal, provided you authorize it.
- How secure is the venue?
- Very. I just raised the alert level.
But we need to inform Hassan,
ideally before the conference.
We can't tell Hassan.
Certainly not before
the press conference.
- Why not?
- Well, he might scuttle everything,
- out of concern for his own safety.
- Hassan's a big boy.
He's used to taking risks
or he wouldn't be here, you know that.
Plus, if Hassan finds out
we knew about this and didn't tell him,
then all the trust we've built up
goes out the window,
and then he'll pull out of talks.
Frankly, I wouldn't blame him.
I'll think about it.
Thank you both.
Madam President, I'm telling you,
holding this back from Hassan
could be disastrous.
I said I'd think about it, Rob.
Thank you.
Listen... sorry if I went after you
a little hard in there.
I was just making my point.
No need to apologize, Rob.
I recommended you to the President
because you're not afraid to speak up.
She needs that.
Still,
I know I can get carried away.
Don't worry, kid...
I ain't dead yet.
I can handle myself.
Even up against you.
Sweetheart, it's me.
We're almost done.
Are you on your way?
Something came up.
I'm gonna be a little late.
How late?
I should meet you at the airport.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
- Kim, I promise everything's fine.
Teri is so excited
you're coming back with us.
- Let me know when you're on your way.
- Okay, thanks, sweetheart.
Keep your eyes open.
The precinct's two blocks away.
Let's cut through here.
Come on.
The FAA's cleared a route
and informed all relevant agencies
that we will be in the air.
Good luck.
Aruz's file...
it was in a proprietary database.
- That's why it took so long.
- That shouldn't have thrown you.
- You've been here a month.
- Almost a month,
and I've had to relearn everything here.
Everything's changed.
And you're having trouble adapting,
I understand.
But I don't think
it's a question of your intelligence.
- Thanks.
- I think it's ambivalence.
Ambivalence?!
I know you only took this job
because your husband was downsized.
- Am I wrong?
- No!
I mean, yes.
Please, just give me a little more time
to get up to speed here.
Mr. Hastings, I need this job.
Fair enough.
But I'm all about efficiency,
so if you don't improve,
you may want to rethink working here.
Now,
I trust this has been clarifying.
Sure.
If you really wanted to be
more efficient, just say
that if I don't catch up soon,
I'll be fired.
Your flight path is a straight shot
southwest over the river,
and the 12th Precinct has confirmed
that their helipad is clear
and operational.
Full coverage of your flight, both legs,
and full-time aerial from the drone...
Why are you looking at me like that?
Like what?
I just want to make sure
nothing's wrong.
Nothing's wrong, like I said.
- Just be careful, okay?
- I will be.
You ready?
Maybe she should finally set a date.
She's getting cold feet.
How about you shut up
and just focus on your assignment?
Come on, Victor!
Look out!
Stay with me.
Victor, stay with me!
Stay with...
Damn it.
Stay with me!
We're going to need
to recompress the wound.
If successful, the agreement
could be the beginning
of a real lasting peace
in a long-troubled region.
Presidents Taylor and Hassan
are scheduled
to give their first joint
press conference
in just a few minutes,
and we'll carry that live.
In a moment, Christiane Doumany
will have a report on the history
of the many failed attempts
at a Mideast peace,
and why this accord
may be different.
It's time to go.
Tell your father
I'll be right there.
I'll wait until you're done.
He doesn't trust me to be on time.
Of course he trusts you.
When did you become
such a good liar?
You don't have
to defend your father, Kayla.
He can take care of himself.
You look beautiful, Dalia.
And you look handsome.
Let's not pretend
any more than we have to.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
It's not your fault.
My dear Kayla.
We should go.
Let her through.
Thank you.
I will tell you
the same thing that I told him.
Unless you want to destroy
everything that he's worked for,
stay away from him.
Excuse me, ma'am.
President Hassan is on his way.
You won't tell him
he's being targeted.
I'm sorry.
You risk destroying
in a single day all the...{\
- Rob,}
You've made your point.
More than once.
I don't like keeping this
from President Hassan any more than you.
Then tell him.
Mr. President.
Ladies.
- You've met my chief of staff?
- Of course.
Hello.
I haven't had the chance
to thank you
for compromising
on the verification issue.
It was the right thing to do.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to brief you
on the format
of the press conference.
The Secretary-General will introduce
you both after some brief remarks.
The conference itself shouldn't take
any longer than 25 minutes or so.
Put your hand on it.
Let's go.
We're almost there.
Don't move!
Got a call that you're having
a problem down here.
- What's up?
- My name is Jack Bauer.
I'm transporting
this man on behalf of CTU.
He's an informant
vital to national security.
Call it in.
The men that are trying to kill him
are monitoring all emergency channels.
Don't let him make that call.
Shut up and get against
the Dumpster. Now!
At least take us into the precinct.
We can verify everything there.
Get down, now!
Damn it!
I cover you.
Make a run for the door.
You ready? Go! Go!
Keep moving.
I'm out of bullets.
Chloe, it's Jack.
How far out is the helicopter?
- Two minutes. Jack, what's wrong?
- We're under attack.
Put me in touch
with whoever's in command of that unit.
Okay. It's Agent Ortiz.
He's the head of field ops.
- Is there a problem?
- Yes.
Mr. Hastings, we have a situation
with the pickup.
Keep going to the roof.
Now.
Don't stop for anything.
Keep going.
- Agent Ortiz, you're on with Bauer.
- Roger.
What's going on?
We're being pursued by two shooters.
We can't make the precinct.
We're in a building on West 21st,
three doors in from Ninth Avenue.
We're heading to your position now.
We're looking
for an alternate pickup.
Copy that.
Right there.
The roof of that parking structure
might work.
- Can you zoom in closer?
- It'll take a minute.
I'm moving the drone there now.
There's a parking structure next to you.
Roof looks clear to land.
Did you get that?
Yeah, I see it.
Mr. Bauer,
looks like you can access that roof
from the eighth floor of the building.
- How far out are you?
- 90 seconds.
Copy that.
Don't be late.
Victor, listen to me.
Tell me everything you know
about the hitter,
so I can call it in
if we don't make it.
If I don't make it,
I don't care what happens.
Get me to CTU.
You always were a son of a bitch.
Come on.
Let's go.
Stay there.
Lock down access points to the roof!
- Where are the hostiles?
- They're dead.
You need to get him out of here.
He's losing a lot of blood.
Cole Ortiz.
It's an honor to meet you.
Thanks for doing this.
Hastings wants to debrief you at CTU.
I'm not going back to CTU.
I'm done.
I got a flight to catch.
That's it?
Get down!
Ortiz, report in.
What's your status?
Jack, come in.
Jack, can you hear me?
Anyone, come in.
Come on.
Stay with me, stay with me.
Listen to me.
You don't want to die like this.
Do the right thing.
Tell me what you know.
The hitter has someone
on the inside.
Close to Hassan.
Give me a name.
Give me a name!
Who's on the inside?
Come on.
He's dead.
The brother revoked my clearance,
but I had Hassan reinstate it.
I know.
I know I'm behind schedule.
But it'll get done.