Previously on 24.
Without you,Sangala
has no leader.
These people,they work
for Dubaku,don't they?
Mr. Matobo,
we've accessed the air
intake to your safe room.
We are feeding in
ammonium dysterate gas.
If you do not open
the door,you will die.
Ule...
Get him out of there!
Get the woman,too.
- Mr. Taylor. - Sam.
I can't stay long.
They killed Roger and made
it look like a suicide.
Who are they?
I don't know who they are.
They just said that they would
kill me if I said anything.
Roger was tasked with auditing
the brokers in his department.
It's all here.
Account numbers,
trading records,everything
that he knew.
Roger was looking into
things he shouldn't have.
You killed my son.
It's Tetradyzine,sir.
It's a neuromuscular paralytic.
The situation here
is in control.
- Are you tracking Ms.
Roth?  - Yeah.
Time to get her back
to her apartment.
Ms. Roth.
Henry Taylor sent me.
Mr. Taylor's been looking into
the matter you discussed.
He believes you're
in imminent danger.
He wants me to place you
in protective custody.
Larry,it's Renee.
I've got a visual on them
loading Matobo and
his wife into a truck.
- Where the hell is SWAT? -
They're still about five minutes out.
Drop the gun.
Far as I can tell,she's alone.
Damn you,Bauer,you
son of a bitch.
Nichols wants her
out of the way
before we deliver Matobo.
Come on.
Yeah.
Turn around.
Trust me.
I'll get you through this alive.
I want three more
teams combing the site
where Matobo was abducted.
Pull them in from
regional if you have to.
We're going to
expand the search.
Coordinate with Metro Police to
set up a point-by-point grid
encompassing a ten-mile radius.
And talk with NSA.
I want to back all of this up
with synchronized
satellite sweeps.
- I'll do what I can.
- What does that mean?
Well,every time I ask for
something,they pull their
cloak-and-dagger nonsense.
I have to get approval
for every little scrap of data.
Janis,this isn't
easy for anybody.
Just,please,
make it happen.
Yes,sir.
We know that another
attack could be imminent.
The only way to stop it is
to find Almeida and Bauer
and take control
of the CIP device.
Um... for those of you
who haven't heard,
Renee Walker was abducted
by these people.
We're the only
chance she's got.
So,let's get to work.
What have you got?
Audio forensics cleaned
up the recording.
Okay.
Walker is extraneous.
Kill her before you get here.
Okay,we'll be with you soon.
Be quick about it.
Dubaku's anxious to get his
hands on the Prime Minister.
Been combing through
it,looking for a tag
that will give up
their location.
- So far,nothing. -
Is there anybody else
you can put on this?
Larry,I don't think
it's worth it.
- There's nothing here.
- All right.
Fine,help Janis
coordinate with NSA.
I'm sorry about Renee,Larry.
She was a good agent.
We don't know that
she's dead yet!
All right?
Are you sure this is it?
She's going to run out of air.
Tony said near the backhoe.
Here,here.
I got her,Chloe.
I got her.
All right,here she is.
Here she is.
She's not breathing.
Give me the adrenaline.
It's all right.
You're okay... you're okay.
Who are you?
We're working with Jack.
told us where to find you.
It's gonna be okay.
Take deep breaths.
You're gonna be okay.
We're close to the
rendezvous point.
What's your ETA?
Good.
We'll see you then.
It's all set.
Nichols is on his way
with the diamonds.
Is something
bothering you,Jack?
No,I was wondering...
why you never told Tony
how you got him out of CTU.
How did you do it?
Christopher Anderson.
Christopher Anderson
tried to kill him.
Anderson had no intention
of killing Tony.
He purposely missed the
artery when he injected him.
It was just enough
to slow his heart
to the point where you'd
think that he was dead.
My job was to...
extract and revive him and...
use him against you.
And?
By the time I stabilized him,
you had already
killed Anderson.
Mission had failed.
So,my team went dark.
Why did he just let Tony go?
Tony chose to stay with us.
He was consumed
with hatred and anger
over what the government
had done to Michelle.
Anyway... I talked to him.
More importantly,I
listened to him.
Pretty soon,we came
to realize that...
I was right.
About what?
That the rules had changed.
And there was nothing
such as honor left.
That we would have to
take care of each other.
Like brothers.
Mr. Emerson.
Yeah?
We're almost there.
How is the deal gonna go down?
Don't worry,Jack.
You're about to find out.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Tony,Jack.
Go help Litvak with the door.
Go get the Matobos.
Yeah.
You better tell me what
the hell's going on.
Drop the gun,David.
You know,I just couldn't
figure out your play,
so I tried to give you some
time so you'd come clean,
'cause we are
like brothers,right,Tony?
Put the gun down,David.
You actually think
that I would let you
steal those diamonds from me?
It's not about the diamonds.
It's about killing
innocent people.
I can't let you finish this.
Take a shot.
Put down the weapon
or I will kill him.
Tony,take a shot!
- Shut up,Jack! -
Put it down,Tony,
- or he's dead. -
David,I don't want to kill you,
- but I will. - Damn it,Tony,
drop the...
You okay?
Yeah.
David.
Okay,you say that
Bauer and Almeida
are working undercover,but
CTU has been shut down,
so,I mean,if you're
telling the truth,
who's running this operation?
We are.
We're not working
with any agency.
We believe there's been
widespread infiltration...
... of the government...
... by Dubaku and
the Juma regime.
Okay.
I need to contact my boss.
- He needs to know that I'm okay.
- You can't do that.
Why not?
Dubaku has informants
in the FBI.
If they find out you're alive,
they'll know Jack is
working against them.
You don't know
who you can trust.
I can trust Agent Moss.
You're not listening to me.
You cannot contact the FBI.
You will jeopardize
this operation,
and I won't let you do that.
Well,I don't work for
you,I work for Larry.
Now give me a phone.
Sit still,please.
We're nearing the endgame.
Dubaku is the key...
... to finding out who
in the government...
... has been corrupted.
Luckily,we have
something he wants.
Matobo.
He's our best chance
to locate Dubaku,
reacquire the CIP module
and get to the bottom of
the government corruption.
Until all that happens,you
have to stay dead.
Yeah.
Did you find Agent Walker?
Yeah,we got her,Jack.
She's fine. Where are you?
Northwoods Airfield.
Litvak is dead.
Emerson's been wounded.
Nichols is en route.
I need you to get over here now.
Have you talked to Matobo?
- Not yet. -
He needs to agree to this,Jack.
We can't do it without him.
I'll get him to agree.
Just get over here.
It's all right.
What the hell is going on?
Mr. Matobo,I'm not
going to hurt you...
... or your wife.
I know how scared you are...
... and I know what
you've been through,
but we are here to help you.
What in God's name
are you talking about?
- You kidnapped us. -
We had to to gain Dubaku's trust.
That's the man we're after.
We're trying to stop him.
I want to call my people.
I can't let you do that,not
until you hear me out.
Sir,we have a plan
to stop Dubaku,
but we can't do it
without your help.
We don't have much time.
Please.
Come with me.
Mr. Dubaku.
I'm heading...
... to the meeting place.
They're bringing Matobo now.
And his wife?
Both of them.
Once you have Matobo,you
know what to do.
Emerson's team is
now a loose end.
Tie it off.
Are you sure about this?
We may need their
services again.
I would rather
keep my diamonds,
and Almeida has proved
to be a liability.
So.
Any response from
the White House?
Not the one we wanted.
American forces are
still in position.
President Taylor must
know we have Matobo.
She can't attack
Sangala without him.
The country will collapse.
Taylor may be holding
out hope that she can
somehow retrieve Matobo.
Or she doesn't believe
we are willing to
carry out our threats.
She will only respond when
there are dead Americans.
I'll call you when
I have Matobo.
These gentlemen are
at your command.
There are still 1,300
planes in the air.
Which region do
you want targeted?
Washington DC.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
I understand,Bob.
All right,thanks.
That was Bob Cornell at NSA.
They've detected
another firewall breach.
There's been another attack?
Not yet,but they believe the
CIP device is being utilized.
We have to assume Dubaku is
initiating another attack.
It's safe to say this won't
be another warning shot.
This time Dubaku's gonna
make sure that people die.
I want to speak personally
with all first responders
across the country.
They need to know to
brace for the worst
and that they have
our full support.
Instead of preparing for it,
maybe we should be trying
to preempt this
attack,Madam President.
The deadline Dubaku gave us
for withdrawing our troops
from Sangala has passed,
but if we made some
kind of gesture...
began an immediate pullback,
it might keep Dubaku
from pulling the trigger.
We've discussed this,Ethan.
It's not an option.
I won't be dictated
to by this madman.
Madam President,we can't
invade Sangala without Matobo,
and there's very little chance
of him being recovered.
Why are we risking
American lives?
I've told you my reasons.
Withdraw our forces
before it's too late.
You asked me to be your advisor
because you trust my opinion.
Well,I'm giving it to you now.
We're out of options.
We're not,Ethan.
The NSA is
attempting to localize
what part of the infrastructure
is being targeted,
and the FBI is still trying
to track down the CIP device.
I'll keep an open channel
with both agencies.
I'll keep you apprised.
Good.
Let me see it.
Let me see it!
This wasn't about
the diamonds,David.
You crossed a line I
wasn't willing to cross.
I'm sorry.
You're looking
for forgiveness...
Go to hell.
You...
live with it.
You're asking us
to risk our lives
to be delivered into Dubaku's
hands,based on nothing
but what you have told us.
Everything I have told
you is the truth.
Dubaku is in this country,and
we need to find him.
You have as much at stake
as we do.
He's attacked both
our countries.
Listen to him,Ule.
You told me yourself
President Taylor
will not commit
forces to Sangala
until these attacks
are stopped.
But how can we trust this man?
Because he has no
reason to lie.
I will do what you
ask,but I will go alone.
Dubaku wants you and your wife.
- That's the deal. - No.
I will not put my wife in
the hands of that monster.
I will be honest with you,sir.
He wants your wife as leverage.
If I don't deliver
both of you,he will back out.
Leverage.
You mean he wants
to torture her
to make me tell him what I
know about the resistance
- in Sangala? - Yes,sir.
And we won't let that happen.
We'll be following you.
Still,you can't promise me
that she won't be
harmed,can you?
Can you?
I won't do it.
May I speak with my husband?
Of course,Ma'am.
I want to do this,Ule.
- What? - I am ashamed
that I opened the door
to the safe room.
I want to do what is
right for our country.
Absolutely not.
You can't stop me,Ule.
Sangala
is my country,too.
I have been by your side
for 22 years.
I am not going to leave it now.
Mr. Bauer.
We will do this together.
Thank you.
You are both very brave.
We'll need to go soon.
Excuse me for one moment.
Tony.
The Matobos are
gonna work with us.
We've got to go.
Tony.
Let's get the bodies
out of sight.
Ok.
We're locked onto the FAA node.
Begin rerouting the targets.
RSA 471,turn right,
heading 274.
Descend and maintain
flight level
270.
Call the White House.
The latest report from the NSA.
I can summarize it
- for you. - Go ahead.
They've had no luck
in localizing the
firewall breach.
Dubaku's attack
could hit anywhere.
What about the FBI?
They've dedicated
every available agent
to the manhunt for Matobo.
They're no closer
to finding him.
Uh,excuse me.
We're at a dead
end,Madam President.
You need to order the pullback,
and you need to order it now.
Can it be traced?
Okay.
Hold on.
- Madam President.
- What is it,Tim?
I've just been forwarded
a scrambled call.
It's from Colonel Dubaku.
He's demanding to
speak with you.
I'll take it.
This is
President Taylor.
Madam President...
I'm disappointed
that you have not taken
my demands seriously.
Your forces are still in
position near my country.
Colonel Dubaku,I
assure you we've had
very serious discussions
regarding your demands.
The time for
discussions is over.
The deadline for your forces
to begin their
withdrawal has passed.
Go to the window.
Look to the
southwest,Madam President.
What?
See what you have done.
Colonel Dubaku,if
you're endangering
one American life...
Oh,my God.
Go,Madam President.
You son of a bitch.
Comply with my demands
within the hour,
or 10,000 more
Americans will die.
Is the Cabinet still assembled?
Yes,Madam President.
It was Flight 131
out of Chicago.
240 passengers,ten
crew members.
They collided with
a small commuter jet
carrying 21 people.
There's also a high probability
of casualties on the ground.
The aircraft went down in
a residential neighborhood
near Edgeborough.
Thank you.
We've also just gotten word
that Congressman Brighten
and his wife
may have been on 131.
We're waiting for confirmation.
How many planes are
still in the air?
Over 1,300.
Madam President,
this is a catastrophic
loss of American lives,
and it's only
going to get worse.
We have to withdraw our forces
before the next deadline.
I'm forced to agree,
Madam President.
Go ahead,Tim.
I want to hear what you think.
We're simply not prepared
to contend with the scope
of damage these
people can inflict.
The tragedy we've
just witnessed
is nothing compared
to what could happen if
they begin targeting
power grids,nuclear facilities.
We're talking deaths in
the hundreds of thousands.
All in support of a policy
that cannot possibly
succeed without Matobo.
He's the only man who
can stabilize Sangala.
Without him,
the entire operation
is pointless.
There's still a chance
that Prime Minister
Matobo will be recovered.
And while that chance
exists,I'm not giving in.
Admiral Smith,your strike force
will remain in position and
at full battle readiness.
Yes,Madam President.
Madam President,you're
guaranteeing
another attack on our country.
We will not be blackmailed,Joe,and
we will not be held hostage.
This country does not
negotiate with terrorists.
Tell that to the
families of the dead!
Do you have any idea what
the public reaction will be
when word gets out that
these are acts of terrorism?
Brought about by your
reckless foreign policy?
I can guarantee there will be
a call for your impeachment...
That's enough,Joe.
I will not stand by
and let this happen.
Then you can turn in
your resignation,Joe,
because I'm not
changing my mind.
Now sit down or leave.
I'm sorry,Madam President.
You people think about
what you're doing here...
about the cost you're
willing to pay.
Gentlemen,
ladies...
I know that there
are many of you here
who agree with
Secretary Stevens.
If I can't alleviate
your doubts,
I can at least help
you to understand
my reasoning.
When I took the oath of
office,I swore to myself,
and to the American people,that
this country would continue
to be a force for
good in this world.
We're a nation
founded on ideals,
and those ideals are
being challenged today.
Now how we respond will not only
define this administration,
but an entire generation.
And not just
Americans,but Sangalans,
and anyone else who looks to
us for guidance and strength.
I won't fail them...
and neither will you.
We're in for some
tough times ahead.
Let's make sure we're ready.
Thank you,everyone.
Hey,Jack.
They're over there.
I want you to put a wire
on Mr.
Matobo as fast as you can. Go.
You okay?
What do you think,Jack?
You shot me and
buried me alive.
If we hadn't,Emerson
would have killed you.
I'm sorry we had to
keep you in the dark,
- but we didn't have a choice.
- Yes,you did.
You could have trusted me.
If I had told you
everything back at the FBI,
would you have believed me?
Have a seat,please,sir.
What's that?
It's a transmitter.
I'll be affixing it
to one of your teeth.
We'll know exactly where
you are at all times.
You won't be alone.
Are you with the FBI?
No,I'm a stay-at-home mom.
Open your mouth,please.
Wider.
Good.
Chloe accessed the FBI server.
Dubaku brought down two planes
just outside the capital.
Over 270 people
were killed.
He's threatened to
kill 10,000 more.
We have less than
an hour to stop it.
How long before
Nichols gets here?
Ten minutes.
- Here's your com. - Thanks.
You all right?
Yeah,just a little dizzy.
You should take a seat.
I'm fine.
Hey,come on. Take a seat.
So it's really true?
Yeah.
I've devoted my
life to the Bureau
and you just expect me to
believe that it's corrupted...
that the entire government's
been corrupted?
Not all of them.
But until we find out who,
we can't trust anyone.
And the four of you really
think you can stop this?
We have to.
It's as simple as that.
Ethan...
Can we...?
The president
is completely alone on this,
and she's going to get a
lot of Americans killed.
You've got to find a way to
talk some sense into her.
We're both on the
same side here,Tim.
And I'm going to need your help
if we're going to
change her mind.
How do you propose we do that?
There is someone
she'll listen to.
Maybe we can convince
him to help us.
Go ahead.
I just dropped her off.
She's on her way up.
Okay,stay in the
car and keep watch.
I'll call you when it's done.
Mr. Taylor,how did
you get in here?
Um... the agent you sent
just brought me by to get
a few of my things for...
Mr. Taylor,are you all right?
Mr. Taylor,are you okay?
Mr. Taylor,unless you tell me
what's wrong,I
don't know what...
Help me. Please.
Yes,Mr. Kanin.
Agent Gedge,I'm looking
for Henry Taylor.
He's not answering his phone.
Is he with you?
You can't talk with
him right now,sir.
Why not? Where is he?
Well,he's meeting
with Samantha Roth
in her apartment,sir.
For what possible
reason?
I don't know,sir.
He didn't tell me.
Why aren't you with him?
Mr. Taylor insisted
on meeting with her alone,sir.
I'm in the car.
I'm just outside the building.
I don't give a damn
what he insisted.
We went through this,Agent Gedge.
You were
supposed to keep
him away from her.
What the hell were
you thinking?
I'm sorry,sir.
I'm not interested
in your apology.
Just pull him out of there
and have him phone me
as soon as possible.
Don't try to speak,sir.
There is nothing enough to say.
We will wait here.
All right.
They're coming.
- One car from the service road.
- How many people?
I can't tell.
The windows are tinted.
Copy that.
How are you doing,Tony?
All right.
I was glad to hear
you're still with us.
Where's Emerson?
You're not going to be
dealing with him today.
What do you mean?
He's dead.
So's Litvak and Bauer.
I got them in a back room.
You want to say hi?
You better start telling me
what the hell is going on.
I decided I'd rather
not split the cut.
I don't understand.
I thought you and
Emerson were friends
Yeah,that was before he left
me to rot with the FBI.
You want Matobo or not?
Where is he?
Close.
I want to see him,and his wife.
Diamonds.
Matobo.
He's in the back of the truck.
Keep your tracks clean.
We might call on you again.
Okay,then.
Let's put that behind us.
You got what you want.
Now,get the hell out of here.
Now!
Clear.
- Chloe. - Jack,I've got him.
Get everyone ready to move out.
Gedge...
Gedge.
Don't do this.
Please...
The White House still
has not complied.
American forces are
still in position.
I think this president
is not just stubborn;
she's insane.
What do you intend to do?
Exactly what we promised.
We're ready,sir.
I'll see you in a moment.
Where is the target located?
Kidron,Ohio.
Population?
30,000.
The processing
facility is located
two miles west of
the town center.
Casualties will be
high,about 18,000.
Begin.