Jack.
Put down your weapon. Now!
What the hell's going on?
Where's Ryan Burnett? What?
Senator Mayer's chief of staff--
where is he?
Tony double-backed to
one of his contacts
who gave him information
of a second attack.
It's gonna take place here in
Washington within the hour.
Juma's operatives
are carrying it out.
Burnett's been supporting
them all along.
He knows where the attack's
gonna take place, so you can
either tell me where he is,
or I will find him myself.
Mr. Burnett,
you are a traitor and a terrorist.
I am not.
I love my country.
Mr. Bauer,
this is President Taylor.
Where's the target?!
What you're doing is against the law,
Mr. Bauer.
I am ordering you
to stand down.
Where's...?
Take Mr. Bauer away.
He's under arrest.
You should have come to me.
You should have
presented your case.
And would it really have
made a difference, ma'am?
Colonel Dubaku is dead.
Laurent must never know about this,
or about his father's cowardice.
There is no sign of my father.
Let me take his place
on the assault team.
Spoken like a true Dubaku.
Laurent, it is
time for us to go.
This is it, Larry, no question.
They're moving out.
Any idea what the
next target is?
No.
From our location, it is approximately
100 meters to the entrance.
Let's move.
That's it.
I need to see her right now.
Ms. Taylor, the president will
see you as soon as she's able.
Well, you tell her her
daughter is done waiting.
I'm going to the hospital
to be with my father.
I think it would be a good idea to talk
to your mother before you do that.
The president's orders are that
you remain in the White House.
So if I try to leave, you will
actually physically restrain me?
Oh, that would never happen,
Ms. Taylor,
because I know you have too much
respect for your mother and her office
to ever let things
get that far.
Well done, Agent.
You've been at this a while.
Five administrations, ma'am.
Olivia, your mother asked me to
fill you in on what's happening.
Well, with all due respect, Ethan,
you're the last person she should
be sending.
There's about to be another
terrorist attack on this city.
That's why she wants
you to remain here.
Are we talking about
more planes going down?
We don't know.
But whatever's going to
happen will happen soon.
I'm heading to the Pentagon.
On top of all of this,
there's also the invasion to deal with.
So, bear in mind, your mother's
under tremendous pressure right now.
It's only a matter of time
before the media picks up
on the heightened
security measures.
I want to issue a statement
before that happens.
Play down the actual likelihood of an
attack, talk about the security measures
as being due diligence,
rather than...
No, Meredith.
The public deserves the truth.
We stress caution and calm,
but we acknowledge we have intel
about another terrorist action.
Yes, ma'am. Angela and I will have
something for you as soon as possible.
Madam President,
Larry Moss is calling in.
He says he's got a
lead on the attack.
Put him through.
Agent Moss,
you're on with the president.
Madam President, we've discovered
what we believe was a staging area
being used by terrorists on
the south shore of the Potomac,
near the ITP rail
and shipyards.
Madam President, we've identified
one of the men as General Juma.
What?!
Juma's in DC?
Yes, ma'am,
and we know that there are at least
a dozen other men involved in the
attack, and they are armed for a
small war.
Have you found evidence that tells
us where the target might be?
No, ma'am,
but we have search teams
out looking for the men,
and we're hoping that
Agent Walker has
more information.
She's the one who I.D.'d Juma, but,
uh, we've lost contact with her.
Lost contact?
Yes, Madam President, but we have every
reason to hope that she's still alive
and in pursuit of
the terrorists.
If she's out there,
ma'am, we'll find her.
Hold it right there!
I'm Agent Renee Walker, FBI.
Agent Walker, we just got an alert
on you. You need to call Larry Moss
at FBI right now.
Tell him there's gonna be
a terrorist attack
on the White House.
Yes, ma'am. I'll call it in right away.
This is Thompson...
Ranger Thompson,
please respond and report your location.
Ranger Thompson...
Bill.
The attorney general wants
you transferred to his custody
so he can file
criminal charges.
Have we learned anything
else about the attack?
I reached Tony.
He couldn't get any more
information from his guy.
According to the FBI,
Renee Walker followed a lead on her own
to an abandoned
warehouse on the Potomac.
Got a visual on a heavily-armed
commando unit led by Juma himself.
But she went missing right
after she called it in.
What do you mean, missing?
We're not sure.
The FBI's searching the area, but
there's no sign of her, or any evidence
telling us what the
target might be.
Burnett knows.
The president offered
him an immunity deal.
He turned it down,
hasn't said a word since.
Damn it, Bill,
he was talking when they stopped me.
Put me in a room with
him for five minutes,
and we can stop this
thing from happening.
Jack, even if I was
willing to release you,
he's being transported
to Kennedy Memorial.
You couldn't get access to him.
Fine. Then you do it.
You can get access.
I'm not trained in
coercive techniques.
This is not a maybe.
Ryan Burnett is an accessory
to a terrorist attack.
If you don't do this,
people will die.
Look, I'm not arguing about
what needs to be done.
But I can't do it.
I don't do that. It's not me.
That's not good enough. Jack!
Damn it, Bill.
That's not good enough.
You were the one who told me,
people who stand by--
they might as well help
them plant the bomb.
You can do this.
Bill, you have
to do this.
I can't, Jack.
I'm sorry.
Bill?
I can't.
This is it, General.
We're on the other
side of the conduit.
Are you in position?
Yes, General.
I'll be ready for you.
What was that?
I thought I heard
you say something.
Just, uh, talking to myself.
Yeah. Hey, I tell you we're
having people over on Saturday?
Nothing fancy.
We're bringing in Chinese.
You think you're gonna
make it this time?
Oh. Chinese.
But I was looking forward
to Sheila's cooking.
All clear, General.
Excellent.
We'll have access
in ten seconds.
Once we're in, we'll have two minutes
until the proximity alarms come back up.
Five, four, three,
two, one...
Move!
I've accessed the Secret
Service tracking grid.
Where is she?
Right here in the Oval Office.
Let's go.
Clear.
We will meet resistance,
which we must counter quickly.
Silently.
We have nine minutes until the
next Secret Service roll call.
We must find the
president by then.
Yeah, I'll let you know,
as soon as it's ready for release.
Let go of the phone.
Huh.
Five minutes until
roll call, General.
Juma had your father killed.
What?
Listen to me,
I know that Dubaku is your father.
Juma's been lying to you.
Your father is dead.
My father is alive!
Juma had to make sure that
your father didn't talk.
So he sent a man named
Udo to murder him.
No. No, I...
I don't believe you.
Look, I was there
when Udo did it.
That's how I found you.
By following him back
to the rail car.
General Juma betrayed you.
You are lying. You are lying!
Renee!
I know the target.
Reissued warrants and
order for transport, sir.
Sorry, Jack.
This way, Mr. Bauer.
Bill Buchanan.
It's Larry Moss.
Renee Walker says the
target is the White House.
How good is her intel?
Firsthand. She says they're
getting in via subterranean access.
I'll initiate a lockdown.
You alert CIRG.
This is Bill Buchanan.
I have confirmation the White House
is a target of a terrorist attack.
Condition red. Repeat:
Condition red. Secure the president.
Get to your posts.
Jack, I could use your help.
I need to know you'll
do exactly as I say.
You have my word.
Where's the president now?
Oval Office.
What's the meaning of this?
You need to come with us.
The White House is
under attack. What?!
Madam President, we need to go.
Ma'am, we need to go right now.
Ms. Taylor.
I've got the
president's daughter.
We're on our way
to the lockdown.
Men are down.
There's no safe path out.
We need to secure her in
the first floor lockdown.
Bill, we're clear.
What the hell is he doing here?
He's with me.
Madam President, right now,
you need all the help you can get.
How is this happening?
Where's my daughter?
Aaron Pierce is taking her to lockdown
as we speak, but we need to move.
Agents in zones five,
seven and nine, please respond.
Five, seven and nine, respond.
I can't reach anyone
in the quadrant.
Juma's men are headed
straight for us.
They know where she is.
They're tracking her, Bill.
Madam President,
let me see your tracker.
Bill, what's the most direct route
to the lockdown? From the east.
I'll head west with the
tracker and draw them away.
You go with Jack.
Agent Bauer.
This is your house.
I'll follow.
We're moving the
president to lockdown.
Agent Hovis, we've got agents
down in multiple quadrants.
We need reinforcements, sir.
Copy that.
We're on our way to the lockdown now.
Let's go.
General.
The president has
left the Oval Office.
She's heading down
the west corridor.
Udo, take your team that way.
We'll trap her in between us.
We're getting close to
the president, sir.
Up ahead, around this corner.
The president's tracker, sir.
They know we're here.
They're moving the
president to the lockdown.
Find her.
Take him. We need hostages.
Start gathering 'em up.
Let's move.
We've engaged hostiles on
the way to the lockdown.
We do not have a visual
on the president.
We're still two minutes away.
Get up!
Get up! Get up! Get up!
Move it! Come on!
Come on, move it! Come on!
Aaron, it's Jack. I'm with the
president, approaching lockdown. Where
are you?
We're still upstairs, Jack.
Move! Move! WOMAN: Please...
Hostiles are in
control of the area.
Looking for a way past
them to the lockdown.
Copy that.
Juma's men are closing on our position.
You're going to have about
30 seconds to get here
before I have to seal this door.
PIERCE: Understood.
You will not close this door until my
daughter gets here. Madam President,
right now,
your life is the priority,
whether you like it or not.
Please, step inside.
Madam President,
are you all right?
Aaron, it's Jack.
We're sealed off
in the lockdown.
We came under attack.
We didn't have a choice.
We couldn't have made
it anyway, Jack.
We'll try to find a way
out of the building.
Copy that, Aaron...
Jack.
Jack, do you read me?
Aaron, it's Jack. Do you copy?
Damn it.
Juma's cut off our communication.
I need to know that
my daughter's safe.
Madam President,
I can't answer that yet.
Abo.
General Juma,
they brought in reinforcements.
I don't know how much longer we can
hold them off from your position.
Stand by.
Ngozi?
Agents are moving in from all
directions; we will be
heavily outnumbered.
Does Secret Service know the
president is secured in the lockdown?
The only ones who saw are dead.
Put me on to their
communications channel.
Go ahead, sir.
This is General Juma.
I have the president.
Evacuate immediately,
or she will die.
I need proof you have the president
before I can give that order.
Let us speak to her.
Who is this?
Special Agent Hovis.
Agent Hovis,
move your men out of the building
and beyond the fence line,
or I will kill the president.
And her death will
be on your head.
Agent Hovis?
We're pulling back.
All agents,
fall back immediately!
I repeat: All agents fall back.
General, Secret
Service is retreating.
They are retreating, General.
All of them?
Yes, sir.
Gather all the hostages
and bring them here.
Lock down the exits. Move. Sir.
Confirming Secret Service
retreat in western quadrant.
Copy, General.
The only reason Secret
Service would retreat
is if they thought Juma
had the president.
But that man, Bauer,
said he g t my mother into the lockdown.
Juma's bluffing them.
We need to get out of here
and let our people know that
as soon as possible so they
can retake the building.
Get out of here? How?
They're everywhere.
Move it! Shh!
Keep your hands on your head--
move it!
Go! Move it!
Go! Move!
Move it! Move!
Move it!
Come on, move!
Move it! Move your feet.
Get out here.
Move it. Move it.
Right here. Keep going.
Come on. Move it!
Sit down! Sit down!
Everyone down!
Get down. Down now!
Get down! Turn around.
Turn around.
Can you open it?
Yes.
Assuming the specifications
Hodges gave us are correct.
How long?
15 minutes.
We confronted them in one of
the first floor corridors.
At that point,
Juma ordered us to retreat,
threatening to kill the
president if we didn't comply.
But he never gave a
visual confirmation
he was holding the president?
No, he didn't, but I felt,
at that point,
I had no choice but to pull back.
His men were killing
civilians and agents.
Any idea how many people
are still trapped inside?
Cross-checking the evacuees
with the White House manifest.
So far, it looks like 53.
Any Secret Service?
HOVIS: As far as I know,
we have no agents left
in there still alive.
They'll be prepared to storm the
building as soon as the order is given.
Yeah, well, at this point, that order
has to be given by the vice president.
What's his status?
Secret Service has him en
route to a secure location.
All right,
let me know as soon as he's locked down.
And Hovis, I need an infrared
SAT-SCAN of the building.
Highest resolution possible.
Got it.
You didn't tell me that Jack
was in the White House.
He was under arrest.
Being held under guard when
the attack took place.
Under arrest for what?
He found out an aide to Senator Mayer
named Burnett was part of
the conspiracy.
He was caught torturing him...
in the White House.
Almost killed the man
before he was stopped.
Renee, the president is our priority,
not Jack Bauer.
Are we clear on that? Clear.
Are you sure? Yes.
They're bringing
in more hostages.
Get down! Now!
Get in here! Sit!
No talking.
I don't see Olivia.
Madam President,
that's good news.
I know Aaron Pierce.
He will do everything in his power to
make sure that your daughter is safe.
This is the White House,
for God's sake.
How is it possible that they were able
to get around our security protocols?
There's only one explanation.
They had help on the inside.
From whom?
Oh, this is insane.
Juma must realize that there's no
way for him to get out of this alive.
I'm afraid he does.
This is his endgame.
He came here to make a statement,
and he's willing to die for it.
As soon as the rescue teams realize
that you're secure, they'll move in.
It's only a matter of time.
What's he doing?
Is that some kind
of explosive? No.
Mr. Bauer?
Oh, my God.
They've got the access codes.
I need to get into that panel.
Is there something I can do?
Yeah, give me that
toolbox over there.
Put it on the table.
Damn it.
Madam President,
plug the cord into the wall, please.
Now.
Okay.
General.
What's wrong?
It just went dead.
Somehow, they must have disabled
the circuitry from inside.
Then, we'll use C4 to
blow open the door.
We'll have to drill sinkholes
into each of the 11 locking rods.
It will take too long.
Depending on how the steel is hardened,
C4 might not even work.
Then we'll find another way.
There can be no room for doubt.
We have the president trapped.
We open up that door,
we become a part of history.
We will find
another way.
Yes.
Um...
just a moment.
Call came in on the
dedicated uplink.
I heard it.
It's him, sir.
Put him on speaker.
General, didn't expect to be
hearing from you directly.
What is it I can do for you?
We have a problem.
The president is
secured in the lockdown.
Well, we prepared you
for that possibility.
We gave you the specs for
the locking mechanism.
They shorted the lock
out from the inside.
I need you to find
me another way in.
General, I've given you
everything I have to give.
My part in this thing is over.
Are you forgetting that you
don't have the shipment yet?
Now, General,
I expect you to be an honorable man.
We made a deal.
We held up our end
of the bargain.
We got you in the White House.
I expect you to hold up yours.
I don't care about
your expectations.
You help me, or I will destroy that
shipment before it ever arrives to you.
Hang on.
Well...
Seaton, what do you think?
Can he do what he says?
The shipment's not due in the
port for another two hours.
His men will have plenty of time
to destroy it, render it useless.
General?
Tell me-- who else is in the
lockdown with the president?
My men saw her enter
with another man.
Well, I'm looking at the
White House manifest,
and according to this, Olivia Taylor
is presently in the building with you.
The president's daughter?
Are you sure?
Their system logs everyone
in and out electronically.
If it says that she's in there,
she's in there.
Now, you find Olivia Taylor, and you'll
get the president to open that door.
Your shipment will
arrive as planned.
Thank you.
There, you see-- stress.
Stress...
is the fertilizer
of creativity.
Let's play some darts.
The president's daughter is
somewhere in the White House.
Let's find her.
Raise your heads.
Show me your faces.
What do you think's going on?
I asked you a question,
Mr. Buchanan.
You think I made the
wrong call with Bauer.
You think that if I'd signed off
on him torturing Ryan Burnett,
all of this could
have been avoided?
You don't know what
I'm thinking, Senator.
She's not here.
Go ahead and find her
and bring her to me.
What happened?
What did you see?
The door's guarded.
Well, there's got to
be another way out.
There are only three exits to this wing,
and they're all covered.
The windows are
sealed and hardened.
Unbreakable. We have
to let them know
the terrorists are bluffing;
that they don't have my mother.
Our only option is
to get a signal out.
We can do it from the windows of
the residence. Okay, okay, good.
You'll be safer if I leave
you in a secure area.
I'll get the signal out
and come back for you.
I'm not gonna sit and hide in
some damn vent, Agent Pierce.
Ma'am, it is a long way, and we're
probably gonna encounter more of
Juma's men.
It's too dangerous.
I don't care.
I'm going with you,
and don't try to argue.
We don't have the time.
Okay.
Stay behind me.
Agent Moss,
SAT-SCAN's all set up here.
We can see the cluster of hostages,
but not the individual bodies.
That the best they can do?
They can't boost the resolution on this?
No, sir.
The White House is one of the most
heavily shielded buildings in the world.
Yeah, got it.
The vice president's ready.
They're initiating
communication. Thanks.
Yeah.
Give us the room.
You're on with the
Vice President.
Mr. Vice President, I'm Special Agent
Moss, head of the FBI's DC branch.
This is Agent Walker.
I've been briefed on
the general situation.
What are the latest
facts on the ground?
There's nothing further from General
Juma, but an infrared scan of
the building
shows he's holding the hostages in a
hallway outside the Roosevelt Room.
Now this is very possibly
good news for the president.
Explain.
The area's not one of the more
defensible places in the building.
Tactically, it makes no sense for
Juma to have chosen it as a base.
However, the area is adjacent
to the ground floor lockdown,
which we know the
president was en route to.
So, you think the president
made it into the lockdown?
That's our best explanation
for him being there.
We're therefore are
asking you to authorize
the rescue operation before Juma
manages to penetrate the lockdown.
Do you have any other evidence
that supports your theory
that the president
is in the lockdown?
There's the fact that he
couldn't produce the president
when we asked him to
prove that he had her.
Couldn't or wouldn't?
You can't be certain which one it is,
can you?
Certainty's not possible
in this case, sir.
We're giving you our best estimation
and we urge you to allow us to launch.
What if you're wrong?
What if Juma does
have the president?
He will kill her as soon as he
realizes what you're doing.
Inaction has its own risks,
too, sir.
The more time Juma has to
reinforce his position,
the more difficult it'll be to take
the building and to save lives.
I understand.
But my priority must be
the president's life.
Prudence dictates that I hold off
on authorizing the rescue operation
until we can be more
certain of her status.
Mr. Vice President, terrorists
are in control of the White House.
I would ask you to
consider if prudence
is the appropriate response
in this situation.
I thank you for your thoughts,
Agent Walker.
Until you can provide me with more
intel on what's going on in there,
you are instructed to refrain
from launching any action.
Keep me apprised of any
further developments.
All he's interested in
is covering his own ass.
He's the Vice President.
Right now,
he's calling the shots.
It was the right call, sir.
You can't order an operation that
results in the president's death
and your own
elevation to the job.
It would be
politically untenable.
Never let anyone hear you
talking like that, Derek.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
Oh, God...
Oh, my God, Aaron!
They would've
heard those shots,
so you're going to need to
get the signal out before they
get back. There's a security kit
behind that door in the bureau.
It's got first aid
and a flashlight.
You'll flash Morse
Code out the window.
Reach in my jacket.
I got a pen.
Here.
Give it to me.
Give me your hand.
This is called "Code Green." A dot is
a short blink; a dash is a long one.
"Code Green" will
signal them to move in.
Go!
Okay... okay...
Okay...
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
General Juma,
I have the president's daughter.
Bring him.
Sources have confirmed that the
siege inside the White House
began approximately
40 minutes ago.
We do not yet have confirmation on
the number of hostages being held,
or if the president
is among them.
Behind me, you can see dozens of
tactical assault units standing by.
Government analysts tell us the
order to launch any operation
in these circumstances would
rest with the vice president.
General, I discovered fiber-optic
cameras embedded in the chandelier.
Sit!
Get me a chair.
Yes, General.
He spotted the cameras.
Give me a secure channel.
Go ahead, sir.
President Taylor,
I see now that you've been watching us.
Good.
There is something I
think you should see.
God, no.
If you don't open the door, I'm
going to cut out your daughter's eyes
one by one.
And then I'm going to
cut out her tongue...
...and then her head.
Mom, don't listen!
I know what you're thinking.
How do you know if you open
the door that I won't kill her?
All you need to know is that
I most certainly will kill her
if you don't.
Open the door.
Madam President, I can't!
No. Open the door.
Open the door! I can't!
That is my daughter out there.
Do you understand?
I've already lost my son.
Have you any idea what
it's like to lose a child?
 Madam President, I am genuinely
sorry, but I cannot let them take you.
There is nothing you
can do for her now.
Do you have children, Jack?
I have a daughter.
Could you do what
you're asking me to do?
Just stand by and
watch her butchered?
No, ma'am.
But I am not the President
of the United States.
Well, I am
the president.
And I am ordering you
to open that door.
You're running out of time.
Mom...
Perhaps this will make your
mother decide more quickly.
Mom, you shouldn't have...
I wouldn't let them
hurt you, darling.
Damn it, Bauer.
What have you done?!
All right, General,
you've got me now.
There's no reason to
hold anyone else.
Let them go.
You...
don't give orders to me.
Get the camera ready
for her statement.
What statement?
The last one you'll ever give.
Oh, my God, Aaron!
They would've
heard those shots,
so you're going to need to
get the signal out before they
get back. There's a security kit
behind that door in the bureau.
It's got first aid
and a flashlight.
You'll flash Morse
Code out the window.
Reach in my jacket.
I got a pen.
Here.
Give it to me.
Give me your hand.
This is called "Code Green." A dot is
a short blink; a dash is a long one.
"Code Green" will
signal them to move in.
Go!
Okay... okay...
Okay...
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
General Juma,
I have the president's daughter.
Bring him.
Your life takes you down
many different paths.
Because you're more
than one thing.
So is VENZA.
Sources have confirmed that the
siege inside the White House
began approximately
40 minutes ago.
We do not yet have confirmation on
the number of hostages being held,
or if the president
is among them.
Behind me, you can see dozens of
tactical assault units standing by.
Government analysts tell us the
order to launch any operation
in these circumstances would
rest with the vice president.
General, I discovered fiber-optic
cameras embedded in the chandelier.
Sit!
Get me a chair.
Yes, General.
He spotted the cameras.
Give me a secure channel.
Go ahead, sir.
President Taylor,
I see now that you've been watching us.
Good.
There is something I
think you should see.
God, no.
If you don't open the door, I'm
going to cut out your daughter's eyes
one by one.
And then I'm going to
cut out her tongue...
...and then her head.
Mom, don't listen!
I know what you're thinking.
How do you know if you open
the door that I won't kill her?
All you need to know is that
I most certainly will kill her
if you don't.
Open the door.
Madam President, I can't!
No. Open the door.
Open the door! I can't!
That is my daughter out there.
Do you understand?
I've already lost my son.
Have you any idea what
it's like to lose a child?
 Madam President, I am genuinely
sorry, but I cannot let them take you.
There is nothing you
can do for her now.
Do you have children, Jack?
I have a daughter.
Could you do what
you're asking me to do?
Just stand by and
watch her butchered?
No, ma'am.
But I am not the President
of the United States.
Well, I am
the president.
And I am ordering you
to open that door.
You're running out of time.
Mom...
Perhaps this will make your
mother decide more quickly.
Mom, you shouldn't have...
I wouldn't let them
hurt you, darling.
Damn it, Bauer.
What have you done?!
All right, General,
you've got me now.
There's no reason to
hold anyone else.
Let them go.
You...
don't give orders to me.
Get the camera ready
for her statement.
What statement?
The last one you'll ever give.