Subtitles: Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu
There's an IRK cell trying to smuggle
weapons-grade uranium.
Just read the assessment.
I need you to shut down
all bridge and tunnel traffic.
- Where'd he go?
- There's only one way to get in.
- Across the East River.
- That's right.
CTU was just hit by an EMP.
- All of our systems are down.
- Where's Jack?
He might be in some kind of trouble.
We need to find him.
Get the CTU back on line.
Once you acquire Jack's position,
you can direct me to him.
I have a faster way to get us back.
- They won't listen.
- You need to make them.
Do what you have to do.
Senior Engineer
at the New York field.
I hope that you're here to help.
- You going in through the CLR?
- We're gonna create a brand-new subnet.
That'll take forever.
I can create a workaround.
Why not tap into the trunk line?
It will be a lot faster.
I'm here to clean up your mess.
Leave.
You get out.
Get out!
We got power to comm.
Load the rods.
It'll be short work
once we get the rods across the river.
A vehicle is coming.
Wait until the SUVs in range,
then take them out.
Get down! Now!
I've got two men
leaving the doc in a boat.
They're carrying a box
and shape for the rods.
I got through to CTU.
They just got back on line.
NYPD's sending choppers.
We still finding them.
I know you're involved
with that robbery.
What?
You are out of your mind.
I'm not leaving here
until I know the truth.
CTU is back on line.
I know.
Their helicopter's
searching the river.
They're close.
We need your help getting clear.
I will get you out.
Stand by.
I'll call you in a few minutes.
You have grade 3 level bruising.
- You sure about painkillers?
- They're wrapped tight.
I can't know if the ribs
are broken without an X-ray.
Any more stress
could cause the lung to collapse.
They're not broken. Thanks.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Fine.
Where are we at with the rods?
We found the Zodiac partly submerged
in the river near 11th Street, empty.
The rods are in Manhattan.
CTU doesn't think we're more
than a few minutes behind.
Who's running the ground op. Cole?
Contact Chloe. Get her to download
archival photos from 11th and the river.
Have her date 'em back 15 minutes.
Fire it up. I want you ready to go
as soon as we've got a target.
Just spoke to a witness who said
he saw four men unloading the contents
of a metal crate into a yellow cab.
- He didn't get a plate.
- Can we roll back satellite?
Yes. NSA just rerouted them.
I'm logging onto their server now.
This is from one minute ago.
I'm rolling back
in 30 second increments.
- This is from six minutes ago.
- Find them in real time.
Alert NYPD. Dana?
- Right here.
- Contact Hazmat NEST teams
- get them mobilized.
- Right on that.
Almost there.
Suspects are proceeding west
- on 14th Street.
- Did you get that?
Yes, sir.
On the move.
They've located you on satellite.
- How far away are they?
- Not very.
- Hold on.
- NYPD units are on the way.
- How far out?
- Ten blocks
- coming from the north.
- Head to the south.
Turn left.
- Suspect turned south on Seventh.
- Got it.
- I hear sirens. Hurry up.
- Just a second.
I'm inserting the machine code now.
Just get ready.
Satellite will be disabled for 30
seconds.
On my mark.
Go.
- What happened?
- The trunk line went out.
Get it back!
lost picture.
Last location, Seventh and Waverly.
Copy that.
Where are you?
- On the Hudson, heading uptown again.
- You'll run into Ninth Avenue.
You'll be able
to blend into cab traffic there.
Back up.
- Cab's gone.
- Find it!
Scanning.
Help me widen the grid.
You take West of Seventh, me East.
Widening it.
Anything?
We were out for 30 seconds.
They could be anywhere.
- We're back up, but we lost them.
- I'll have NYPD cordon off the area.
You have them check every garage,
warehouse, loading dock.
They must have pulled in somewhere.
Get me the president.
Are we clear?
Good.
We're moving the weapon
into place as soon as it is assembled.
I need you to send me
NYPD patrol patterns and checkpoints.
- As soon as it's safe.
- That's not good enough.
My instructions were to help you,
not jeopardize my cover.
I will call you back when I can.
I'm afraid I have bad news.
Despite our best efforts,
the terrorists have gotten
the nuclear rods into Manhattan.
How good is your intelligence?
Are you sure?
We are. In fact we had a visual
on the suspects until a few moments ago.
What happened?
We lost them.
We're launching a multi-agency search
in the area we think they're in.
That you think they're in?
Will you be able
to find them, or not?
We're doing everything in our power,
but right know
I don't have an answer for you.
I'm sorry to have to tell you this.
I can no longer guarantee
the safety of Manhattan.
How could this happen?
CTU had one priority.
To make sure this didn't happen!
It's unacceptable!
I want you to consider
the entire resource
of the government at your disposal.
We must find those rods.
I understand.
We need to prepare for the worst.
I want all branches
of local law enforcement
ready to respond
to an imminent radiologic attack.
Set up a situation room
and assemble
the National Security team.
Has Hassan
been evacuated from the UN yet?
He will be shortly,
he's still at the UN.
Get me Jack Bauer.
How long was the satellite down?
30 seconds?
I know what you're thinking.
Odd we lost the feed
just as we were closing in
on the target.
Who was running point at CTU?
Chloe O'Brian.
You know her from before?
- Yes.
- And you trust her?
With my life.
I have President Taylor.
I call you back.
I got the White House on the line.
Jack, it's President Taylor.
- I'm calling to ask you a favor.
- Anything.
Hassan and his family
are being evacuated
from the UN and brought here.
I would like for you
to supervise that operation.
With all due respect,
I think I'd be much more helpful
staying in place here with CTU.
Secret Service is more than capable.
Maybe, but I'd feel a lot better
knowing you were on the job.
In light of the threat to New York,
President Hassan's role
in securing a lasting peace
is more crucial than ever.
I need him safe.
I understand.
I'll leave for the UN now.
Thank you.
I'll see you when you get here.
She wants me to supervise Hassan's evac
to McGuire Air Force Base.
Let's go.
I need to do this on my own.
I'm coming with you,
end of discussion.
- Do you have the rods?
- In the trunk.
Where is Ali?
He didn't make it.
I'm sorry.
Tarin will take his place as driver.
How long
before the device is functional?
All we have to do
is load in the rods.
Get ready to leave.
I want to place the bomb as soon after
I talk to the president.
Agent O'Connor.
I know. I've been briefed
by command at McGuire.
We're cleared
for a subterranean evacuation.
Hassan will be safer underground
- in he event of a the attack.
- How many agents?
Seven Secret Service,
including myself,
two of Hassan's internal security,
and you two.
- Time frame?
- Ten minutes.
There's a service tunnel
leading into New Jersey.
- We're just waiting on the vehicles.
- I'd like to see the exact route.
The protocols are
in the conference room,
but Hassan is asking to see you first.
He's in the council chamber.
Fine.
You two get started.
I'll be right back.
President Taylor wanted me to supervise
the evac of you and your family
- to McGuire Air Force Base.
- So I'm told.
And I'm glad for it.
How long will it take to be ready?
We're ready now.
My family are in the residence
awaiting your instructions.
In ten minutes
we'll evacuate you
through the service tunnel,
straight on to New Jersey.
And here I thought I would be leaving
the United Nations today
at the head of a peace march
down Fifth Avenue.
My president still thinks
that might happen.
I hope she's right.
Me too.
Ten minutes.
We need to talk about a response.
I've prepared
three retaliatory strike scenarios
- against targets inside the IRK.
- Do I need to remind you,
the Islamic Republic
is an ally?
No.
But what good is an ally
if its citizens can attack us
on their own?
A man called the White House
and he says he has the rods
He wants to talk to you.
Do we believe
he's who he says he is?
Confidence is high.
He's offered details of recent events
that no civilian could know.
Plus he's on an anonymous ICC channel
that's scrambled.
Put him on speaker.
This is President Taylor.
Good morning, Madam President.
This is going to be
a short conversation.
Who are you and what do you want?
You know I have the rods.
You know I got them into Manhattan.
What I want now is to convince you
that I have no desire
to harm innocent Americans.
And yet you're threatening them
with a bomb.
Actually,
a radiological dispersal device,
capable of contaminating 40² blocks
under a dense radiation cloud.
Any attack on the United States
will prompt a retaliation
against your country.
I would expect nothing less.
But you should listen to me.
What I'm asking for is simple.
Turn over President Hassan.
What?
He's a traitor and must stand trial.
That will never happen.
You have exactly one hour
to change your mind.
Mr. Woods knows how to contact me.
The clock starts now.
40² blocks...
how many people is that?
Between a 100,000 and 150,000.
Inform CTU of the threat,
but the ransom demand
stays in this room.
Tim, call up the New York Guard
to support first responders,
and have the military police execute
an evacuation plan.
What is it?
I'm just going to say it.
We should consider the alternative.
Which is?
We have an out here.
We should take it.
Give in to the demand
to turn over President Hassan?
No one man is worth
the lives of tens of thousands.
I bet he would agree.
Are we really
having this conversation?
Doesn't it deserve a conversation?
Not unless you're intent
on destroying our moral authority.
This country's unique place
among nations, maybe forever.
As opposed to what?
The irradiation of all those people?
Real businesses and homes
uninhabitable
for a hundred years or more?
I agree.
Giving up Hassan is wrong,
but a wasteland at the heart of NYC
is unthinkable.
- This country would never be the same.
- They'd crucify us if word ever got out
- that this could have been avoided.
- Now we're talking politics?
We're talking about
the primary role of government...
any government...
- which is to protect its citizens.
- It could also escalate.
They attack us,
we attack them back.
The entire region could be drawn
into the conflict and destabilized.
Weren't you the one just advocating
for a retaliatory strike?
In the military, we like
to talk about facts on the ground.
They have changed.
Now, we have a viable option.
Viable?
Is that the sense in the room then?
That surrendering
President Hassan is somehow viable?
First,
the people who are offering us this deal
cannot be trusted.
And if they detonate
the bomb anyway?
Secondly,
Hassan is a guest of this country.
He is my partner in peace.
And I will not sell him out
to the very terrorists
that we are determined to defeat.
And finally,
caving to any terrorist demand
weakens this nation immeasurably.
Now, we have 60 minutes
to find these bastards.
And I believe we will.
But if we don't,
and the worst happens,
we will deal with it.
We will pick ourselves
up off the floor and deal with it.
Why? Because that's what we do.
Americans don't stay down.
We rise up together
in times of crisis.
We carry on.
Is that clear?
Start the calls.
I need an updated list
of road closures and checkpoints.
I thought Arlo
was interfacing with NYPD.
He is, but National Guard units
and the FBI are on their way.
I want to know where the holes are,
so I can plug them.
I'll forward it to your screen now.
Thank you.
- Yes?
- It's me.
Do you have
the roadblock information?
In five minutes.
- Did you speak to President Taylor?
- I did.
Her response was as I anticipated.
But as the time pressure builds,
she'll change her mind
- and give up Hassan. I'm certain of it.
- What if she doesn't?
Then we'll strike a hard blow.
Either way,
the peace process dies.
It's ready.
I don't have time
to deal with these.
Can I have a word?
Certainly.
I thought Secretary Kanin's point
was a good one.
If we simply turn Hassan over,
we risk damaging the good name
of the United States.
What are you suggesting?
A third way.
A covert action...
in which
we deliver Hassan to the terrorists,
but make it look like
they took him hostage.
Two birds, Mr. Weiss.
We spare New York
and we preserve our reputation
in the eyes of the world.
I admit, I'm intrigued.
But?
It'll never fly.
You heard the president.
She won't go for it.
- Not in a million years.
- No, of course, she won't.
The question is, will you?
I'm asking
for your cooperation.
For the good of the country.
Even if I agreed to help,
it's too late.
Hassan's already on his way here.
It's not.
A Wet Ops team was mobilized
in the event of a strike
against the IRK.
If you get me Hassan's exact route,
I can redirect them
to intercept his security detail.
I don't have access that information.
It's being handled through
- the Secretary of State's office.
- We just have to get it from Mr. Kanin.
It's sedition, General Brucker.
Are you familiar
with the fourth Nuremberg principle?
If the orders of the president
are illegal,
it is our moral obligation
to disobey them.
And you think they are?
Illegal?
The president is letting her idealism
get in the way of her responsibilities
- as Commander in Chief.
- It's hardly the same thing.
You don't think so?
With the fate of an American city
in the balance?
"The primary role of government
is to protect
"its citizens."
Your words, Mr. Weiss.
It's time to decide
whether or not you meant them.
I need everyone's attention.
The White House just received
credible intelligence
that the terrorists
we've been tracking
plan to detonate a radiological device
in New York City,
in less than 50 minutes.
All of us have friends
and family who live in the city.
We know we are bound by law
not to warn them.
But we also know it is still
in our power to protect them.
We a their last line of defense.
That is our job.
That is what we will do
with every second
of every minute we have left.
Starting now.
Go back through all your leads.
Appeal to your sources
one more time.
Find that bomb.
I just heard
from our source inside CTU.
Based on the roadblocks,
Amsterdam is closed off,
but there's a potential target area
just to your left.
You'll be avoiding NYPD checkpoints
to the south and west.
All right.
Turning.
Can you park in that block?
Good.
The fallout radius will include
a good part of the Upper West Side.
I'll wait for your call.
How many men on the detail?
Eleven.
Hassan's own security,
Secret Service,
and two former agents,
Jack Bauer and Renee Walker.
Why is Bauer involved?
The president trusts him.
Believe me,
he's not someone to be taken lightly.
He's up against elite team
who will have the advantage of surprise.
Bauer and his people
don't stand a chance.
The loss of life is regrettable.
No one feels this more keenly
than a soldier
who's led men into battle.
But right now,
we don't have a choice.
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
I thought you were with the president.
I was.
What are you doing in here?
I asked Mr. Weiss to pull up the latest
White House readiness protocols.
He couldn't log on from his computer,
so we were trying from yours.
I was also reviewing
Hassan's itinerary
to see if we could facilitate
a military escort.
Open the door.
I'm afraid I can't do that,
Mr. Kanin.
Then get out of my way.
- Rob?
- Listen, I...
No, you listen to me.
I think I have a pretty good idea
what's going on here.
Sit down.
There are some things you need to know.
There sure as hell are.
But I'll stay where I am,
if you don't mind.
Do what he says.
Sit down, please.
This is Bauer. Go ahead.
I said, go ahead.
- Give me your phone.
- Get your hands off of me!
Wait!
This is beyond madness.
You will spend
the rest of your lives in prison.
Maybe.
But my guess is that one day,
the country will thank us for it.
I'm begging you.
Don't do this.
Don't betray your president.
All right.
My God! Ethan!
Here, here, here.
Call a medic.
We call for help, first thing he does
is get word to the president.
He's having a heart attack!
We must to act!
You gave him his medication.
It's not working.
You two are close.
But this is not
an emotional decision,
this is a tactical one.
We wait to acquire Hassan
before calling an ambulance,
understand?
What if he doesn't
make it that long?
We have to pray that he does.
All right?
All right.
Come on.
We pick up the tunnel
under Third Avenue.
From there, the trip to McGuire
by convoy is less than 30 minutes.
Thank you, Ms. Walker.
Secretary Kanin, this is Jack Bauer.
I can see on my phone
that you just tried to call me.
Please call me back as soon as you can.
Thank you.
CTU.
This is Bauer. Patch me through
to McGuire Air Force Base.
How far are you from an access point
into the tunnels?
Based on what I'm looking at,
less than two miles.
The security detail's on the move.
Can you get there in time?
Yeah, if we haul ass.
- And the ambush happens where?
- At the vehicle.
Remember,
the objective is President Hassan.
Do what you have to do
to take him alive.
Good luck.
Thank you. Have him call me back
as soon as possible.
Secretary Kanin tried to call me.
Now he's not answering his phone.
The operator at McGuire Air Force Base
can't find him either.
Something's not right.
Keep your eyes open.
Hold up.
- We set?
- Yeah, the vehicles
for the Hassans
are 200 meters up the tunnel.
There is a section
we couldn't get by.
Agent Dalton, standby.
We are bringing the family down now.
- Did you walk it?
- Yes, sir. All clear.
Get the family.
This way. Let's go.
Our SUVs are a short hike up the tunnel.
Stay together as we move towards them.
- Operations.
- This is Bauer.
Patch me through to Secretary Kanin.
Here they come.
Is Hassan with them?
Masks on.
Take your positions.
Wait until they are in the kill zone.
Remember, we need to take Hassan alive.
Secretary Kanin?
Just a minute.
What is it?
Excuse me, but Jack Bauer's
calling for Mr. Kanin.
- He's busy with me right now.
- I understand that,,
but Mr. Bauer's persisting.
He says it's important.
He's holding on line one.
All right, thank you.
I'll take care of it.
Hi. It's Rob Weiss.
We're in a tunnel under...
I'm sorry, you're breaking up.
Can't hear you.
We're in a service tunnel
under the UN.
We're evacuating President Hassan.
- Is everything fine?
- You tell me.
Secretary Kanin tried to get ahold of me
about ten minutes ago on his cell.
Ever since, he won't pick up.
The secretary's tied up
with the Joint Chiefs.
What did he want
to talk to me about?
Couldn't say.
It could've been anything.
I don't think so.
He knows we're making a sensitive evac.
He called me during it.
There must be a connection.
I'll make sure he gets the message.
I don't think you understand.
I need to talk to Secretary Kanin now.
That's not possible.
What do you mean?
We're dealing with an imminent
terrorist attack on our soil!
Do your job and t us do ours!
All due respect, I am doing my j...
- Son of a bitch just hung up on me.
- He's under a lot of stress.
I don't give a...
Agent O'Connor, stop.
Start walking them back now.
Something's wrong. We'll head back
to the UN, reassess there. Let's go.
President Hassan, I'm very sorry,
but you're too exposed down here.
I trust in you.
They're turning around.
How far are they?
About a hundred yards.
Okay, take out as many as you can.
Get down!
I need you to get
President Hassan and his family
to the side tunnel
and back to the UN!
What about you?
I'll be right behind you!
You need to go. Now. Now!
Go! Go!
Your orders are to stay
with President Hassan. You need to go.
I know what I have to do.
Good Iuck.
Thank you, sir.
- You ready?
- I'm ready.
Now!
See if you can get wide
and outflank them.
I'm going to try to draw them
into a crossfire.
Shoot only on my command.
Engage.
- We need to keep moving.
- Your people are being slaughtered.
- We need to help them.
- They're buying us the time we need.
Don't let it be in vain.
We need to go!
Give me a weapon.
I've been a soldier. I can handle a gun.
I'll fight with you.
My job is to protect you.
You need to do what I say. Now, go!
- We have to keep moving. Come on.
- Come on. We got to go.
We won't to make it.
Take cover.
Go! Go!
I'm going to head up the middle.
When I set these off, start firing.
Doesn't matter if you hit anything.
Just make some noise...
President?
You take care of your family.
You ready?
Let's go.
Mathis! Donner! Go!
Move! Move!
Move! Move! Move!
I'll take the high ground.
In about 5 seconds,
start giving me cover fire.
Take the weapon off.
Take the weapon off now!
Now!
Who are you?
You're making a huge mistake.
You're American.
Why did you attack us?
Because a dirty bomb
will be detonated in New York
unless we deliver
Hassan to the terrorists.
What are you talking about?
A ransom demand has been made.
Him for the bomb by 06:15 hours.
Jack, that's less than 20 minutes.
- Does the president know about this?
- She refused the deal.
This is General Brucker's operation.
- Get up. Get up!
- What are you doing?
Get you up to the street level,
so I can make a call.
There's no time for that.
This is on you now.
You have to deliver
Hassan to the terrorists.
I don't take orders from anybody
but the President. Now, move.
Keep moving.
Yes?
- Why haven't I heard from you?
- Because I don't know anything.
I don't understand. Are the Americans
handing over Hassan, or not?
We only know that he's being
transported to McGuire Air Force Base.
We lost comm with his security detail
about 20 minutes ago.
So President Taylor
doesn't intend to give him up.
Think for a minute.
You use that bomb,
you lose your leverage.
The president leaves me no choice.
The blood will be on her hands.
Tarin?
The president has not responded.
Start the countdown.
You need to stay with the bomb.
Make sure no one interferes with it.
- Did you hear me?
- Yes, I heard you.
Your name will never be forgotten.
Your family will be honored
above all others.