Subtitles:
Put the gun down Team
www.sub-way.fr (1.00)
Before his death,
Jonas Hodges told us
that there were other parties
involved with him
in the creation of this bioweapon
The FBI has apprehended
Tony Almeida.
He is a key figure in this plot.
Jonas Hodges was killed
outside FBI headquarters.
Ms. Taylor might be involved.
Olivia is capable of many things,
but I can't believe
committing murder is one of them.
I need you to access
the digital recording system.
To see if their conversation
was recorded.
What I can't live with
is that monster getting away with this.
My operatives
are with your daughter.
In fact,
I'm looking at her right now.
You will help Tony Almeida escape
or my people will murder
your daughter.
- Don't move!
- Jack, why?
The people that are working with Tony
have operatives with Kim right now.
They threatened to kill her
if I don't break him out.
The people who are watching you
are our only lead to finding your father
That laptop has the camera
they were using to track me.
We may be able to back trace
to my father.
Your people are gonna be able
to launch the biological attacks,
just as they originally planned.
How?
We have Jack.
The pathogen's in his organs.
We'll be able to harvest
what we need from his body.
Tony believes in what we're doing.
Are you suggesting I meet with him?
I'll look Almeida in the eye,
and if, for any reason,
I don't like what I see,
I can't let him walk
out of that meeting alive.
- How much longer does he have?
- A couple of hours, give or take.
The pathogen could survive
up to two hours after death.
The only sure way to destroy it
is by exposure to extreme temperatures
above 500-degrees Celsius.
Get him ready to move.
Tell me if you need more people,
I will get them for you.
We don't need people
but to get lucky.
The transmitter node on the laptop
is encrypted with multiple relays.
- Can you source the transmission?
- I'm trying with a work-around.
Call me as soon as
you have something.
- They can't source the transmission?
- They're working on it.
Chloe and Janis are doing
everything they can.
Is there no other lead,
no other way to find my father?
This is a good lead.
We have it 'cause of you.
Yeah, except my father's dying.
And we don't know
how much time he has left.
Come in.
What are you still doing here?
Just finishing up
the conversation we started.
I told you to escort Ethan
to the gate.
Take him out of my office
and off the White House grounds.
No, ma'am,
I am not gonna do that.
I'm calling security.
Having me dig up dirt
on Noah Daniels is one thing.
- This is a whole different animal.
- I'm aware of that, Martin.
I want this to happen.
I want this person taken care of.
It's Jonas Hodges.
The digital card
you confiscated from me was blank.
I gave the real one to Agent Pierce.
How long have you known, Aaron?
I had my suspicions, ma'am,
but I was hoping I was wrong.
I'll wait outside, Sir.
- This doesn't tell the whole story.
- Sounds pretty clear to me.
Hodges is dead, you're responsible.
I know, but I tried
to stop it from happening.
Save it, Olivia!
You can't talk your way
out of this situation, not this time.
All right, Ethan...
You win.
I'll resign.
Come up with some excuse.
You could have your job again.
- Everything will go...
- This isn't about getting my job back!
It's about the truth!
The truth could destroy
my mother's administration.
I am fully aware of the implications
if this goes public.
You don't have
to spell them out for me.
Then what do you want?
For the president
to take the next step.
Whether she decides to prosecute this
or bury it, that's her call.
But she needs to know the truth.
I'll let you tell her yourself.
I can't believe you're doing this.
You're betraying everything
that you've ever worked for.
You think this country failed you,
I don't care what kind of ideology
you believe in now.
This is no way to fight for it.
What you're doing is wrong.
This is wrong, and you know it!
Damn it, Tony, look at me!
Please...
As someone
who was once your friend...
Let me die in peace.
Don't let them use me
to kill innocent people.
I have no intention of letting them
use you as a pathogen, Jack.
- I never did.
- I overheard you.
This was your idea.
You sold it to them.
It was just a play.
A play?
To get the man
who's coming here right now.
Took me three years to find him.
Took me another year
to get him to meet me face-to-face.
I had to prove myself to him
by taking down Jonas Hodges.
I had to convince him
that I was a true believer in his cause.
What are you talking about?
His name...
is Alan Wilson.
He was the man behind Charles Logan.
He's the one who ordered
the hit on David Palmer,
He had Michelle killed
to cover his tracks.
This is the man
who murdered my wife, Jack
Everything that you've done today
is for personal revenge?
- It's about justice.
- Justice.
You killed innocent people, Tony!
Ten times as many people would have died
if it hadn't been for me.
The deeper I dug to find the person
responsible for Michelle's death,
the more I kept running
into men like Jonas Hodges.
They're the ones with
the crazy ideology, not me.
I'm the one who had a plan
to bring them down.
I'd enlisted Bill and Chloe to help me
track all the elements of this group.
And when I finally got
what I wanted,
they would turn them in
and shut them down.
You screwed that all up,
didn't you, Jack?
You see...
I'm the one who saved lives today, Jack.
Not you.
I'm the one who helped you
recover the CIP device,
who warned you
about the White House attacks,
I'm the one who stopped Jonas Hodges
from launching those missiles!
You tell yourself whatever you want.
You launched a biological attack
on Washington Center Station,
If we hadn't gotten there in time,
thousands of innocent people
would have been killed!
I did what I had to do
to get Alan Wilson there.
And now...
he's gonna die.
You kill him,
and no one will ever know
the full extent of this conspiracy.
I'm not gonna kill him, Jack...
You are.
Damn you, Tony.
Damn you.
I'm sorry that it has to be you.
The truth is they wouldn't let me
within 50 feet of the guy.
You're the one he's coming for.
You're not honoring Michelle's life.
You are reveling in her death,
and she would despise you for this.
We're clear.
- When's Wilson coming?
- Soon.
He wants to see
Bauer's medical record.
It's right over there.
Wilson doesn't know about us.
And it's best to keep it that way,
at least for now.
Sure.
I understand.
He's here.
Ready?
Let's go.
Put your hands behind your head.
We're all clear.
Go ahead.
That's far enough for you.
This is Tony Almeida.
- I've been looking forward to this.
- Yes, I know.
Where's Bauer?
Right inside.
Second door on the right.
Need this.
So, Cara...
thinks you should be playing
a larger role in our organization.
- You've been an asset.
- Thank you, sir.
But I believe there's a lot more
I can bring to the table.
But first, I want to see
Bauer's pathology report.
I have it right here.
This is the FBI!
You're surrounded!
- Lay down your weapons!
- Fire at will!
I repeat, lay down your weapons!
Set us down!
I need you to get me
to that green van! Go!
Stay away from me, I'm wired with C4.
Tony's got the detonator.
Stay away!
Wait, I know this trigger mechanism.
I can disarm it.
Where's Kim?
She's safe.
She's the reason
we were able to find you.
Tony's been playing both sides
all along. You need to stop him.
He's trying to kill the man
who's behind this conspiracy.
His name is Alan Wilson.
He was responsible
for killing Tony's wife Michelle.
That's why he's doing this.
You want to end this for good,
you need to stop Tony
from killing him.
Otherwise, you're gonna lose any chance
of exposing the others.
You're clear.
Let's go!
Woodside Industrial Complex.
We're at the southeast quadrant
on our way to the perimeter.
Call me when you have
an exfiltration point.
How did this happen?
- How did they track us?
- I don't know.
Thank God you're okay.
The extraction team will be here soon
but we gotta move.
It took me a long time to find you.
To peel back all the layers of people
you hide behind.
But I stayed patient.
Because ever since the day
you had her killed,
the only thing that kept me alive
was this moment right here.
You sound like you were involved
in some kind of a tragedy
but I had nothing to do with it.
See, Michelle and me
had gotten out of all this.
We made it out together.
And we were gonna start
a whole new life.
Until you came along
and took it all away
in a split second.
It wasn't just my wife you murdered.
She was carrying my son.
You killed my son!
My son!
And now,
I'm gonna kill you.
Tony, don't move!
Get him out of here.
These people think they can take
everything away from us, Jack!
Somebody had to stop them!
And what'd you do?
You ran away!
That's right, you ran away, Jack!
You're one of them now!
Congratulations!
How would Teri
feel about that, Jack?
You lost your nerve!
You're a coward, Jack!
A lot of people died today
because of you.
Including someone close to me.
You will be charged with treason
and conspiracy to launch
terrorist attacks against this country.
The only way that I see you avoiding
the death penalty is by cooperating.
Tell me who else is involved
in this conspiracy,
and I'll make sure
that your cooperation
is taken into account by the grand jury.
How can I cooperate if I have no idea
what you're talking about?
It's not gonna work, Wilson.
Whatever this conspiracy is
that you think that I'm a part of,
I guarantee
you won't find a shred of material
evidence connecting me to it.
In the eyes of the law,
- I'm an innocent man.
- You son of a bitch!
Anything else you need to say,
- you can say to my attorneys.
- Ma'am.
They're almost ready to take Bauer
to the hospital.
You wanted a heads up.
I give you Hydromorphone
to make the ride easier.
It'll make you sleepy,
but it'll break the pain.
No, not yet.
Please.
- Could you give us a moment?
- Dr. Macer wants you at the hospital.
It's all right, she can wait.
What happened?
He's denying everything.
Claims that we don't have a case
against him.
Is he right?
Maybe.
Which means he has absolutely no reason
to tell us who else is involved in this.
But I can make him talk.
If we don't find these people,
one day they'll launch another attack,
and I can't live with myself knowing
I could have done something to stop it.
I don't know what to do.
I can't tell you what to do.
I've been wrestling with this one
my whole life.
I see 15 people held hostage
on a bus,
and everything else
goes out the window.
And I will do whatever it takes
to save them,
whatever it takes.
I guess maybe I thought...
if I save them...
I'd save myself.
Do you regret anything
you did today?
Then again,
I don't work for the FBI.
I don't understand.
You took an oath.
You made a promise
to uphold the law.
When you cross that line,
it always starts off with a small step.
Before you know it, you're running
as fast as you can
in the wrong direction to justify
what you started in the first place.
These laws were written
by much smarter men than me.
And in the end, I know that these laws
have to be more important
than the 15 people on the bus.
I know that's right.
In my mind,
I just don't think my heart
could ever have lived with it.
I guess the only advice
I can give you is...
... try to make choices
that you can live with.
I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything at all.
Mr. Bauer, we really need to go.
What are you doing out of bed?
What's going on?
Olivia wouldn't say
until you got here.
You'll understand when I tell you.
It's gonna be hard enough
to say once.
I'm listening, Livy.
What's this about?
Jonas Hodges.
He's dead because of me.
Don't tell me you were the one
who leaked the information.
It's worse than that.
Talk to us.
He killed Roger.
Hodges killed my brother.
And then you agreed
to put him into witness protection.
And the thought of him getting away
was too much for me.
So I called Martin Collier.
He had once...
told me he knew someone
who could do this kind of thing.
You're saying...
Collier hired someone
to kill Jonas Hodges?
I did.
I tried calling it off,
but it was too late,
and everything was happening so fast.
Who else knows about this?
He has a recording
of my conversation with Martin.
He's agreed not to turn it over
to the attorney general.
He says he'll respect whatever
you decide to do with the evidence.
- Mom, say something.
- How could you do this?
How could you do something
so stupid?
I'm sorry!
I tried to call it off, I swear!
It doesn't matter, darling,
it happened!
For God's sake, Allison,
stop yelling at her.
Hodges killed our son.
I know what he did.
Then you know
if anyone deserves to die, it's him.
All you should be thinking about now
is how to protect our daughter.
Protect her?
How?
Destroy that recording.
And cover up a murder?
Henry,
I can't just disregard the law!
Allison, spare me your sanctimony.
You're Olivia's mother.
I'm also the president
of the United States.
And our family's already paid
a steep enough price for that.
What are you saying, Henry?
You know exactly what I'm saying.
Your job cost our son his life.
That is a cruel thing to say.
I couldn't have done anything
- to prevent Roger's death.
- But you can do something about this.
For God's sakes, Allison...
We've already lost one child.
Sorry, Madam President,
but there's some news
from the Bureau you need to hear.
Good news.
I'll be down in a moment, Tim.
Yes, ma'am.
Go, Allison.
But so help me...
destroy that recording...
and save what's left of this family.
Dad, what did I do?
We're going to figure this out.
I'm sorry.
We'll figure it out.
He's a high-value suspect, make sure
you restrict access until I get there.
Agent Walker's bringing him back
now.
- What's their ETA?
- About 10 minutes.
I'll be there in 20,
have transfer papers in order by then.
Excuse me, Chloe?
I've got to work on transfer papers,
so we'll have to schedule debriefing
- for later.
- I can come back later, or tomorrow.
You staying in town?
I want to be here for Jack.
I'd like to thank you
for all the help
- you gave me today.
- Yeah, it was interesting.
Given what you have to work with,
you're doing a pretty good job.
I'll take that as a compliment.
Thank you.
Good.
That's what it was meant to be.
Because the pathogen was weaponized,
the disease is at an advanced stage.
I'm sorry, Mr. Bauer.
All I can do is administer morphine,
which will induce a coma,
but you won't feel any pain.
No morphine.
Not yet, please.
Excuse me Dr. Macer,
Mr. Bauer has a visitor.
All right.
He'll see you now.
I'll be outside.
Thanks for coming.
I was surprised to get your call.
I'm dying.
I know.
I made so many mistakes.
And I always thought that
I would have the time to correct them.
You've the time.
Right now.
You don't know what I've done.
We live in complex times.
Nothing is black and white.
But I do know this.
I see before me a man,
with all his flaws,
and all his goodness.
Simply a man.
Let us both forgive ourselves
for all the wrongs that we have done.
Thank you.
It's time.
Olivia, come and sit down.
I can't.
I never imagined that this job
would be so hard on both of you.
I had no idea
of the price this family would pay.
And for that, I am so sorry.
But I have
a sworn duty
to enforce the Constitution.
And failing to honor that oath
would be the worst kind of hypocrisy.
I love you
more than anything in this world.
And I will do everything I can
to help you through this.
But as president,
this is what I have to do,
no matter how much
it breaks my heart.
Agent Pierce will remand you
to federal custody.
I am escorting you
to the Justice Department,
where you will be held
until formal charges
have been issued.
I'm sorry, honey.
If you'd like to talk later...
As much as I wanted
to cover this up,
I couldn't.
You don't have
to explain yourself to me.
I understand completely.
Henry doesn't.
He'll come around.
In time.
I don't think he will, Ethan.
I really don't.
I've lost my family.
I've lost everyone.
Not everyone.
Then you'll take back
your letter of resignation?
If you want me to.
I do.
I need your help,
I need it now.
The FBI has taken a man
into custody.
His name is Alan Wilson.
Woods is on his way
to pick up Wilson,
you need to sign the documents.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
- Get out of here.
- Excuse me?
- I said get out of here.
- What are you doing?
Get out.
Absolutely not. I'm staying right here
until Wilson is transferred.
Fine.
What are you...?
- What are you doing?
- Put your hands over your head.
I said do it now, Janis!
Secure your hands to that pole.
- Now!
- Okay.
Just calm down, all right? Just...
Renee, please don't do this.
Please don't do this.
You've done your job.
You arrested him.
Let the courts take it from here.
Stop this now,
before it's too late.
Don't throw away your career.
This is absolutely insane.
Larry would not have wanted this.
Don't dishonor his death like this.
Daddy.
- I'm too late.
- He's still alive, Kim.
We induced a coma to help
ease him through
the harsher symptoms.
My name is Gohar.
I'm a friend.
A friend?
We spent the last
few minutes talking,
and I can tell you he's accepted
what is happening.
Maybe he has.
But I haven't.
The stem cell treatment
you told me about. Can we still do it?
As I told you, it's experimental
and the odds of success
- are very low.
- Just tell me if it's too late to try.
Then I want to do it.
- The risks...
- I understand the risks.
And I know my father didn't want me
to take that chance,
but it's my choice now,
I made up my mind.
This is Sunny Macer.
I need immediate access
to a surgical suite.
Have Dr. Rosen call me right away.
I'm sorry, Daddy.
But I'm not ready to let you go.