Subtitles:
Put the gun down Team
www.sub-way.fr (1.00)
Agent Walker told me
that there's a chance,
a small chance
that I could help you.
I'm dying.
And whatever small chance there is
to stop that from happening
it is not worth the pain
for me to let you sit
there and watch me die.
- I don't want to lose you.
- Come here.
I don't.
What is it?
Sweetheart, I'm sorry,
but you need to go.
Hodges was behind
everything that happened today,
from the planes going down
to the attack on the White House.
He's also responsible
for the death of my brother.
All you need to know is Hodges
worked a deal. Witness Protection.
My mother approved it
and he's going free...
- unless someone intervenes.
- I'll get you
contact information, a price
and instructions
on how to transfer the funds.
Martin, it's Olivia Taylor.
I spoke to the contact,
but I couldn't go through with it.
Listen to me, Jibraan.
If you don't do exactly as I say,
you'll watch your younger brother die
in front of your eyes.
And then...
I'm gonna kill you.
The Americans killed our parents.
I'm going to make them pay.
What have you done to my brother?
This isn't my brother.
We're looking for a man who comes here.
Jibraan Al-Zarian. Do you know him?
I know him,
but he is not a terrorist.
We did not come here to debate
this with you! Where does he live?
You come into a house of worship
with information you should not have,
an outrageous accusation,
no legal warrant and threaten me.
I have not threatened you.
Not yet,
but we both know
where this is going.
It's Chloe. I found something weird
about these hits on Jibraan Al-Zarian.
You know how I said that the $2 million
was deposited over a period of 6 months?
They were backdated.
What about the extremist Web sites?
Same thing with the time stamps.
The hits were backdated 30 minutes ago.
Jibraan could be innocent.
What do you have, Agent?
Armed hostile in the back room
holding a hostage.
- What about Almeida?
- He's not in there. See for yourself.
- Is that who you're looking for?
- No.
It's Jibraan's brother, Hamid.
They're using him
to make Jibraan do what they want.
- How can you be sure?
- It's what I'd have done.
Hamid, stop!
Put it down.
We're FBI. We need him alive.
The canister's being retrofitted
to maximize dispersion.
We're on target
to release the bioweapon
at Washington Central Station
within the hour.
Your casualty estimates
are holding up?
I think they're conservative.
A significant portion of the pathogen
will escape into the ventilation system,
which will circulate it for us.
Between 8,000 and 10,000 commuters
will be exposed.
Tell me about Mr. Al-Zarian.
Is he compliant?
Yes.
His primary concern at this point
is for the safety of his brother.
All right.
What's his level of awareness
regarding the plan?
He won't know anything
about the canister until it's too late.
Good. We'll talk once it's done.
Trigger mechanism's working.
This device will tell me
where you are at all times.
It will also allow us
to talk to each other.
Talk about what?
You still haven't told me
what you want me to do.
Right now I just want you
to get on the subway
and take the Red Line
all the way to Washington Center.
And when I get there?
I'll let you know then.
I'm not stupid.
I know you're going to blame me
for something.
- Jibraan...
- What's your plan?
You're going to hurt people?
Jibraan, the only person you
need to worry about right now
is your brother.
You follow my instructions,
and Hamid lives.
You do something stupid,
and he dies...
badly.
Understood?
Good.
Red Line,
westbound,
to Washington Center, got it?
Let's go. Come on.
Sorry this had to happen like this.
We will find your brother.
You should talk to him.
Kid doesn't know anything,
except that his brother was taken
by Tony about a half an hour ago.
He didn't overhear anything
about a target or the time frame.
Right now, he's our only lead.
I don't know
if he's in any condition to talk.
My God!
Hold his head.
I'm going to give him some morphine.
No, you're not.
His wound is in the middle
of a nerve cluster.
- He can go into shock from the pain.
- I know.
Back off.
You just step out of the room.
Do what you need to do.
Where's Almeida?
- Give me the morphine.
- I'll give you
the morphine as soon as you talk.
Where's Tony Almeida?
- What's the target?
- I don't know...
- I don't know!
I'm telling you the truth!
My job was just to watch the kid
and monitor things here.
Almeida didn't tell me where
he was going or where the target is.
- How do you contact him?
- I can't.
Okay, okay.
I have a number.
But I'm not supposed to use it
unless there's a problem.
You better start
thinking of one fast.
- Where is his phone?
- I have it here.
Give him enough morphine
so that he can take the pain
out of his voice. Nothing more.
Get Chloe to run a trace
on this number.
Tell her to feed it back
to our cell phones.
Start thinking
about what you're gonna say.
You try and screw with me on this,
it'll be the last thing you ever do.
Understood?
Do you understand me?
Yes.
- Janis Gold.
- It's Renee.
I need Chloe to run a peer-to-peer
cellular trace from a GSM I.D.
I can do that.
Jack asked for Chloe
to run point on this.
What's the number?
- Alpha-Charlie-3316.
- Got it.
- Run it back through to me and Jack.
- Hold on.
- She's working on it.
- Good.
I'll open up the locate protocol.
You establish a secure VPN.
- Opening a channel on the Inter-Sat...
- Why would you do that?
What?
You know connecting through a DMA node
would be a lot faster.
I don't know it's quicker to use a node
or else I would have done just that.
I had no idea the DMA nodes
were up and running.
Really? Because they've been up
and running for about two years.
It's obvious I'll never be able
to do things as well as you did at CTU.
All I ask is that you not
make me feel like an idiot
while you're pointing that out.
All right.
Agent Walker, the trace is up
and running whenever you're ready.
Chloe, I'm on.
You ready?
What's the number?
202...
555...
0147.
It's ringing.
- Why are you calling me?
- I was checking Al-Zarian's computer,
double-checking
everything we planted.
The bank that we use in Switzerland
just e-mailed him,
rejecting one of the transfers
we made in his name.
- You know how to resubmit it?
- I'm not sure.
- Are you getting this?
- Tony's got something on his phone
encrypting his location.
I'm trying to get around it.
All right.
Call our man in Zurich.
He'll walk you through it.
All right. I just wanted to get
your authorization before I did that.
Any other problems?
Good.
Chloe, did you get that?
I didn't have time to decrypt the }data.
All I know right now
somewhere
in the Adams Morgan district.
We're running out of time.
We have to narrow that down.
I'm trying. I have to decrypt
the rest of the location data.
- How long will that take?
- I don't know.
- We've got to do better than that.
- I need to get off the phone.
Janis, I want you
to contact Metro P.D.
I want you to get them to move
their Hazmat teams and their Tac teams
over to Adams Morgan.
We're on our way now. Let's go.
- I need you to call the police.
- Excuse me?
Speak up, sir.
I can't do that.
- They're listening.
- Who's listening?
The people who have my brother.
The terrorists.
They're going to kill my brother
unless I do what they say.
They want me to get on this train.
- That's it? Just get on the train?
- Yes, please.
You have to help me, okay?
You have to call the police.
Is there a problem here, sir?
Yes, thank you, officer.
Please, I need your help.
Sir, just calm down
and step this way.
What is it?
Listen, they have my brother hostage.
Okay, you have to believe me.
Put the earpiece back in.
- What?
- I said, put the earpiece back in.
Now.
Listen, Jibraan,
I understand you had to try.
But don't do it again.
Your brother's life depends on it.
Yes, okay, please,
just don't hurt him, okay?
- Well, that's up to you.
- Yes, I'll do whatever you say, okay?
I won't cause any more problems.
I promise.
All right.
Do you remember your instructions?
Yes...
Westbound Red Line
to Washington Center.
We'll be watching.
We're always watching.
- Hello?
- Ms. Taylor, this is Agent Pierce.
Yes, Aaron?
Secretary Woods was asking for you.
You told me you were
retiring to the residence,
but upstairs detail confirmed
that you're not there.
Why is Tim looking for me?
The Justice Department is investigating
the Jonas Hodges car bombing.
They're requesting
phone and internet records
and want to interview
everyone, as well.
I didn't realize
Justice was getting involved.
Apparently, there were only 11 people
who knew Hodges was alive.
It stands to reason
that information was leaked.
- Okay, I'll get there as soon as I can.
- Where are you?
I needed to run a personal errand.
Ma'am, am I to understand that you've
left the White House premises
without Secret Service protection?
I won't be long, Aaron. Ten minutes.
Ms. Taylor,
this is a serious
breach of protocol.
Your safety is my responsibility.
Aaron, I know.
I promise you it won't happen again.
Just cover for me till I get back?
Will you do that for me, Aaron?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
This is a mistake.
We shouldn't be meeting.
Calm down. I needed to see you.
You were hysterical on the phone.
No, you don't understand!
There's an investigation.
The Justice Department
is asking about my whereabouts!
Did you think no one would bat an eye
when a government witness was murdered?
I told you I changed my mind.
I didn't transfer the funds.
The man you put me in touch with
said he wouldn't act
until he received payment.
Why would he go ahead
and kill Hodges if he wasn't paid?
Because I told him to.
What?
He called me and told me
the money hadn't come through yet.
I told him you were
good for it and to proceed.
Why, Martin?
Why would you do that?
Hodges was going
into Witness Protection,
there was
a finite window of opportunity.
And because it's what you wanted.
Right?
Despite all my warnings
for you to reconsider,
you looked me in the eye
and you said you wanted Hodges dead,
to make it happen.
And I did, and he's dead.
Oh, my God...
But my phone records...
- my computer... everything...
- Don't worry about any of those.
I'll send you a program
to erase your internet tracks.
The calls to me mean nothing.
Olivia, the time to worry
about your conscience
was before you put this in motion.
If you let this eat away at you,
people are going to notice
and get suspicious.
You will bring us both down...
destroy your mother
and her administration.
Think about it.
Is that what you want?
Okay, then pull yourself together.
I promise you,
this will all pass
if you do what I say.
Can you do that?
Say it.
I can do it.
You need to transfer the funds,
Olivia.
You do not want
this man unhappy with you.
- Hey, honey.
- Sorry I woke you.
No, no, no, that's okay. I've been up
with Teri a couple times anyway.
She's been having a rough night.
I think she misses her mother.
Listen, I just called to let you know
that my flight's been delayed.
How long?
Well, they're saying an hour.
Which probably means two.
Okay.
What?
I don't know, maybe
you should see this as a sign.
A sign?
That you should stay there,
try to convince your father
that he should be spending whatever time
he has left with his only daughter.
As much as I want to,
he made it very clear
that he does not want me around
to watch him die.
Okay, all right.
Sorry I brought it up.
Teri and I will be at the airport
to pick you up.
My battery is dying.
Is the hospital okay with that?
Yeah, I talked to Kevin.
He said he'd cover my rounds.
Well, that's great.
Well, I can't wait to see you guys.
- I love you.
- Okay, bye.
- Oh, excuse me, sorry.
- That's all right.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah, yeah, sorry.
This stop, L Street.
Next stop, Washington Center.
Next stop will be the last stop.
The package is in place.
The dispersal mechanism
is set to go off
while the train is stopped
at Washington Center.
Good, we're on the move.
I'll pick you up at 22nd.
Jack, I unlocked
Tony's location data.
- Where is he?
- Three blocks
immediately south
of your position on 22nd.
Where exactly on 22nd?
West side of the block
you're coming up on.
900 feet ahead...
800 feet...
All teams, bring your units up
from the south and prepare to move in.
- You're almost on him.
- Okay, we've got him.
Suspect is in a black van.
We can't let this turn into a pursuit.
Hold on.
Hold on!
Tony was trying to destroy
some kind of device when I grabbed him.
I got it!
Lock down this piece of crap.
- What do you got?
- Some kind of mobile computer,
he damaged it badly.
It has something to do with the attack.
Contact Chloe, see what we can find.
I'm gonna sweep the van
for the canister.
Tony's UMPC device
is damaged everywhere I look.
I don't think
I can get it back up and running.
Try a partial reconstruct. Anything
to find out what Tony's been up to.
At this point I don't even know
about our chances of even doing that.
- Chloe.
- I know.
Do me a favor.
Send me your screen.
- Why?
- Why not?
What?
Looks like I can reconstruct the memory
of the UMPC at the time it was damaged.
- No. There isn't enough intact data.
- Yeah, there is, in the PROM module.
A lot of devices
back up their memory there.
That can't be done,
not without the file headers.
Really?
- Almeida just regained consciousness.
- Thank you.
Stay with this.
I need you to walk away.
Please, you and your men
just walk away.
Where is it?
Where's the canister?
I am not going to stop
until you tell me where it is.
Why did you betray me?
Why?
I have nothing left to lose.
You tell me where that canister is,
or so help me God,
I'll lay you down right now.
You think I've got
anything left to lose, Jack?
Do it.
There were a number of applets running.
We can run them on our hardware.
I'm uploading a mirror to you now.
- You should have it.
- You think it's Jibraan?
I can't tell. But whoever it is,
they're southbound on Connecticut
at 30 miles an hour.
And they just went right through
St. Matthew's Cathedral
- and out the other side.
- He's got to be on the Metro.
Yes, the Red Line
ending at Washington Center.
Washington Center's the target.
Put these in the car.
Jack, we have Jibraan.
Jibraan is on the Metro,
headed toward Washington Center.
Chloe, it's Jack. I'm back on comm.
How much time do we have?
Not long.
He's almost there.
Okay, listen. Tony had to be able
to communicate with Jibraan somehow.
See if they were using some frequency
strong enough to work in the subway.
Looking...
Wait.
There's a proprietary K-band running.
- That's it.
- Okay. Patch me through.
Go ahead, Jack.
Jibraan, my name is Jack Bauer.
Can you hear me?
Your brother is safe.
I'm working with the FBI.
The man who was holding him
has been taken into custody.
- Let me talk to Hamid.
- He's not with us right now.
No. I need to talk to him.
Jibraan, listen to me.
Your brother is safe, but you are not.
The people who are doing this,
they gave you some kind of a package.
No. They didn't give me anything.
We've got real time coverage
of the station.
Jibraan, these people are trying
to frame you for a terrorist attack.
They had to give you
some kind of a package.
It has to be on the train.
I want you to start looking for
an abandoned suitcase,
- knapsack, anything like that.
- No, I can't tell. There's nothing.
It has to be there. Keep looking.
It was a woman.
- What woman?
- She was with them when...
when they took Hamid.
I think I saw her get off the train.
Are you pulling
into the station right now?
I want you to stay on the train
and wait for the passengers to get off.
It's a bomb, isn't it?
It's a biological weapon.
If it goes off,
a lot of people are going to die.
Are all the passengers
off the train?
- Can you see the package?
- I don't know.
Jibraan, keep looking.
It's got to be there.
- Yes. I see it. I see a duffel bag.
- Okay.
I need you to open it.
Wait. Why me?
Why must I do this?
Now, you're the only person that can
and if you don't, people are gonna die.
Jibraan, I need you to open the bag.
Look, I know I'm asking you a lot.
Please.
Jibraan, are you still there?
It looks like a bomb.
I see a light.
It's a timer.
It's counting down.
- How much time is left?
- One minutes, eighteen seconds.
That's not enough time for us
to get down.
I want you
to get the device outside.
There's an escalator to your right.
I want you to start moving now.
I'll meet you on the street.
We're about a minute out.
- That's him.
- Hold on!
I have to get out.
What is that?
Is that even yours?
I have a bomb. Okay?
This is a bomb. Get back!
Get back. I have a bomb.
Wait, he's with us.
Jibraan!
Jibraan. I'm the man who was talking
to you. Give me the canister.
These men will help you.
- Is he all right?
- Yes.
- You're Mr. Bauer?
You did great.
Thank you for everything.
I want to see my brother.
I know.
We're going to bring him here.
But I'd like you to go with Agent Moran,
so he can take your statement, please.
Follow me.
It's all right.
- You need a shot.
- I already did, 20 minutes ago.
It's not working.
It's okay.
We stopped it.
You can finally rest.
- Can I have a piece of paper?
- Yeah, sure, you can have all this.
What's that?
This is section "A",
the only thing I want.
I'll give it to you
as soon as I'm done.
Excuse me,
do you mind if I sit here?
No, of course not.
- You heading home?
- Yeah.
Us, too.
We live in Glendale.
Woodland Hills.
My husband's parents live there.
You know the Pelusos?
I don't think so.
- Do you mind doing me a favor?
- Sure.
Do you see the man behind us at a table?
He's wearing a suit.
- Short, dark hair?
- Yes.
Yes, is he staring over here?
No.
You know him?
No, it's just that
he was staring at me earlier.
Well, you're very pretty.
- What?
- No, he's moving away now.
I've got her in sight.
She's waiting at the gate now.
They should board within the hour.
I know
that the bioweapons threat is over,
but I'd feel a lot better if you'd watch
over her until she gets on that plane.
I'll let you know
when she's in the air.
Thanks.
Contact the Bureau Office.
Tell them we need an interrogation
package ready for when we arrive.
- Yes, sir.
- Thanks.
I just got word.
Jonas Hodges was killed with a car bomb
less than an hour ago.
What?
- How?
- We don't have any leads yet,
but somehow the people he was working
for found out he was still alive.
They're going to be coming after Tony.
We need to transport him in a convoy,
full guard detail, weapons ready.
We're not losing him again.
The FBI located Al-Zarian.
There was nothing we could do.
You're telling me
the canister is gone.
Damn it!
Without that pathogen, everything
that we've worked for is finished.
You should also know
the FBI has Tony.
Then you need
to have him eliminated.
- Alan.
- He knows too much, Cara.
We can't take the risk that he'll break.
You need to take him out.
I'm trying to tell you
that won't be necessary.
Tony won't be in custody for long.
- What are you talking about?
- Trust me.
We've got another play.
You'd better have.
The incoming flight from Boston
will be arriving shortly.
Once the passengers have deplaned
and the maintenance crew is given
a chance to clean up the aircraft,
we should be able to begin boarding.
We appreciate your patience.
Thank you.
At least we know
the plane's on its way.
I'll believe that when I see it.
I'm gonna get some coffee.
- Does anybody want anything?
- I'll take a decaf.
- Nothing for me, thanks.
- Come on.
- Are you sure? It's my treat.
- No, thank you.
Your husband's really nice.
He has his moments.
You know what?
I'm gonna use the restroom.
Do you mind watching my bag?
Thank you.
- Miss Taylor.
- Agent Pierce.
I know you're upset I went off protocol,
as I told you, it won't happen again.
No, ma'am, it won't...
or you'll need to find
someone else to do this job.
Aaron, that won't be necessary.
You said you left the grounds
to run a personal errand.
May I ask what it was?
I just needed to get out of here,
be alone, clear my head,
if only for a short time.
Everything that's happened today...
being held hostage,
Jonas Hodges' murder...
and seeing my father
so weak and vulnerable...
I was feeling overwhelmed.
Aaron, I'm trying to live up
to my mother's expectations.
And I didn't want her...
or anyone else for that matter...
to know I was being affected
by the pressure.
I hope you can understand that.
Yes, ma'am,
I think I can.
You feeling all right now?
I am, actually.
I guess I just needed to tell someone
what was going on with me.
I'm glad
it was someone I could trust.
Thank you, ma'am.
I'll have those phone
and internet records
ready for the Justice Department
investigators shortly.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you, Aaron.
- This is Kanin.
- Sir, this is Agent Pierce.
- I hope I didn't wake you.
- No, Agent Pierce,
I'm wide awake.
- What can I do for you?
- Mr. Kanin,
some years ago,
while I served
on President Palmer's detail,
I was made aware
of some modifications
made to the Chief of Staff's office.
During Mike Novick's tenure.
Specifically the installation
of a voice-activated recording system.
It allows staff meetings
to be logged and archived.
If you're asking whether
I used the recording equipment,
the answer's yes.
Did you disconnect it
when you resigned
and left your office?
No. Why you asking?
I'd prefer not to answer that
at this time.
I need to know
how to access the digital recorder.
You can't.
It's secured with a biometric lock.
You need my thumbprint.
Look, Aaron, if you want my help,
you're gonna have to tell me
what this is about.
Olivia Taylor's
still using my office.
Does this have to do with her?
I really can't talk about this
over the phone right now.
I'll be at the White House
within a half hour.
Thank you, sir.
Do you have something
you'd like to say to me?
- Like what?
- I think you know.
I don't think I do.
How about "Good job, Janice,
on reconstructing the UMPC"?
Or "Just maybe I should have
considered the possibility
"that you actually know
what you're doing."
You don't know me, but if you did,
you would understand
that this is the last place you should
look for any type of validation.
How about just acknowledging
you were wrong?!
- We're almost ready to go.
- Okay.
Is this her?
Yes,
but when I saw her in the Metro,
she had on this dark wig
and a leather jacket.
Your brother's here.
Let's pack up.
The coffee place over here...
excuse me...
didn't have decaf,
so I had to go all the way
to the other end of the terminal,
but I want you to know...
I got it.
Thank you.
This is Bauer.
I'm sending a link to your phone.
It's something I think you should see.
Who is this?
Open the link, Mr. Bauer.
Who the hell is this?
Your daughter's
in the company of our operatives.
And Agent Franks
has already been neutralized.
You will help Tony Almeida escape
or my people will murder your daughter.
Any effort to contact her
or warn anybody about this
will have the same result,
do you understand?
What you're asking me to do
is impossible.
Tony Almeida's already been secured.
He's under heavy guard.
That's your problem.
Put this call on your earpiece
and keep the line open.
I'm gonna be listening
to everything you say.
Now, Bauer.
You're gonna pay
for what you did to Larry.
I thought you were going with Moran.
Changed my mind.
I wanna see this through.
You're gonna make your move
to break Almeida out soon.
I'm gonna tell you what to do
and when to do it.
And Mr. Bauer,
if any of those agents in that van
get in the way,
you will have to eliminate them,
or your daughter will die.