Subtitles:
Put the gun down Team
.: La Fabrique :.
www.sous-titres.eu (V 1.00)
Sir, we just found this
among Meredith Reed's personal effects.
It's a dedicated key card, UN issue.
- To who?
- President Hassan and his family.
It accesses their private residence.
We got her.
I want to know where you got it.
Omar gave it to me.
I gave Miss Reed this key card
for reasons I'm sure are clear to you.
Sir, are you confirming a romantic
involvement with Meredith Reed?
I trust your complete discretion
in this matter.
We have a problem.
My brother confessed to the affair.
I don't know if the frame will hold.
There is no reason
to diverge from the plan.
How much longer?
Your brother will be dead
before the hour is out.
What are you doing here?
I thought I told you
to leave me alone.
CTU.
Senior Data Analyst.
Well, sounds like an important job.
- Damn it, what do you want from me?
- A place to crash, for starters.
You can stay the night.
I want you out tomorrow.
We're evacuating immediately,
due to a possible bomb threat.
You and Mr. Kanin need to move now.
President Hassan,
if you'll follow me.
He's in the third car.
The motorcade's coming up the ramps now.
This is going down now.
You can either stand here and do nothing
or you can help me stop it.
Stop Hassan's car now.
The assassin
is part of the evacuation detail.
There is no bomb in the UN.
It's too late.
Hassan's car just exited the tunnel.
You need to stop that car,
or Hassan's a dead man.
What was that?
What happened?
This is a damn disaster.
- You don't know what happened?
- How is Hassan? Is he all right?
We don't know yet.
It appears the bomb threat at the UN
was a hoax designed
to get him out of the building.
"It appears"?
An IED was planted
on Hassan's evacuation route.
And you drove him right into it!
One of our agents
detected the ambush,
tried to head him off
just as the bomb exploded.
You better pray
he got there in time.
Security there! Now!
Stand down! I'm with CTU.
Sir, we need to move you
to another vehicle. Now.
You do not want to stay here.
Get in.
Move! Move!
- Thank God you're okay.
- I got lucky.
Hassan escaped the blast, he's fine.
He's heading toward CTU,
eastbound on 48th Street
in a black SUV.
Got him.
Mr. Hastings, here.
Hassan, he's safe.
The assassin was posing
as a part of the security team.
I know. We got the info from Chloe.
The police are putting up a cordon now.
Are you there?
I've got the suspect,
he's dressed as a cop.
Entering a white low-rise
north of the UN.
- Call it in! I'm in pursuit!
- I need to put out a priority APB.
Move, move!
What is it now?
They've got a lead on the assassin.
4722 East 47th Street.
- I'm gonna need my weapon.
- Your bag's right behind my seat.
East 47th Street...
That's just above the UN.
You're gonna need to turn now.
Now! Now!
UN Four, come in.
UN Four, this is CTU Two.
Come in, please.
- I'm sorry, I can't reach him.
- Try again.
- That's my husband in that car.
- They're not answering.
- I have to go to him.
- Ma'am, you need to remain in the car.
Stay calm.
I'll try another number.
Where are you?
Yes, we're safe.
Dalia, Kayla and myself.
I need to know about my brother.
He's alive.
He survived.
How is he?
He's alive.
God is with us.
Can you tell me what happened?
A car in the motorcade
swerved in front of him.
They're locking down
the entire area.
What would you suggest we do?
It's over.
Get out now.
It can't be long
before they realize it's you.
Sir, please stay in the car!
Please, sir.
I need you to get back in the car.
Get on your knees.
Slide your weapon back to me.
Slowly...
Slow...
Now...
you're going to walk me out of here.
Call in.
Say the southwest corner is clear.
Tell them to move the search team
to the northeast.
Do it.
You want to live?
Make the call.
This is Cole Ortiz
in the southwest corner of the building.
I'm in pursuit of the assassin.
He's with me now.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Son of a bitch.
Mr. President, Brian Hastings.
We spoke on the phone.
We're glad you're here.
Please follow me.
Is my family here?
No, sir. We'll try
and get you all together shortly.
- Are they all right?
- Your wife and daughter are fine.
And my brother?
Was he hurt?
It appears your brother
was involved with the attack.
- My brother?
- Yes, sir.
That can't be right.
Bring him to me.
I need to talk to him.
Unfortunately, we don't know
where he is at the moment.
Then how can you be sure it was him?
Mr. President, after the explosion,
he killed one of my men
to facilitate his own escape.
There were witnesses,
including your wife and daughter.
He's the insider
we've been looking for.
There's no doubt.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry for interrupting.
You asked for any updates
about the assassin.
- And?
- He's dead.
Jack just called it in. He uplinked
some video footage that you need to see.
I'll be there in a minute.
- Don't let me keep you from your job.
- Thank you, sir.
No, thank you. I owe you my life.
Conference room.
Meredith Reed, the woman
you brought here for questioning,
- where is she?
- Still here.
Looks like she'll be cleared
of any wrongdoing.
- I'd like to talk to her.
- I'll arrange it.
Excuse me.
- I saw that.
- What?
The way you looked at me
when he thanked me.
- He should have been thanking you?
- I was actually thinking
he should thank Jack, then Cole,
then maybe me.
I underestimated you, Chloe.
You saw what was really going on,
I did not.
It was a major save.
And my report will state that.
- You have some video to show me.
- Yes, sir. Take a look.
These are images uplinked by Jack Bauer
from the bomb site.
It's the assassin
who was targeting Hassan.
- We have an ID?
- Not yet.
But I believe
we do have a workable lead.
These are tattoos off the two men
who attempted to take out
our informant this afternoon.
Same as the assassin.
We believe they indicate membership
in a particular Russian crime syndicate.
What's a Russian gang have against
the leader of the Islamic Republic?
I don't know.
Could just be hired muscle.
But when the photos arrived,
I ran them by the FBI.
Turns out, they had an agent undercover
working with the Russian mob here
several years ago.
- A woman.
- Contact her.
Already done.
I have a helicopter bringing her in now.
I think you worked with her.
Renee Walker.
Says here she's no longer
with the FBI.
It's true.
She resigned over an internal dispute.
Meaning she was fired
and her records have been sealed.
- What are we getting into here?
- We are only using her to brief us.
These Russian groups are secretive
to the point of paranoia.
She's the only one
who ever got close.
President Omar Hassan
was not harmed in the attack,
and has since been taken
to a secure location.
Confirmed fatalities
now stand at three...
... including a police officer.
Why is my brother still alive?
You're upset, Farhad.
- Justifiably.
- Your man failed!
Once you have the materials,
your brother, his peace conference,
none of that matters.
Isn't that what you told me?
All you have to do is stay calm
and stick to your plan.
Or should I be looking
for another buyer?
I'll be there soon.
Good.
We'll have a nice meal waiting.
And we'll talk.
I've been informed
that the bomb threat was a hoax.
That's confirmed.
We've swept the negotiating chamber
and ground-penetrating radar.
I can assure you, it's safe.
I'm glad to hear it.
Hassan is standing by at CTU.
- How is he, Rob?
- He narrowly escaped
being blown to pieces
by his own brother...
So not too well.
But your call to him
can't just be all sympathy and concern.
We need to know
where he stands vis-a-vis the talks.
- It's hardly the time.
- It's exactly the time.
The signing is scheduled
for tomorrow.
Dozens of world leaders
are en route to NY.
We need to know
if we still have a peace process.
Put him on.
Sir,
I have President Taylor for you.
- Madam President.
- I cannot begin
to say how relieved I am
that you survived
this terrible attack, Omar.
Thank you.
I'm mortified that this outrage
happened on US soil.
I'm the one
who should be embarrassed.
My brother, Farhad, did this.
He betrayed me, and worse,
he put you in harm's way.
I should have realized
what he's up to.
We can only be betrayed
by the people we trust.
He fooled all of us.
Sir, this is Rob Weiss.
You've heard Farhad escaped.
Can I ask what you think
his agenda might be
aside from targeting you?
What I mean, sir, is...
does he have a plan?
Yes, he has a plan.
Regime change.
- Isn't that what you call it?
- Mr. President,
we're doing everything we can
to apprehend Farhad,
but while he's at large,
I'd understand it
if you wished not to continue the talks.
However,
I hope that I can
persuade you to reconvene.
We have come so far together.
- And to let this moment slip...
- Would be to hand Farhad victory.
I'll not give him this satisfaction.
If you are willing to continue
with these talks,
so am I.
I am delighted to hear it.
If you could persuade
Mr. Hastings here to release me.
We'll coordinate with CTU
so that you can return
to the UN as soon as possible.
I know that you want to be
with your family.
Thank you.
Thank you, Madam President.
- You want your office back.
- It's fine, sir.
Can I ask
what you and President Taylor agreed?
That I should return to UN
as soon as possible.
We'll make the arrangements.
Before I leave, I would like to thank
the man who saved my life.
That would be Agent Ortiz.
He's returning to CTU.
You should go to Medical.
Soon as I hand
the body over to forensics.
- What are you going to do?
- Finish my debrief and go to LA.
Thanks. It's been an honor.
Take care of yourself, okay?
- I'm glad you're okay.
- Thanks. Me, too.
We ID'd the assassin
using your video footage.
We think he was working
for Russian mob here.
- Any idea which one?
- Not yet.
But we're bringing in
someone to brief us.
Good.
It's Renee.
What?
Why?
Six years ago, she worked
undercover with the Russian mob.
FBI says she's still one
of the best experts they have.
- Have you spoken to her?
- No.
I tried phoning her,
she never returned my calls.
She made it clear she didn't want
to speak to me, so I let it go.
I heard she had a rough time.
Like, a really rough time,
some sort of a breakdown.
She should be landing any minute.
She didn't want to talk to me then,
she's not gonna do now,
I want to respect that.
So, please,
don't tell her I'm here, okay?
- You sure?
- Yeah.
I'll be waiting for you
up in Debrief One.
We'll get you a set of photos
as soon as possible.
Thanks.
- Agent Ortiz.
- Mr. President.
Thank you for saving my life.
You're welcome, sir,
but it wasn't just me.
If it weren't for Jack Bauer
and Chloe O'Brian,
- I wouldn't have succeed.
- I'll thank them, too
but you risked your life for me.
You put yourself
between me and the bomb.
My family and I are in your debt.
What's that?
It's a hazardous materials alert.
- Hazardous materials?
- Please wait here, sir.
- What's going on?
- The body triggered a hazmat alarm.
- We've radioactive contaminants.
- What sort of contaminants?
Rad count's low,
it could be uranium.
It's just trace elements.
No danger.
U-235?
- It's highly enriched uranium.
- It's weapons-grade?
How did he come into contact
with that?
I don't know, but he had
to have been exposed to it recently.
- I think I know the answer.
- What is it, sir?
We're talking about nuclear materials.
If you know something, tell us.
I need to talk
to Mr. Hastings right now.
It's good to see you.
This way.
Didn't know you were back at CTU.
Yeah.
Morris lost his job a year ago.
I asked to be reinstated,
and they assigned me here.
What about you? I heard
you've been working for a security firm.
I was.
Didn't work out.
So it's confirmed
and you're certain.
Thanks.
It's Forensics.
They confirmed the composition
of the radioactive material.
It's U-235,
94.7% pure, weapons-grade uranium.
If you have an explanation,
I'm eager to hear it.
Before we started
this peace initiative,
my country was close
to developing a nuclear weapon.
Yes, our intelligence
was aware of that.
We could not enrich
enough fissile material to arm it.
Soon after our countries began
to negotiate the peace process,
my brother tell me
that someone had approached him
with weapons-grade uranium.
- Who?
- Someone who had access
to decommissioned Soviet stockpiles.
You think it's the same Russians
who were trying to kill you today?
Yes, I do.
I told my brother
to stay away from them
but obviously he had other plans.
Mr. President,
the nuclear material
that you were offered,
you have any idea where it is?
That man was contaminated recently.
Doesn't that mean the materials are here
in the US?
Farhad always used to tell me
that our country will always be
at the mercy of the West
unless we become a nuclear power.
You must find the Russians
before they can get
the uranium to my brother.
We'll do what we have to do, sir.
I'll notify my security forces
to cooperate fully.
Patty,
get me the file on Renee Walker's
undercover operation.
The stars mean
they were part of the criminal elite.
Vory v zakone.
This one spent time
in a Siberian prison camp IK-10.
The number of spires
means length of sentence.
- Three years?
- Three life terms.
Must have escaped.
Now these, broken cross,
here, here and here.
Same on all three.
So what does it mean?
Brian Hastings, director of CTU.
I appreciate that you came in.
- So what does it mean?
- It means "You can break our arms,
"and every bone in our body,
we'll never talk."
Supposed to be the symbol
for a group called Red Square.
Supposed to be?
We tried to find them but in vain.
The rumors say that they're ex-military,
special forces,
intelligence, whatever.
- I'm not sure they actually exist.
- They exist, Ms. Walker.
And we need to find them.
Why?
You're aware of the attack
in midtown today?
The smoking crater by the UN?
Yeah, it was hard to miss.
We believe it's just the beginning,
and that the responsibles
possess a unsecured nuclear materials.
Now Dana asked you here today
to brief on background.
But I have a much bigger ask.
You were undercover for nearly 2 years
with the Russian mob.
Your cover's still intact.
What are you saying exactly?
Are you asking me to go back in?
Would you give us a moment, please?
I wouldn't be asking
if it weren't important, but yes,
I want you to go back in.
This doesn't seem
in the least bit...
I don't know, ironic to you?
I know that you left
the FBI
under difficult circumstances.
Difficult doesn't even begin
to describe it.
I can get you your badge back.
I laid down my badge, Mr. Hastings.
I took it from my pocket
and I laid it down.
So why would you possibly think
that I want it back?
What do you want?
What do I want?
Nothing.
You have weapons-grade uranium
in the hands of the Russian O.C.
I can do something.
So I'll go back in...
but not for a badge.
Thank you.
We brief in ten minutes.
- Just want to say good-bye.
- You're off finally?
How did Renee's debriefing go?
- Fine until Hastings kicked me out.
- Why'd he kick you out?
It just started to get
really uncomfortable.
Is that her file?
I'm just trying to get up to speed.
They found traces of uranium
on the assassin.
Hastings says
there's nuclear materials in play.
What's that got to do with Renee?
He asked her to go back under
with the Russians.
What is it?
- Chloe didn't tell me you were here.
- I asked her not to.
I didn't think you'd want to see me.
Right.
You tried to get in touch,
and I didn't call back.
Sorry.
I was so happy to hear
that you were okay, though.
Thank you.
I'm surprised
that you're back at CTU.
I'm not.
I'm moving back to LA with my daughter.
I'm supposed to be with her right now.
Then what are you doing?
An old informant knocked on my door.
Everything went downhill from there.
The attack in midtown.
That's why I'm here, too.
I heard Hastings wants you
to go undercover with the Russians.
He does. I've agreed.
You think that's a good idea?
They need me.
I'm not worried about them.
I'm worried about you.
I know what you did.
Really?
What did I do?
You almost killed Wilson
during your interrogation.
It was so bad,
the FBI had to let you go.
Even after
everything you did that day.
I know where you are,
and it's a dark place.
- And I've come back.
- It takes longer than you think.
I wouldn't have signed up for this
if I wasn't ready.
I don't think you are.
Renee, this is too important.
You need to let them take care of it.
They will.
I appreciate
what you're trying to do, really.
You said you were to be
with your daughter.
- Please don't do this.
- Go to California.
I have a briefing.
You will receive an official apology
for your detention here,
but in the meantime I hope you can
accept my sincere personal regrets.
I'm sure you understand that
given the threat to President Hassan,
we were under extreme pressure.
I would have thought
that came with the job.
Along with the ability to handle it.
Good-bye, Mr. Hastings.
Ms. Reed.
Thank God you're all right.
I was lucky.
I heard it was Farhad
who tried to have you killed.
I can't believe he would betray you.
He betrayed both of us, Meredith.
And then...
I betrayed you.
What are you talking about?
I told them about us.
I was scared. I panicked.
- I hope you can forgive me.
- There's nothing to forgive.
But you stood by me.
You didn't deny me.
Even though
you had a million reasons to.
Before that moment...
I never really knew...
what you felt for me.
You should have.
Didn't I make it clear?
What? What is it?
I nearly died today.
And I saw...
how fragile it all is.
Not only my life,
but everything I've ever worked for.
Any good I might be able to do.
I just can't jeopardize that.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
6 years ago I was undercover with them.
They were running an arms trafficking.
We arrested everyone
except for the man in charge,
Vladimir Laitanan. He's our target.
It was through him
I heard about Red Square.
If anyone can connect us to them
it's him.
All I've read about him
says he disappeared without a trace.
- How are you going to find him?
- Through this guy.
Ziya Dakhilov. He's out on parole.
He'll take us to Vladimir.
The FBI offered Ziya full immunity
if he gave up Vladimir.
He turned it down,
kept his mouth shut and did his time.
I'm not FBI,
I'm a former felon, remember?
I'll offer him the deal of a lifetime.
Trust me, he'll take it.
Once I contact Vladimir,
I'll tell him I've heard whispers
of nuclear materials on the market.
- I'll say I have a buyer for them.
- Who? Agent Ortiz?
- You up for this?
- Yes, sir.
- How much money are we talking about?
- For nuclear rods,
we need offshore accounts
of $100 million at least.
- Probably twice that.
- Okay, I'll get on that.
Chloe will work up a story to cover
the time after your release from prison.
Now you and Agent Ortiz
need to figure out where you met,
how long you've known each other.
I thought you'd left.
Sorry to interrupt.
But could I have the room
with Mr. Hastings alone, please?
- You, too, Renee.
- I think I'll stay.
What's going on?
She hasn't been undercover
for over 6 years.
I think you're making a mistake
by putting her in.
- Tell him what's really on your mind.
- I'll tell him what I told you.
I'm concerned about her,
and this operation.
- What does that mean?
- She's not ready for this.
- You must have other options.
- Mr. Hastings.
No one else knows these Russians.
No one else can get you as close.
Unfortunately, I'm your only choice.
I appreciate your concern,
but she's right.
She's our only way in.
Fine, then I want to go with her.
I assume your plan
is trying to set up a competing buy?
I'll act as a buyer.
- Agent Ortiz has already agreed.
- He doesn't have the experience.
- This is how he gets it.
- Not with nuclear weapons on the line.
I'm requesting
that you send me in with Agent Walker.
If you're willing to do this,
I'd be foolish to object.
We'll work up a cover for you
and dovetail it with her alias.
We must work fast.
They're going to want to unload
the nuclear rods as quickly as possible.
I'm sorry.
Are you sure
this information is reliable?
- It checks out.
- All right then.
- Farhad is here.
- Bring him in.
You look worried.
Every cop in the country is hunting him,
but we let him come here?
How does looking like a scared girl
help us?
This man is our buyer.
We found him,
we can find another.
My son,
we are on the verge
of the biggest deal of our lives.
Farhad is paying us
more than anyone dreamed possible,
you want to send him away
because he makes you nervous?
Sit down, please.
- A drink first, then some food.
- I want to see the rods.
They will be on the same ship
that will transport you to your country.
As soon as we have completed
our financial arrangements.
You'll be paid, Bazhaev,
after I have the rods.
They are in a secure place.
- Show me.
- You've seen the photographs.
That's not good enough.
I want proof that the rods exist
or you will not be paid.
You want proof?
Okay. Come with me.
My younger son.
He was transporting the rods...
and he was careless.
There. You have your proof.
How long will it take
to get them to the ship?
5 hours.
I want to be there
to supervise the loading.
Whatever you want, my friend.
Now where is my money?
I'll make the call.
Agent Walker worked undercover
as Renee Zadan
for 16 months before the bust went down
and she was incarcerated.
We're focusing on the period of time
just after her release
when she's supposed
to be in Mexico working with Jack.
We're synchronizing two years
of travel materials
mostly to and from Mexico City.
What all do we know
about this Ziya that she's visiting?
Not much.
He pled out to a class-three felony
one month after the bust.
He's in Long Island City
working in a store
as a condition to his release.
That's where Jack and Renee
are headed now.
- Where exactly are they?
- En route. Just leaving Manhattan.
Chloe,
download the cover materials to them.
Walk them through it.
Make sure there's no surprises.
Jack, it's Chloe.
You should be receiving
a consolidated timeline
plus detail files
for travel and residency.
- Have they downloaded to your PDA yet?
- We got it, Chloe.
Dana would like for me to review
the facts with you, if that's okay.
We're fine, Chloe.
I know how to prep a cover.
- I'm sure, it's just...
- It's all right.
We'll get back to you.
I guess I will leave you then.
Good luck.
Thanks.
You got a problem?
You've got everyone treating me
like I'm an invalid.
You're not an invalid. It's procedure.
They're trying to sync up two stories.
He won't quiz me on the facts.
He'll decide if I'm lying.
I know. And whatever happens
after that, we need to be ready.
It's hard being with you when
you don't think that I'm up to this.
I never said you weren't up to this.
I said I was concerned about you.
It's different.
Whatever you call it, the fact is
you don't trust me, not really.
So here we are.
Me and my babysitter.
How are we on aerial?
Already in place
and they're not there yet.
Jack and Renee
are 2 minutes from target.
They should arrive
before he closes up.
Someday, you're going to have to tell me
how you picked that name.
I can't talk now.
I like your apartment, Jenny.
Real homey.
And I gotta compliment you
on your skills, everything...
is in its place.
And I've been admiring your photos,
I hope you don't mind.
And I've noticed kind of a theme.
You and your boyfriend,
I'm guessing.
Is that right?
I hope it's not too serious.
We're getting married, Kevin.
Who would have guessed?
When I saw you, you weren't
exactly wearing an engagement ring.
So tell me about him.
Kevin, don't.
Don't what?
I'm curious, can you blame me?
He's just a guy that I met.
A guy you met.
What's that mean, a guy you met?
I spent seven years in prison with guys.
Is that the kind of guy you mean?
We need to talk about this
in person.
I'm in the middle of a crisis here.
I can't. I don't have time.
In my experience, when something's
important, you make time for it.
Don't you think?
Jenny, are you there?
- Don't call me that!
- What?
I said...
You don't tell me what to call you,
you understand that?
I'll call you whatever I want!
You don't tell me anything, Jenny!
Now get back here.
I said...
that I will...
as soon as I can.
Well, it better be soon.
That's him.
Looks like he's closing up.
We'll use these for comm so I can
hear you in case you get into trouble.
This is your last shot.
You don't have to do this.
I know, but I want to.
We're closed.
What'd I say?
Ziya.
Nice outfit.
Not a lot of men can pull off a skirt.
When did you get out?
I thought
you were serving seven-to-ten.
They let me out early.
Good behavior.
With warden?
Eventually.
But it's like anything else,
you gotta work your way up.
Why you here?
I'm looking for Vladimir.
Got a business proposition
I know he'd be interested in.
What kind of business proposition?
Got a buyer,
something big being sold.
I don't know.
Vlad disappear.
Maybe.
But you can find him.
Really?
Why I do that?
Why do you think?
I don't know.
I'll cut you in.
Unless you're making so much money here
that's of no interest to you.
See? Your greedy little eyes
are saying "Show me the money",
so what's the problem, Ziya?
Parole bracelet?
They know where I am 24-7.
I'm like dog.
I leave yard, I get shock.
Then help me out.
Make some calls.
Make calls?
You know what happen
I make call asking where's Vladimir?
Tomorrow,
have accident on way for work.
Sensitive information,
done face-to-face, you know that.
You're lucky.
You get out.
Me, I'm still in prison.
Let me see the bracelet.
Come on.
Let me see it, Ziya.
What?
Have I ever messed you up ever?
Come on.
Let's see.
I can get this off, guaranteed.
You screw, you know what happen?
Cops come running in.
In two hours, I'm back inside.
Parole violation.
What?
That won't happen, I'm telling you.
I know how to get this off.
- How do you know?
- 'Cause I'm constantly deal
with people like you, that's how.
I can get it off
if I can just hold it steady.
- But... you can't cut bracelet.
- I'm not gonna cut the bracelet.
What have you done?
What the hell have you done?
He was trapped here.
And you think he'll help you now?
This is over.
This is over!
Maybe for you,
but I'm just getting started.
Find something
to cauterize that wound.
Damn it.